const ngslQuestions = {
    "level 1": [
        {
            "Question": "shu, oâ€™sha",
            "RightAnswer": "the",
            "options": [
                "wherever",
                "nowhere",
                "anymore"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bo'lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "be",
            "options": [
                "what",
                "which",
                "mine"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "va",
            "RightAnswer": "and",
            "options": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "wherever"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ning",
            "RightAnswer": "of",
            "options": [
                "one",
                "second",
                "master"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ga",
            "RightAnswer": "to",
            "options": [
                "till",
                "except",
                "until"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bir",
            "RightAnswer": "a",
            "options": [
                "the",
                "wherever",
                "nowhere"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "da, ichida",
            "RightAnswer": "in",
            "options": [
                "of",
                "one",
                "second"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ega bo'lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "have",
            "options": [
                "be",
                "what",
                "which"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "u (narsa yoki hayvon)",
            "RightAnswer": "it",
            "options": [
                "plus",
                "versus",
                "to"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sen, siz ",
            "RightAnswer": "you",
            "options": [
                "it",
                "plus",
                "versus"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "u (o'gil bola)",
            "RightAnswer": "he",
            "options": [
                "you",
                "it",
                "plus"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uchun",
            "RightAnswer": "for",
            "options": [
                "in",
                "of",
                "one"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ular",
            "RightAnswer": "they",
            "options": [
                "he",
                "you",
                "it"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "emas",
            "RightAnswer": "not",
            "options": [
                "cool",
                "tender",
                "pale"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'sha, shu",
            "RightAnswer": "that",
            "options": [
                "than",
                "while",
                "whilst"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "biz",
            "RightAnswer": "we",
            "options": [
                "they",
                "he",
                "you"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "da, ustida",
            "RightAnswer": "on",
            "options": [
                "for",
                "in",
                "of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bilan",
            "RightAnswer": "with",
            "options": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "in"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bu",
            "RightAnswer": "this",
            "options": [
                "either",
                "least",
                "enough"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "men",
            "RightAnswer": "I",
            "options": [
                "we",
                "they",
                "he"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "do",
            "options": [
                "have",
                "be",
                "what"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kabi",
            "RightAnswer": "as",
            "options": [
                "hence",
                "otherwise",
                "yet"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "da, atrofida",
            "RightAnswer": "at",
            "options": [
                "with",
                "on",
                "for"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "u (qiz bola)",
            "RightAnswer": "she",
            "options": [
                "I",
                "we",
                "they"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "lekin",
            "RightAnswer": "but",
            "options": [
                "and",
                "a",
                "the"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dan",
            "RightAnswer": "from",
            "options": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "on"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tomonidan",
            "RightAnswer": "by",
            "options": [
                "from",
                "at",
                "with"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bo'ladi",
            "RightAnswer": "will",
            "options": [
                "hello",
                "hi",
                "each"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yoki",
            "RightAnswer": "or",
            "options": [
                "but",
                "and",
                "a"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aytmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "say",
            "options": [
                "do",
                "have",
                "be"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bormoq",
            "RightAnswer": "go",
            "options": [
                "say",
                "do",
                "have"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shuning uchun",
            "RightAnswer": "so",
            "options": [
                "badly",
                "abroad",
                "apart"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "barcha",
            "RightAnswer": "all",
            "options": [
                "this",
                "either",
                "least"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "agar",
            "RightAnswer": "if",
            "options": [
                "or",
                "but",
                "and"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bir",
            "RightAnswer": "one",
            "options": [
                "second",
                "master",
                "fashion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bo'lardi",
            "RightAnswer": "would",
            "options": [
                "will",
                "hello",
                "hi"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haqida",
            "RightAnswer": "about",
            "options": [
                "by",
                "from",
                "at"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qila olmoq, mumkin",
            "RightAnswer": "can",
            "options": [
                "ought",
                "must",
                "might"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qaysi",
            "RightAnswer": "which",
            "options": [
                "mine",
                "neither",
                "none"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "u yerda",
            "RightAnswer": "there",
            "options": [
                "instead",
                "down",
                "out"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "know",
            "options": [
                "go",
                "say",
                "do"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'proq",
            "RightAnswer": "more",
            "options": [
                "as",
                "hence",
                "otherwise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "get",
            "options": [
                "know",
                "go",
                "say"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kim",
            "RightAnswer": "who",
            "options": [
                "she",
                "I",
                "we"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yoqtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "like",
            "options": [
                "swear",
                "damn",
                "prompt"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qachon",
            "RightAnswer": "when",
            "options": [
                "so",
                "badly",
                "abroad"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'ylamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "think",
            "options": [
                "get",
                "know",
                "go"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qilmoq, yaratmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "make",
            "options": [
                "think",
                "get",
                "know"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vaqt",
            "RightAnswer": "time",
            "options": [
                "can",
                "ought",
                "must"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'rmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "see",
            "options": [
                "make",
                "think",
                "get"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 2": [
        {
            "Question": "nima",
            "RightAnswer": "what",
            "options": [
                "which",
                "mine",
                "neither"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yuqoriga",
            "RightAnswer": "up",
            "options": [
                "back",
                "nowadays",
                "aside"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ba'zi",
            "RightAnswer": "some",
            "options": [
                "all",
                "this",
                "either"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshqa",
            "RightAnswer": "other",
            "options": [
                "some",
                "all",
                "this"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashqarida",
            "RightAnswer": "out",
            "options": [
                "up",
                "back",
                "nowadays"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaxshi",
            "RightAnswer": "good",
            "options": [
                "bad",
                "young",
                "large"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "odamlar",
            "RightAnswer": "people",
            "options": [
                "time",
                "can",
                "ought"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yil",
            "RightAnswer": "year",
            "options": [
                "people",
                "time",
                "can"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "take",
            "options": [
                "see",
                "make",
                "think"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yo'q",
            "RightAnswer": "no",
            "options": [
                "several",
                "few",
                "every"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaxshi",
            "RightAnswer": "well",
            "options": [
                "faithfully",
                "gently",
                "subsequently"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chunki",
            "RightAnswer": "because",
            "options": [
                "if",
                "or",
                "but"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "juda",
            "RightAnswer": "very",
            "options": [
                "not",
                "cool",
                "tender"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "faqat",
            "RightAnswer": "just",
            "options": [
                "very",
                "not",
                "cool"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kelmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "come",
            "options": [
                "take",
                "see",
                "make"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qila olardi",
            "RightAnswer": "could",
            "options": [
                "would",
                "will",
                "hello"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "work",
            "options": [
                "found",
                "rear",
                "lean"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "foydalanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "use",
            "options": [
                "work",
                "found",
                "rear"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qaraganda",
            "RightAnswer": "than",
            "options": [
                "while",
                "whilst",
                "whenever"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hozir",
            "RightAnswer": "now",
            "options": [
                "just",
                "very",
                "not"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "keyin",
            "RightAnswer": "then",
            "options": [
                "now",
                "just",
                "very"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yana, ham",
            "RightAnswer": "also",
            "options": [
                "then",
                "now",
                "just"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ichiga",
            "RightAnswer": "into",
            "options": [
                "about",
                "by",
                "from"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "faqat",
            "RightAnswer": "only",
            "options": [
                "well",
                "faithfully",
                "gently"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qaramoq",
            "RightAnswer": "look",
            "options": [
                "come",
                "take",
                "see"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xohlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "want",
            "options": [
                "look",
                "come",
                "take"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "give",
            "options": [
                "want",
                "look",
                "come"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "birinchi",
            "RightAnswer": "first",
            "options": [
                "ashamed",
                "lazy",
                "fortunate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yangi",
            "RightAnswer": "new",
            "options": [
                "good",
                "bad",
                "young"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yo'l",
            "RightAnswer": "way",
            "options": [
                "year",
                "people",
                "time"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "topmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "find",
            "options": [
                "give",
                "want",
                "look"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ustidan",
            "RightAnswer": "over",
            "options": [
                "near",
                "unlike",
                "via"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "har qanday",
            "RightAnswer": "any",
            "options": [
                "other",
                "some",
                "all"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "keyin",
            "RightAnswer": "after",
            "options": [
                "inside",
                "alongside",
                "regardless"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kun",
            "RightAnswer": "day",
            "options": [
                "way",
                "year",
                "people"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qayerda",
            "RightAnswer": "where",
            "options": [
                "when",
                "so",
                "badly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "narsa",
            "RightAnswer": "thing",
            "options": [
                "day",
                "way",
                "year"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "eng",
            "RightAnswer": "most",
            "options": [
                "more",
                "as",
                "hence"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kerak",
            "RightAnswer": "should",
            "options": [
                "could",
                "would",
                "will"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kerak",
            "RightAnswer": "need",
            "options": [
                "use",
                "work",
                "found"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'p miqdorda",
            "RightAnswer": "much",
            "options": [
                "no",
                "several",
                "few"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'g'ri",
            "RightAnswer": "right",
            "options": [
                "alright",
                "okay",
                "monthly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qanday",
            "RightAnswer": "how",
            "options": [
                "also",
                "then",
                "now"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "orqa",
            "RightAnswer": "back",
            "options": [
                "nowadays",
                "aside",
                "forth"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "anglatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "mean",
            "options": [
                "insure",
                "compute",
                "unite"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hatto",
            "RightAnswer": "even",
            "options": [
                "how",
                "also",
                "then"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mumkin",
            "RightAnswer": "may",
            "options": [
                "should",
                "could",
                "would"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bu yerda",
            "RightAnswer": "here",
            "options": [
                "even",
                "how",
                "also"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'p sonli",
            "RightAnswer": "many",
            "options": [
                "any",
                "other",
                "some"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shunday",
            "RightAnswer": "such",
            "options": [
                "many",
                "any",
                "other"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 3": [
        {
            "Question": "oxirgi",
            "RightAnswer": "last",
            "options": [
                "first",
                "ashamed",
                "lazy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bola",
            "RightAnswer": "child",
            "options": [
                "thing",
                "day",
                "way"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aytmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "tell",
            "options": [
                "find",
                "give",
                "want"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haqiqatan",
            "RightAnswer": "really",
            "options": [
                "here",
                "even",
                "how"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'ng'iroq qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "call",
            "options": [
                "need",
                "use",
                "work"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oldin",
            "RightAnswer": "before",
            "options": [
                "after",
                "inside",
                "alongside"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kompaniya",
            "RightAnswer": "company",
            "options": [
                "child",
                "thing",
                "day"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "orqali",
            "RightAnswer": "through",
            "options": [
                "over",
                "near",
                "unlike"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "pastga",
            "RightAnswer": "down",
            "options": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "back"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'rsatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "show",
            "options": [
                "call",
                "need",
                "use"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hayot",
            "RightAnswer": "life",
            "options": [
                "company",
                "child",
                "thing"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "erkak",
            "RightAnswer": "man",
            "options": [
                "life",
                "company",
                "child"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'zgartirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "change",
            "options": [
                "show",
                "call",
                "need"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "joy",
            "RightAnswer": "place",
            "options": [
                "sir",
                "outside",
                "tonight"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uzun",
            "RightAnswer": "long",
            "options": [
                "last",
                "first",
                "ashamed"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "orasida",
            "RightAnswer": "between",
            "options": [
                "into",
                "about",
                "by"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "his qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "feel",
            "options": [
                "tell",
                "find",
                "give"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ham, juda",
            "RightAnswer": "too",
            "options": [
                "really",
                "here",
                "even"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hali ham",
            "RightAnswer": "still",
            "options": [
                "only",
                "well",
                "faithfully"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muammo",
            "RightAnswer": "problem",
            "options": [
                "man",
                "life",
                "company"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yozmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "write",
            "options": [
                "feel",
                "tell",
                "find"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bir xil",
            "RightAnswer": "same",
            "options": [
                "new",
                "good",
                "bad"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'p",
            "RightAnswer": "lot",
            "options": [
                "problem",
                "man",
                "life"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ajoyib",
            "RightAnswer": "great",
            "options": [
                "same",
                "new",
                "good"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "harakat qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "try",
            "options": [
                "change",
                "show",
                "call"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tark etmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "leave",
            "options": [
                "write",
                "feel",
                "tell"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "raqam",
            "RightAnswer": "number",
            "options": [
                "lot",
                "problem",
                "man"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ikkisi ham",
            "RightAnswer": "both",
            "options": [
                "such",
                "many",
                "any"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ega bo'lmoq, o'zi",
            "RightAnswer": "own",
            "options": [
                "latter",
                "sharp",
                "round"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qism",
            "RightAnswer": "part",
            "options": [
                "number",
                "lot",
                "problem"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nuqta",
            "RightAnswer": "point",
            "options": [
                "place",
                "sir",
                "outside"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oz, kichkina",
            "RightAnswer": "little",
            "options": [
                "long",
                "last",
                "first"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yordam bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "help",
            "options": [
                "try",
                "change",
                "show"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "so'ramoq",
            "RightAnswer": "ask",
            "options": [
                "leave",
                "write",
                "feel"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uchrashmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "meet",
            "options": [
                "ask",
                "leave",
                "write"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "start",
            "options": [
                "help",
                "try",
                "change"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "gaplashmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "talk",
            "options": [
                "start",
                "help",
                "try"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nimadir",
            "RightAnswer": "something",
            "options": [
                "who",
                "she",
                "I"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'ymoq",
            "RightAnswer": "put",
            "options": [
                "meet",
                "ask",
                "leave"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yana bir",
            "RightAnswer": "another",
            "options": [
                "both",
                "such",
                "many"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bo'lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "become",
            "options": [
                "put",
                "meet",
                "ask"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiziqish",
            "RightAnswer": "interest",
            "options": [
                "point",
                "place",
                "sir"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mamlakat",
            "RightAnswer": "country",
            "options": [
                "part",
                "number",
                "lot"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "eski, qari",
            "RightAnswer": "old",
            "options": [
                "great",
                "same",
                "new"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "har biri",
            "RightAnswer": "each",
            "options": [
                "another",
                "both",
                "such"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maktab",
            "RightAnswer": "school",
            "options": [
                "country",
                "part",
                "number"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kech",
            "RightAnswer": "late",
            "options": [
                "little",
                "long",
                "last"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "baland",
            "RightAnswer": "high",
            "options": [
                "late",
                "little",
                "long"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshqacha",
            "RightAnswer": "different",
            "options": [
                "old",
                "great",
                "same"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'chirilgan",
            "RightAnswer": "off",
            "options": [
                "through",
                "over",
                "near"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 4": [
        {
            "Question": "keyingi",
            "RightAnswer": "next",
            "options": [
                "high",
                "late",
                "little"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oxir",
            "RightAnswer": "end",
            "options": [
                "interest",
                "point",
                "place"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yashamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "live",
            "options": [
                "become",
                "put",
                "meet"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nima uchun",
            "RightAnswer": "why",
            "options": [
                "too",
                "really",
                "here"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "paytda",
            "RightAnswer": "while",
            "options": [
                "whilst",
                "whenever",
                "nevertheless"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dunyo",
            "RightAnswer": "world",
            "options": [
                "school",
                "country",
                "part"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hafta",
            "RightAnswer": "week",
            "options": [
                "world",
                "school",
                "country"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'ynamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "play",
            "options": [
                "talk",
                "start",
                "help"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mumkin",
            "RightAnswer": "might",
            "options": [
                "may",
                "should",
                "could"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kerak",
            "RightAnswer": "must",
            "options": [
                "might",
                "may",
                "should"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uy",
            "RightAnswer": "home",
            "options": [
                "bottom",
                "compound",
                "fat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hech qachon",
            "RightAnswer": "never",
            "options": [
                "why",
                "too",
                "really"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'z ichiga olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "include",
            "options": [
                "live",
                "become",
                "put"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kurs",
            "RightAnswer": "course",
            "options": [
                "week",
                "world",
                "school"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uy",
            "RightAnswer": "house",
            "options": [
                "course",
                "week",
                "world"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hisobot",
            "RightAnswer": "report",
            "options": [
                "play",
                "talk",
                "start"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "guruh",
            "RightAnswer": "group",
            "options": [
                "house",
                "course",
                "week"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "holat",
            "RightAnswer": "case",
            "options": [
                "group",
                "house",
                "course"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ayol",
            "RightAnswer": "woman",
            "options": [
                "case",
                "group",
                "house"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "atrofida",
            "RightAnswer": "around",
            "options": [
                "off",
                "through",
                "over"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kitob",
            "RightAnswer": "book",
            "options": [
                "end",
                "interest",
                "point"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oila",
            "RightAnswer": "family",
            "options": [
                "woman",
                "case",
                "group"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'rinmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "seem",
            "options": [
                "include",
                "live",
                "become"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ruxsat bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "let",
            "options": [
                "seem",
                "include",
                "live"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yana",
            "RightAnswer": "again",
            "options": [
                "never",
                "why",
                "too"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tur, xushmuomala",
            "RightAnswer": "kind",
            "options": [
                "criteria",
                "thirst",
                "hunger"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "saqlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "keep",
            "options": [
                "let",
                "seem",
                "include"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "eshitmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "hear",
            "options": [
                "keep",
                "let",
                "seem"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tizim",
            "RightAnswer": "system",
            "options": [
                "family",
                "woman",
                "case"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "har",
            "RightAnswer": "every",
            "options": [
                "that",
                "than",
                "while"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "savol",
            "RightAnswer": "question",
            "options": [
                "book",
                "end",
                "interest"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "davomida",
            "RightAnswer": "during",
            "options": [
                "between",
                "into",
                "about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "har doim",
            "RightAnswer": "always",
            "options": [
                "again",
                "never",
                "why"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "katta",
            "RightAnswer": "big",
            "options": [
                "different",
                "old",
                "great"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'rnatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "set",
            "options": [
                "report",
                "play",
                "talk"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kichik",
            "RightAnswer": "small",
            "options": [
                "big",
                "different",
                "old"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'rganmoq, o'qimoq",
            "RightAnswer": "study",
            "options": [
                "set",
                "report",
                "play"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ergashmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "follow",
            "options": [
                "hear",
                "keep",
                "let"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "begin",
            "options": [
                "follow",
                "hear",
                "keep"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muhim",
            "RightAnswer": "important",
            "options": [
                "small",
                "big",
                "different"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dan beri",
            "RightAnswer": "since",
            "options": [
                "before",
                "after",
                "inside"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yugurmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "run",
            "options": [
                "study",
                "set",
                "report"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ostida",
            "RightAnswer": "under",
            "options": [
                "during",
                "between",
                "into"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "burilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "turn",
            "options": [
                "run",
                "study",
                "set"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ozchilik",
            "RightAnswer": "few",
            "options": [
                "every",
                "that",
                "than"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "olib kelmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "bring",
            "options": [
                "begin",
                "follow",
                "hear"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "erta",
            "RightAnswer": "early",
            "options": [
                "next",
                "high",
                "late"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'l",
            "RightAnswer": "hand",
            "options": [
                "question",
                "book",
                "end"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "davlat",
            "RightAnswer": "state",
            "options": [
                "hand",
                "question",
                "book"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'chmoq, harakatlanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "move",
            "options": [
                "turn",
                "run",
                "study"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 5": [
        {
            "Question": "pul",
            "RightAnswer": "money",
            "options": [
                "system",
                "family",
                "woman"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haqiqat",
            "RightAnswer": "fact",
            "options": [
                "money",
                "system",
                "family"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ammo",
            "RightAnswer": "however",
            "options": [
                "where",
                "when",
                "so"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hudud",
            "RightAnswer": "area",
            "options": [
                "fact",
                "money",
                "system"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taqdim etmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "provide",
            "options": [
                "bring",
                "begin",
                "follow"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ism",
            "RightAnswer": "name",
            "options": [
                "state",
                "hand",
                "question"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'qimoq",
            "RightAnswer": "read",
            "options": [
                "provide",
                "bring",
                "begin"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "do'st",
            "RightAnswer": "friend",
            "options": [
                "area",
                "fact",
                "money"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oy",
            "RightAnswer": "month",
            "options": [
                "friend",
                "area",
                "fact"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "katta",
            "RightAnswer": "large",
            "options": [
                "important",
                "small",
                "fat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "biznes",
            "RightAnswer": "business",
            "options": [
                "month",
                "friend",
                "area"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "siz, ega emas",
            "RightAnswer": "without",
            "options": [
                "under",
                "during",
                "between"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ma'lumot",
            "RightAnswer": "information",
            "options": [
                "business",
                "month",
                "friend"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ochmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "open",
            "options": [
                "own",
                "latter",
                "sharp"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "buyurtma",
            "RightAnswer": "order",
            "options": [
                "name",
                "state",
                "hand"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hukumat",
            "RightAnswer": "government",
            "options": [
                "information",
                "business",
                "month"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "so'z",
            "RightAnswer": "word",
            "options": [
                "government",
                "information",
                "business"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "masala",
            "RightAnswer": "issue",
            "options": [
                "order",
                "name",
                "state"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bozor",
            "RightAnswer": "market",
            "options": [
                "word",
                "government",
                "information"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'lamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "pay",
            "options": [
                "move",
                "turn",
                "run"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qurmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "build",
            "options": [
                "read",
                "provide",
                "bring"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ushlab turmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "hold",
            "options": [
                "build",
                "read",
                "provide"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xizmat",
            "RightAnswer": "service",
            "options": [
                "market",
                "word",
                "government"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qarshi",
            "RightAnswer": "against",
            "options": [
                "without",
                "under",
                "during"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishonmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "believe",
            "options": [
                "hold",
                "build",
                "read"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ikkinchi",
            "RightAnswer": "second",
            "options": [
                "master",
                "fashion",
                "spring"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "garchi",
            "RightAnswer": "though",
            "options": [
                "whereas",
                "unless",
                "nor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ha",
            "RightAnswer": "yes",
            "options": [
                "always",
                "again",
                "never"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sevgi",
            "RightAnswer": "love",
            "options": [
                "issue",
                "order",
                "name"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oshmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "increase",
            "options": [
                "pay",
                "move",
                "turn"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ish",
            "RightAnswer": "job",
            "options": [
                "service",
                "market",
                "word"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "reja",
            "RightAnswer": "plan",
            "options": [
                "love",
                "issue",
                "order"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "natija",
            "RightAnswer": "result",
            "options": [
                "plan",
                "love",
                "issue"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uzoqda",
            "RightAnswer": "away",
            "options": [
                "yes",
                "always",
                "again"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "misol",
            "RightAnswer": "example",
            "options": [
                "job",
                "service",
                "market"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sodir bo'lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "happen",
            "options": [
                "believe",
                "hold",
                "build"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taklif qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "offer",
            "options": [
                "increase",
                "pay",
                "move"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yosh",
            "RightAnswer": "young",
            "options": [
                "large",
                "important",
                "small"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaqin",
            "RightAnswer": "close",
            "options": [
                "mean",
                "insure",
                "compute"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dastur",
            "RightAnswer": "program",
            "options": [
                "result",
                "plan",
                "love"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshqarish",
            "RightAnswer": "lead",
            "options": [
                "offer",
                "increase",
                "pay"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sotib olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "buy",
            "options": [
                "happen",
                "believe",
                "hold"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tushunmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "understand",
            "options": [
                "buy",
                "happen",
                "believe"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rahmat aytmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "thank",
            "options": [
                "lead",
                "offer",
                "increase"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uzoq",
            "RightAnswer": "far",
            "options": [
                "still",
                "only",
                "well"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bugun",
            "RightAnswer": "today",
            "options": [
                "home",
                "bottom",
                "compound"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "soat",
            "RightAnswer": "hour",
            "options": [
                "example",
                "job",
                "service"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "talaba",
            "RightAnswer": "student",
            "options": [
                "hour",
                "example",
                "job"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yuz",
            "RightAnswer": "face",
            "options": [
                "program",
                "result",
                "plan"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "umid",
            "RightAnswer": "hope",
            "options": [
                "thank",
                "lead",
                "offer"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 6": [
        {
            "Question": "g'oya",
            "RightAnswer": "idea",
            "options": [
                "student",
                "hour",
                "example"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "narx",
            "RightAnswer": "cost",
            "options": [
                "face",
                "program",
                "result"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kamroq",
            "RightAnswer": "less",
            "options": [
                "most",
                "more",
                "as"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xona",
            "RightAnswer": "room",
            "options": [
                "idea",
                "student",
                "hour"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "gacha",
            "RightAnswer": "until",
            "options": [
                "since",
                "before",
                "after"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sabab",
            "RightAnswer": "reason",
            "options": [
                "room",
                "idea",
                "student"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shakl",
            "RightAnswer": "form",
            "options": [
                "cost",
                "face",
                "program"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sarflamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "spend",
            "options": [
                "understand",
                "buy",
                "happen"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bosh",
            "RightAnswer": "head",
            "options": [
                "form",
                "cost",
                "face"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mashina",
            "RightAnswer": "car",
            "options": [
                "reason",
                "room",
                "idea"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'rganmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "learn",
            "options": [
                "spend",
                "understand",
                "buy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "daraja",
            "RightAnswer": "level",
            "options": [
                "kind",
                "criteria",
                "thirst"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shaxs",
            "RightAnswer": "person",
            "options": [
                "car",
                "reason",
                "room"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tajriba",
            "RightAnswer": "experience",
            "options": [
                "head",
                "form",
                "cost"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bir marta",
            "RightAnswer": "once",
            "options": [
                "however",
                "where",
                "when"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "a'zo",
            "RightAnswer": "member",
            "options": [
                "person",
                "car",
                "reason"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yetarli",
            "RightAnswer": "enough",
            "options": [
                "much",
                "no",
                "several"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yomon",
            "RightAnswer": "bad",
            "options": [
                "young",
                "large",
                "important"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shahar",
            "RightAnswer": "city",
            "options": [
                "member",
                "person",
                "car"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tun",
            "RightAnswer": "night",
            "options": [
                "city",
                "member",
                "person"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qodir",
            "RightAnswer": "able",
            "options": [
                "bad",
                "young",
                "large"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'llamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "support",
            "options": [
                "hope",
                "thank",
                "lead"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...mi yoki",
            "RightAnswer": "whether",
            "options": [
                "because",
                "if",
                "or"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chiziq",
            "RightAnswer": "line",
            "options": [
                "experience",
                "head",
                "form"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taqdim etmoq, namoyish qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "present",
            "options": [
                "tall",
                "opposite",
                "left"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tomon",
            "RightAnswer": "side",
            "options": [
                "night",
                "city",
                "member"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "juda",
            "RightAnswer": "quite",
            "options": [
                "away",
                "yes",
                "always"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "garchi",
            "RightAnswer": "although",
            "options": [
                "whether",
                "because",
                "if"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "amin bo'lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "sure",
            "options": [
                "able",
                "bad",
                "young"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muddat",
            "RightAnswer": "term",
            "options": [
                "side",
                "night",
                "city"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "eng kam",
            "RightAnswer": "least",
            "options": [
                "enough",
                "much",
                "no"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yosh",
            "RightAnswer": "age",
            "options": [
                "term",
                "side",
                "night"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "past",
            "RightAnswer": "low",
            "options": [
                "early",
                "next",
                "high"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "gapirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "speak",
            "options": [
                "learn",
                "spend",
                "understand"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ichida",
            "RightAnswer": "within",
            "options": [
                "against",
                "without",
                "under"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jarayon",
            "RightAnswer": "process",
            "options": [
                "line",
                "experience",
                "head"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jamoat",
            "RightAnswer": "public",
            "options": [
                "tight",
                "wild",
                "quiet"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tez-tez",
            "RightAnswer": "often",
            "options": [
                "quite",
                "away",
                "yes"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "poezd",
            "RightAnswer": "train",
            "options": [
                "process",
                "line",
                "experience"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mumkin",
            "RightAnswer": "possible",
            "options": [
                "sure",
                "able",
                "bad"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aslida",
            "RightAnswer": "actually",
            "options": [
                "often",
                "quite",
                "away"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaxshiroq",
            "RightAnswer": "rather",
            "options": [
                "actually",
                "often",
                "quite"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'rinish",
            "RightAnswer": "view",
            "options": [
                "train",
                "process",
                "line"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "birga",
            "RightAnswer": "together",
            "options": [
                "rather",
                "actually",
                "often"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hisobga olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "consider",
            "options": [
                "speak",
                "learn",
                "spend"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "narx",
            "RightAnswer": "price",
            "options": [
                "view",
                "train",
                "process"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ota-ona",
            "RightAnswer": "parent",
            "options": [
                "age",
                "term",
                "side"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiyin",
            "RightAnswer": "hard",
            "options": [
                "low",
                "early",
                "next"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bazm",
            "RightAnswer": "party",
            "options": [
                "parent",
                "age",
                "term"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mahalliy",
            "RightAnswer": "local",
            "options": [
                "possible",
                "sure",
                "able"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 7": [
        {
            "Question": "nazorat",
            "RightAnswer": "control",
            "options": [
                "support",
                "hope",
                "thank"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "allaqachon",
            "RightAnswer": "already",
            "options": [
                "together",
                "rather",
                "actually"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashvish, qiziqish",
            "RightAnswer": "concern",
            "options": [
                "price",
                "view",
                "train"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mahsulot",
            "RightAnswer": "product",
            "options": [
                "party",
                "parent",
                "age"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yo'qotmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "lose",
            "options": [
                "consider",
                "speak",
                "learn"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hikoya",
            "RightAnswer": "story",
            "options": [
                "product",
                "party",
                "parent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "deyarli",
            "RightAnswer": "almost",
            "options": [
                "already",
                "together",
                "rather"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "davom ettirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "continue",
            "options": [
                "lose",
                "consider",
                "speak"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "turmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "stand",
            "options": [
                "control",
                "support",
                "hope"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "butun",
            "RightAnswer": "whole",
            "options": [
                "public",
                "tight",
                "wild"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hali",
            "RightAnswer": "yet",
            "options": [
                "once",
                "however",
                "where"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "baholamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "rate",
            "options": [
                "concern",
                "price",
                "view"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "parvarish",
            "RightAnswer": "care",
            "options": [
                "rate",
                "concern",
                "price"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kutmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "expect",
            "options": [
                "continue",
                "lose",
                "consider"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta'sir",
            "RightAnswer": "effect",
            "options": [
                "care",
                "rate",
                "concern"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tur, nav",
            "RightAnswer": "sort",
            "options": [
                "effect",
                "care",
                "rate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qachondir",
            "RightAnswer": "ever",
            "options": [
                "almost",
                "already",
                "together"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "istalgan narsa",
            "RightAnswer": "anything",
            "options": [
                "something",
                "who",
                "she"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sabab",
            "RightAnswer": "cause",
            "options": [
                "sort",
                "effect",
                "care"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tushmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "fall",
            "options": [
                "stand",
                "control",
                "support"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kelishmoq, bitim",
            "RightAnswer": "deal",
            "options": [
                "cause",
                "sort",
                "effect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "suv",
            "RightAnswer": "water",
            "options": [
                "deal",
                "cause",
                "sort"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yubormoq",
            "RightAnswer": "send",
            "options": [
                "expect",
                "continue",
                "lose"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ruxsat bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "allow",
            "options": [
                "send",
                "expect",
                "continue"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tez orada",
            "RightAnswer": "soon",
            "options": [
                "ever",
                "almost",
                "already"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "soat , kuzatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "watch",
            "options": [
                "fall",
                "stand",
                "control"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asos",
            "RightAnswer": "base",
            "options": [
                "water",
                "deal",
                "cause"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ehtimol",
            "RightAnswer": "probably",
            "options": [
                "soon",
                "ever",
                "almost"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taklif qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "suggest",
            "options": [
                "allow",
                "send",
                "expect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'tmish, oâ€˜tmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "past",
            "options": [
                "east",
                "plenty",
                "west"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kuch, hokimiyat",
            "RightAnswer": "power",
            "options": [
                "base",
                "water",
                "deal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "test, sinov",
            "RightAnswer": "test",
            "options": [
                "power",
                "base",
                "water"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashrif buyurmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "visit",
            "options": [
                "watch",
                "fall",
                "stand"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "markaz",
            "RightAnswer": "center",
            "options": [
                "test",
                "power",
                "base"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'smoq",
            "RightAnswer": "grow",
            "options": [
                "suggest",
                "allow",
                "send"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hech narsa",
            "RightAnswer": "nothing",
            "options": [
                "anything",
                "something",
                "who"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qaytmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "return",
            "options": [
                "visit",
                "watch",
                "fall"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ona",
            "RightAnswer": "mother",
            "options": [
                "story",
                "product",
                "party"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yurmoq, sayir",
            "RightAnswer": "walk",
            "options": [
                "return",
                "visit",
                "watch"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "masala, muhim",
            "RightAnswer": "matter",
            "options": [
                "center",
                "test",
                "power"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aql, fikr",
            "RightAnswer": "mind",
            "options": [
                "matter",
                "center",
                "test"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiymat",
            "RightAnswer": "value",
            "options": [
                "mind",
                "matter",
                "center"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ofis",
            "RightAnswer": "office",
            "options": [
                "mother",
                "story",
                "product"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yozuv, rekord",
            "RightAnswer": "record",
            "options": [
                "value",
                "mind",
                "matter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qolmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "stay",
            "options": [
                "walk",
                "return",
                "visit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kuch",
            "RightAnswer": "force",
            "options": [
                "record",
                "value",
                "mind"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'xtamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "stop",
            "options": [
                "stay",
                "walk",
                "return"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bir necha",
            "RightAnswer": "several",
            "options": [
                "few",
                "every",
                "that"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yorug', yengil",
            "RightAnswer": "light",
            "options": [
                "past",
                "east",
                "plenty"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rivojlantirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "develop",
            "options": [
                "grow",
                "suggest",
                "allow"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 8": [
        {
            "Question": "eslamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "remember",
            "options": [
                "develop",
                "grow",
                "suggest"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oz, bo'lak",
            "RightAnswer": "bit",
            "options": [
                "office",
                "mother",
                "story"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bo'lishmoq, ulashmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "share",
            "options": [
                "stop",
                "stay",
                "walk"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haqiqiy",
            "RightAnswer": "real",
            "options": [
                "local",
                "possible",
                "sure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "javob",
            "RightAnswer": "answer",
            "options": [
                "force",
                "record",
                "value"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'tirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "sit",
            "options": [
                "remember",
                "develop",
                "grow"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "raqam",
            "RightAnswer": "figure",
            "options": [
                "answer",
                "force",
                "record"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maktub, harf",
            "RightAnswer": "letter",
            "options": [
                "bit",
                "office",
                "mother"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qaror qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "decide",
            "options": [
                "sit",
                "remember",
                "develop"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "til",
            "RightAnswer": "language",
            "options": [
                "letter",
                "bit",
                "office"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mavzu, fan",
            "RightAnswer": "subject",
            "options": [
                "blog",
                "rose",
                "slice"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sinf",
            "RightAnswer": "class",
            "options": [
                "level",
                "kind",
                "criteria"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rivojlanish",
            "RightAnswer": "development",
            "options": [
                "language",
                "letter",
                "bit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shahar",
            "RightAnswer": "town",
            "options": [
                "development",
                "language",
                "letter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yarim",
            "RightAnswer": "half",
            "options": [
                "class",
                "level",
                "kind"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "daqiqa",
            "RightAnswer": "minute",
            "options": [
                "town",
                "development",
                "language"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oziq-ovqat",
            "RightAnswer": "food",
            "options": [
                "minute",
                "town",
                "development"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanaffus, sindirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "break",
            "options": [
                "share",
                "stop",
                "stay"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aniq, tozalamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "clear",
            "options": [
                "open",
                "own",
                "latter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kelajak",
            "RightAnswer": "future",
            "options": [
                "half",
                "class",
                "level"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yoki, har ikkisi",
            "RightAnswer": "either",
            "options": [
                "least",
                "enough",
                "much"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oldin",
            "RightAnswer": "ago",
            "options": [
                "probably",
                "soon",
                "ever"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "har",
            "RightAnswer": "per",
            "options": [
                "within",
                "against",
                "without"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qolmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "remain",
            "options": [
                "decide",
                "sit",
                "remember"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tepa, eng yuqori",
            "RightAnswer": "top",
            "options": [
                "future",
                "half",
                "class"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "orasida",
            "RightAnswer": "among",
            "options": [
                "per",
                "within",
                "against"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yutmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "win",
            "options": [
                "break",
                "share",
                "stop"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rang",
            "RightAnswer": "color",
            "options": [
                "figure",
                "answer",
                "force"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jalb qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "involve",
            "options": [
                "remain",
                "decide",
                "sit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yetmoq, erishmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "reach",
            "options": [
                "win",
                "break",
                "share"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ijtimoiy",
            "RightAnswer": "social",
            "options": [
                "real",
                "local",
                "possible"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "davr, muddat",
            "RightAnswer": "period",
            "options": [
                "food",
                "minute",
                "town"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bo'ylab",
            "RightAnswer": "across",
            "options": [
                "around",
                "off",
                "through"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "eslatma, qayd",
            "RightAnswer": "note",
            "options": [
                "color",
                "figure",
                "answer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tarix",
            "RightAnswer": "history",
            "options": [
                "period",
                "food",
                "minute"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaratmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "create",
            "options": [
                "involve",
                "remain",
                "decide"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haydamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "drive",
            "options": [
                "reach",
                "win",
                "break"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bo'ylab",
            "RightAnswer": "along",
            "options": [
                "across",
                "around",
                "off"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tur, tip",
            "RightAnswer": "type",
            "options": [
                "note",
                "color",
                "figure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tovush",
            "RightAnswer": "sound",
            "options": [
                "type",
                "note",
                "color"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'z",
            "RightAnswer": "eye",
            "options": [
                "sound",
                "type",
                "note"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "musiqa",
            "RightAnswer": "music",
            "options": [
                "history",
                "period",
                "food"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'yin",
            "RightAnswer": "game",
            "options": [
                "music",
                "history",
                "period"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "siyosiy",
            "RightAnswer": "political",
            "options": [
                "social",
                "real",
                "local"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bepul, ozod",
            "RightAnswer": "free",
            "options": [
                "rough",
                "soft",
                "fair"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "receive",
            "options": [
                "create",
                "involve",
                "remain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "lahza",
            "RightAnswer": "moment",
            "options": [
                "game",
                "music",
                "history"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "savdo, sotuv",
            "RightAnswer": "sale",
            "options": [
                "moment",
                "game",
                "music"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "siyosat",
            "RightAnswer": "policy",
            "options": [
                "sale",
                "moment",
                "game"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'shimcha",
            "RightAnswer": "further",
            "options": [
                "free",
                "rough",
                "soft"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 9": [
        {
            "Question": "tana",
            "RightAnswer": "body",
            "options": [
                "policy",
                "sale",
                "moment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "talab qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "require",
            "options": [
                "receive",
                "create",
                "involve"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kutmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "wait",
            "options": [
                "drive",
                "reach",
                "win"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "umumiy",
            "RightAnswer": "general",
            "options": [
                "whole",
                "public",
                "tight"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'rinmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "appear",
            "options": [
                "require",
                "receive",
                "create"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tomon",
            "RightAnswer": "toward",
            "options": [
                "among",
                "per",
                "within"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jamoa",
            "RightAnswer": "team",
            "options": [
                "body",
                "policy",
                "sale"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oson",
            "RightAnswer": "easy",
            "options": [
                "political",
                "social",
                "real"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shaxsiy, individ",
            "RightAnswer": "individual",
            "options": [
                "top",
                "future",
                "half"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'la",
            "RightAnswer": "full",
            "options": [
                "easy",
                "political",
                "social"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qora",
            "RightAnswer": "black",
            "options": [
                "general",
                "whole",
                "public"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ma'no, sezgi",
            "RightAnswer": "sense",
            "options": [
                "eye",
                "sound",
                "type"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ehtimol",
            "RightAnswer": "perhaps",
            "options": [
                "ago",
                "probably",
                "soon"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'shmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "add",
            "options": [
                "appear",
                "require",
                "receive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qoida",
            "RightAnswer": "rule",
            "options": [
                "sense",
                "eye",
                "sound"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'tmoq, o'tish joyi",
            "RightAnswer": "pass",
            "options": [
                "wait",
                "drive",
                "reach"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishlab chiqarish",
            "RightAnswer": "produce",
            "options": [
                "add",
                "appear",
                "require"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sotmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "sell",
            "options": [
                "produce",
                "add",
                "appear"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qisqa",
            "RightAnswer": "short",
            "options": [
                "hard",
                "low",
                "early"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rozi bo'lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "agree",
            "options": [
                "sell",
                "produce",
                "add"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qonun",
            "RightAnswer": "law",
            "options": [
                "team",
                "body",
                "policy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hamma narsa",
            "RightAnswer": "everything",
            "options": [
                "nothing",
                "anything",
                "something"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tadqiqot",
            "RightAnswer": "research",
            "options": [
                "rule",
                "sense",
                "eye"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qoplamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "cover",
            "options": [
                "pass",
                "wait",
                "drive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qog'oz, hujjat",
            "RightAnswer": "paper",
            "options": [
                "research",
                "rule",
                "sense"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "pozitsiya, lavozim",
            "RightAnswer": "position",
            "options": [
                "paper",
                "research",
                "rule"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaqin",
            "RightAnswer": "near",
            "options": [
                "unlike",
                "via",
                "onto"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "insoniy",
            "RightAnswer": "human",
            "options": [
                "individual",
                "top",
                "future"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kompyuter",
            "RightAnswer": "computer",
            "options": [
                "law",
                "team",
                "body"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vaziyat",
            "RightAnswer": "situation",
            "options": [
                "computer",
                "law",
                "team"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xodimlar",
            "RightAnswer": "staff",
            "options": [
                "situation",
                "computer",
                "law"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "faoliyat",
            "RightAnswer": "activity",
            "options": [
                "staff",
                "situation",
                "computer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "film",
            "RightAnswer": "film",
            "options": [
                "position",
                "paper",
                "research"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ertalab",
            "RightAnswer": "morning",
            "options": [
                "activity",
                "staff",
                "situation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "urush",
            "RightAnswer": "war",
            "options": [
                "morning",
                "activity",
                "staff"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hisob",
            "RightAnswer": "account",
            "options": [
                "film",
                "position",
                "paper"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "do'kon",
            "RightAnswer": "shop",
            "options": [
                "account",
                "film",
                "position"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asosiy",
            "RightAnswer": "major",
            "options": [
                "black",
                "general",
                "whole"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kimdir",
            "RightAnswer": "someone",
            "options": [
                "everything",
                "nothing",
                "anything"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yuqorida",
            "RightAnswer": "above",
            "options": [
                "along",
                "across",
                "around"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dizayn, loyihalamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "design",
            "options": [
                "shop",
                "account",
                "film"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "voqea",
            "RightAnswer": "event",
            "options": [
                "war",
                "morning",
                "activity"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maxsus",
            "RightAnswer": "special",
            "options": [
                "full",
                "easy",
                "political"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ba'zida",
            "RightAnswer": "sometimes",
            "options": [
                "perhaps",
                "ago",
                "probably"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "holat, shart",
            "RightAnswer": "condition",
            "options": [
                "event",
                "war",
                "morning"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "olib yurmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "carry",
            "options": [
                "agree",
                "sell",
                "produce"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "choose",
            "options": [
                "carry",
                "agree",
                "sell"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ota",
            "RightAnswer": "father",
            "options": [
                "condition",
                "event",
                "war"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qaror",
            "RightAnswer": "decision",
            "options": [
                "father",
                "condition",
                "event"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "stol",
            "RightAnswer": "table",
            "options": [
                "decision",
                "father",
                "condition"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 10": [
        {
            "Question": "aniq, ba'zi",
            "RightAnswer": "certain",
            "options": [
                "special",
                "full",
                "easy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oldinga",
            "RightAnswer": "forward",
            "options": [
                "far",
                "still",
                "only"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asosiy",
            "RightAnswer": "main",
            "options": [
                "certain",
                "special",
                "full"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vafot etmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "die",
            "options": [
                "choose",
                "carry",
                "agree"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ayiq",
            "RightAnswer": "bear",
            "options": [
                "cover",
                "pass",
                "wait"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kesmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "cut",
            "options": [
                "bear",
                "cover",
                "pass"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tasvirlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "describe",
            "options": [
                "die",
                "choose",
                "carry"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'zi",
            "RightAnswer": "himself",
            "options": [
                "someone",
                "everything",
                "nothing"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mavjud",
            "RightAnswer": "available",
            "options": [
                "main",
                "certain",
                "special"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ayniqsa",
            "RightAnswer": "especially",
            "options": [
                "sometimes",
                "perhaps",
                "ago"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kuchli",
            "RightAnswer": "strong",
            "options": [
                "available",
                "main",
                "certain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'tarilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "rise",
            "options": [
                "cut",
                "bear",
                "cover"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiz",
            "RightAnswer": "girl",
            "options": [
                "table",
                "decision",
                "father"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "balki",
            "RightAnswer": "maybe",
            "options": [
                "especially",
                "sometimes",
                "perhaps"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hamjamiyat",
            "RightAnswer": "community",
            "options": [
                "girl",
                "table",
                "decision"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshqa",
            "RightAnswer": "else",
            "options": [
                "maybe",
                "especially",
                "sometimes"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ma'lum, alohida",
            "RightAnswer": "particular",
            "options": [
                "strong",
                "available",
                "main"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rol",
            "RightAnswer": "role",
            "options": [
                "community",
                "girl",
                "table"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'shilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "join",
            "options": [
                "describe",
                "die",
                "choose"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiyin",
            "RightAnswer": "difficult",
            "options": [
                "particular",
                "strong",
                "available"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "iltimos, mamnun qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "please",
            "options": [
                "join",
                "describe",
                "die"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "detal, tafsilot",
            "RightAnswer": "detail",
            "options": [
                "design",
                "shop",
                "account"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "farq",
            "RightAnswer": "difference",
            "options": [
                "role",
                "community",
                "girl"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "harakat",
            "RightAnswer": "action",
            "options": [
                "difference",
                "role",
                "community"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sog'liq",
            "RightAnswer": "health",
            "options": [
                "action",
                "difference",
                "role"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yemoq",
            "RightAnswer": "eat",
            "options": [
                "please",
                "join",
                "describe"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qadam",
            "RightAnswer": "step",
            "options": [
                "detail",
                "design",
                "shop"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rost",
            "RightAnswer": "true",
            "options": [
                "difficult",
                "particular",
                "strong"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "telefon",
            "RightAnswer": "phone",
            "options": [
                "step",
                "detail",
                "design"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'zlarini",
            "RightAnswer": "themselves",
            "options": [
                "himself",
                "someone",
                "everything"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chizmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "draw",
            "options": [
                "eat",
                "please",
                "join"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oq",
            "RightAnswer": "white",
            "options": [
                "major",
                "black",
                "general"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sana, uchrashuv",
            "RightAnswer": "date",
            "options": [
                "phone",
                "step",
                "detail"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mashq, amaliyot",
            "RightAnswer": "practice",
            "options": [
                "date",
                "phone",
                "step"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "model",
            "RightAnswer": "model",
            "options": [
                "practice",
                "date",
                "phone"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'tarish",
            "RightAnswer": "raise",
            "options": [
                "rise",
                "cut",
                "bear"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mijoz",
            "RightAnswer": "customer",
            "options": [
                "health",
                "action",
                "difference"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "old qism",
            "RightAnswer": "front",
            "options": [
                "human",
                "individual",
                "top"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tushuntirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "explain",
            "options": [
                "draw",
                "eat",
                "please"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "eshik",
            "RightAnswer": "door",
            "options": [
                "customer",
                "health",
                "action"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashqarida",
            "RightAnswer": "outside",
            "options": [
                "tonight",
                "tomorrow",
                "yesterday"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "orqa",
            "RightAnswer": "behind",
            "options": [
                "above",
                "along",
                "across"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "iqtisodiy",
            "RightAnswer": "economic",
            "options": [
                "true",
                "difficult",
                "particular"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sayt, joy",
            "RightAnswer": "site",
            "options": [
                "door",
                "customer",
                "health"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yondashmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "approach",
            "options": [
                "raise",
                "rise",
                "cut"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'qituvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "teacher",
            "options": [
                "site",
                "door",
                "customer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yer, qishloq",
            "RightAnswer": "land",
            "options": [
                "model",
                "practice",
                "date"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zaryad, jarima",
            "RightAnswer": "charge",
            "options": [
                "land",
                "model",
                "practice"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nihoyat",
            "RightAnswer": "finally",
            "options": [
                "else",
                "maybe",
                "especially"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "belgi, imzolamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "sign",
            "options": [
                "charge",
                "land",
                "model"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 11": [
        {
            "Question": "da'vo qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "claim",
            "options": [
                "sign",
                "charge",
                "land"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "munosabat",
            "RightAnswer": "relationship",
            "options": [
                "teacher",
                "site",
                "door"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sayohat",
            "RightAnswer": "travel",
            "options": [
                "claim",
                "sign",
                "charge"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rohatlanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "enjoy",
            "options": [
                "explain",
                "draw",
                "eat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'lim",
            "RightAnswer": "death",
            "options": [
                "relationship",
                "teacher",
                "site"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yoqimli",
            "RightAnswer": "nice",
            "options": [
                "economic",
                "true",
                "difficult"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "miqdor",
            "RightAnswer": "amount",
            "options": [
                "travel",
                "claim",
                "sign"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaxshilamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "improve",
            "options": [
                "enjoy",
                "explain",
                "draw"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rasm",
            "RightAnswer": "picture",
            "options": [
                "amount",
                "travel",
                "claim"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bola, o'g'il",
            "RightAnswer": "boy",
            "options": [
                "death",
                "relationship",
                "teacher"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hurmat, e'tibor",
            "RightAnswer": "regard",
            "options": [
                "picture",
                "amount",
                "travel"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashkilot",
            "RightAnswer": "organization",
            "options": [
                "boy",
                "death",
                "relationship"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "baxtli",
            "RightAnswer": "happy",
            "options": [
                "nice",
                "economic",
                "true"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "juft",
            "RightAnswer": "couple",
            "options": [
                "regard",
                "picture",
                "amount"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "harakat",
            "RightAnswer": "act",
            "options": [
                "couple",
                "regard",
                "picture"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "diapazon",
            "RightAnswer": "range",
            "options": [
                "act",
                "couple",
                "regard"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sifat",
            "RightAnswer": "quality",
            "options": [
                "organization",
                "boy",
                "death"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "loyiha",
            "RightAnswer": "project",
            "options": [
                "range",
                "act",
                "couple"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "doira, atrof",
            "RightAnswer": "round",
            "options": [
                "abstract",
                "concrete",
                "parallel"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "imkoniyat",
            "RightAnswer": "opportunity",
            "options": [
                "quality",
                "organization",
                "boy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yo'l",
            "RightAnswer": "road",
            "options": [
                "opportunity",
                "quality",
                "organization"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kelishuv",
            "RightAnswer": "accord",
            "options": [
                "project",
                "range",
                "act"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ro'yxat",
            "RightAnswer": "list",
            "options": [
                "accord",
                "project",
                "range"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tilamoq, orzu",
            "RightAnswer": "wish",
            "options": [
                "list",
                "accord",
                "project"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shuning uchun",
            "RightAnswer": "therefore",
            "options": [
                "though",
                "whereas",
                "unless"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kiymoq",
            "RightAnswer": "wear",
            "options": [
                "approach",
                "raise",
                "rise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mablag'",
            "RightAnswer": "fund",
            "options": [
                "wish",
                "list",
                "accord"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dam olmoq, qolgan",
            "RightAnswer": "rest",
            "options": [
                "fund",
                "wish",
                "list"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bola ",
            "RightAnswer": "kid",
            "options": [
                "rest",
                "fund",
                "wish"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sanoat",
            "RightAnswer": "industry",
            "options": [
                "road",
                "opportunity",
                "quality"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta'lim",
            "RightAnswer": "education",
            "options": [
                "industry",
                "road",
                "opportunity"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'lchov, o'lchamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "measure",
            "options": [
                "kid",
                "rest",
                "fund"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'ldirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "kill",
            "options": [
                "improve",
                "enjoy",
                "explain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xizmat qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "serve",
            "options": [
                "kill",
                "improve",
                "enjoy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ehtimol",
            "RightAnswer": "likely",
            "options": [
                "short",
                "hard",
                "low"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "albatta",
            "RightAnswer": "certainly",
            "options": [
                "finally",
                "else",
                "maybe"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "milliy",
            "RightAnswer": "national",
            "options": [
                "happy",
                "nice",
                "economic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'zi",
            "RightAnswer": "itself",
            "options": [
                "themselves",
                "himself",
                "someone"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'rgatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "teach",
            "options": [
                "serve",
                "kill",
                "improve"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "soha, dala",
            "RightAnswer": "field",
            "options": [
                "measure",
                "kid",
                "rest"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xavfsizlik",
            "RightAnswer": "security",
            "options": [
                "education",
                "industry",
                "road"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "havo",
            "RightAnswer": "air",
            "options": [
                "field",
                "measure",
                "kid"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "foyda",
            "RightAnswer": "benefit",
            "options": [
                "air",
                "field",
                "measure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "savdo",
            "RightAnswer": "trade",
            "options": [
                "benefit",
                "air",
                "field"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xavf",
            "RightAnswer": "risk",
            "options": [
                "trade",
                "benefit",
                "air"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yangilik",
            "RightAnswer": "news",
            "options": [
                "security",
                "education",
                "industry"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "standart",
            "RightAnswer": "standard",
            "options": [
                "front",
                "human",
                "individual"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ovoz bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "vote",
            "options": [
                "risk",
                "trade",
                "benefit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "foiz",
            "RightAnswer": "percent",
            "options": [
                "news",
                "security",
                "education"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "diqqat markazi",
            "RightAnswer": "focus",
            "options": [
                "vote",
                "risk",
                "trade"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 12": [
        {
            "Question": "bosqich",
            "RightAnswer": "stage",
            "options": [
                "focus",
                "vote",
                "risk"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "fazo",
            "RightAnswer": "space",
            "options": [
                "subject",
                "blog",
                "rose"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'rniga",
            "RightAnswer": "instead",
            "options": [
                "down",
                "out",
                "up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "anglamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "realize",
            "options": [
                "teach",
                "serve",
                "kill"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "odatda",
            "RightAnswer": "usually",
            "options": [
                "certainly",
                "finally",
                "else"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ma'lumot",
            "RightAnswer": "data",
            "options": [
                "percent",
                "news",
                "security"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yakka, yolg'iz",
            "RightAnswer": "single",
            "options": [
                "white",
                "major",
                "black"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "manzil",
            "RightAnswer": "address",
            "options": [
                "stage",
                "focus",
                "vote"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ijro",
            "RightAnswer": "performance",
            "options": [
                "data",
                "percent",
                "news"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "imkoniyat",
            "RightAnswer": "chance",
            "options": [
                "address",
                "stage",
                "focus"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qabul qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "accept",
            "options": [
                "realize",
                "teach",
                "serve"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jamiyat",
            "RightAnswer": "society",
            "options": [
                "performance",
                "data",
                "percent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "texnologiya",
            "RightAnswer": "technology",
            "options": [
                "society",
                "performance",
                "data"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tilga olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "mention",
            "options": [
                "chance",
                "address",
                "stage"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanlov",
            "RightAnswer": "choice",
            "options": [
                "technology",
                "society",
                "performance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "saqlamoq, tejamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "save",
            "options": [
                "wear",
                "approach",
                "raise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "umumiy, keng tarqalgan",
            "RightAnswer": "common",
            "options": [
                "single",
                "white",
                "major"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "madaniyat",
            "RightAnswer": "culture",
            "options": [
                "choice",
                "technology",
                "society"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "umumiy",
            "RightAnswer": "total",
            "options": [
                "common",
                "single",
                "white"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "talab",
            "RightAnswer": "demand",
            "options": [
                "mention",
                "chance",
                "address"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "material, ashyo",
            "RightAnswer": "material",
            "options": [
                "standard",
                "front",
                "human"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chegaralamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "limit",
            "options": [
                "demand",
                "mention",
                "chance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tinglamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "listen",
            "options": [
                "accept",
                "realize",
                "teach"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kerak, sabab",
            "RightAnswer": "due",
            "options": [
                "total",
                "common",
                "single"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "noto'g'ri",
            "RightAnswer": "wrong",
            "options": [
                "right",
                "alright",
                "okay"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oyoq",
            "RightAnswer": "foot",
            "options": [
                "culture",
                "choice",
                "technology"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sa'y-harakat",
            "RightAnswer": "effort",
            "options": [
                "foot",
                "culture",
                "choice"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "e'tibor",
            "RightAnswer": "attention",
            "options": [
                "effort",
                "foot",
                "culture"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ustida",
            "RightAnswer": "upon",
            "options": [
                "toward",
                "among",
                "per"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tekshirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "check",
            "options": [
                "limit",
                "demand",
                "mention"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'liq, yakunlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "complete",
            "options": [
                "clear",
                "open",
                "own"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yolg'on, yotmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "lie",
            "options": [
                "save",
                "wear",
                "approach"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "pick",
            "options": [
                "lie",
                "save",
                "wear"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kamaytirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "reduce",
            "options": [
                "listen",
                "accept",
                "realize"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shaxsiy",
            "RightAnswer": "personal",
            "options": [
                "national",
                "happy",
                "nice"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yer, asos",
            "RightAnswer": "ground",
            "options": [
                "check",
                "limit",
                "demand"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hayvon",
            "RightAnswer": "animal",
            "options": [
                "attention",
                "effort",
                "foot"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yetib kelmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "arrive",
            "options": [
                "reduce",
                "listen",
                "accept"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bemor, sabrli",
            "RightAnswer": "patient",
            "options": [
                "material",
                "standard",
                "front"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "joriy",
            "RightAnswer": "current",
            "options": [
                "due",
                "total",
                "common"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asr",
            "RightAnswer": "century",
            "options": [
                "animal",
                "attention",
                "effort"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dalil",
            "RightAnswer": "evidence",
            "options": [
                "century",
                "animal",
                "attention"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mavjud bo'lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "exist",
            "options": [
                "arrive",
                "reduce",
                "listen"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'xshash",
            "RightAnswer": "similar",
            "options": [
                "personal",
                "national",
                "happy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jang qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "fight",
            "options": [
                "ground",
                "check",
                "limit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yetakchi",
            "RightAnswer": "leader",
            "options": [
                "evidence",
                "century",
                "animal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaxshi, jarima",
            "RightAnswer": "fine",
            "options": [
                "present",
                "tall",
                "opposite"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'cha",
            "RightAnswer": "street",
            "options": [
                "leader",
                "evidence",
                "century"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sobiq",
            "RightAnswer": "former",
            "options": [
                "similar",
                "personal",
                "national"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aloqa",
            "RightAnswer": "contact",
            "options": [
                "fight",
                "ground",
                "check"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 13": [
        {
            "Question": "ayniqsa",
            "RightAnswer": "particularly",
            "options": [
                "usually",
                "certainly",
                "finally"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xotin",
            "RightAnswer": "wife",
            "options": [
                "street",
                "leader",
                "evidence"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sport",
            "RightAnswer": "sport",
            "options": [
                "contact",
                "fight",
                "ground"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tayyorlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "prepare",
            "options": [
                "exist",
                "arrive",
                "reduce"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muhokama qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "discuss",
            "options": [
                "prepare",
                "exist",
                "arrive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "javob",
            "RightAnswer": "response",
            "options": [
                "wife",
                "street",
                "leader"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ovoz",
            "RightAnswer": "voice",
            "options": [
                "sport",
                "contact",
                "fight"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "parcha",
            "RightAnswer": "piece",
            "options": [
                "response",
                "wife",
                "street"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tugatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "finish",
            "options": [
                "pick",
                "lie",
                "save"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taxmin qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "suppose",
            "options": [
                "discuss",
                "prepare",
                "exist"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'llamoq, ariza bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "apply",
            "options": [
                "suppose",
                "discuss",
                "prepare"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "prezident",
            "RightAnswer": "president",
            "options": [
                "piece",
                "response",
                "wife"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "olov, ishdan bo'shatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "fire",
            "options": [
                "voice",
                "sport",
                "contact"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taqqoslamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "compare",
            "options": [
                "apply",
                "suppose",
                "discuss"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sud",
            "RightAnswer": "court",
            "options": [
                "fire",
                "voice",
                "sport"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "politsiya",
            "RightAnswer": "police",
            "options": [
                "president",
                "piece",
                "response"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "do'kon, saqlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "store",
            "options": [
                "court",
                "fire",
                "voice"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kambag'al",
            "RightAnswer": "poor",
            "options": [
                "former",
                "similar",
                "personal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bilim",
            "RightAnswer": "knowledge",
            "options": [
                "police",
                "president",
                "piece"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kulmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "laugh",
            "options": [
                "store",
                "court",
                "fire"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'l, qurol",
            "RightAnswer": "arm",
            "options": [
                "laugh",
                "store",
                "court"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yurak",
            "RightAnswer": "heart",
            "options": [
                "knowledge",
                "police",
                "president"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "manba",
            "RightAnswer": "source",
            "options": [
                "heart",
                "knowledge",
                "police"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xodim",
            "RightAnswer": "employee",
            "options": [
                "source",
                "heart",
                "knowledge"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshqarmoq, uddalamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "manage",
            "options": [
                "compare",
                "apply",
                "suppose"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oddiygina",
            "RightAnswer": "simply",
            "options": [
                "particularly",
                "usually",
                "certainly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bank",
            "RightAnswer": "bank",
            "options": [
                "arm",
                "laugh",
                "store"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "firma, qattiq",
            "RightAnswer": "firm",
            "options": [
                "patient",
                "material",
                "standard"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hujayra, katak",
            "RightAnswer": "cell",
            "options": [
                "employee",
                "source",
                "heart"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maqola, band",
            "RightAnswer": "article",
            "options": [
                "cell",
                "employee",
                "source"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tez",
            "RightAnswer": "fast",
            "options": [
                "wrong",
                "right",
                "alright"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hujum qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "attack",
            "options": [
                "bank",
                "arm",
                "laugh"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xorijiy",
            "RightAnswer": "foreign",
            "options": [
                "poor",
                "former",
                "similar"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hayrat, ajablantirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "surprise",
            "options": [
                "attack",
                "bank",
                "arm"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xususiyat",
            "RightAnswer": "feature",
            "options": [
                "surprise",
                "attack",
                "bank"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "omil",
            "RightAnswer": "factor",
            "options": [
                "article",
                "cell",
                "employee"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chiroyli",
            "RightAnswer": "pretty",
            "options": [
                "likely",
                "short",
                "hard"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaqinda",
            "RightAnswer": "recently",
            "options": [
                "simply",
                "particularly",
                "usually"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta'sir qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "affect",
            "options": [
                "manage",
                "compare",
                "apply"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tushmoq, tomchi",
            "RightAnswer": "drop",
            "options": [
                "finish",
                "pick",
                "lie"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaqinda sodir boâ€˜lgan",
            "RightAnswer": "recent",
            "options": [
                "foreign",
                "poor",
                "former"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bogâ€˜lanmoq, aloqador",
            "RightAnswer": "relate",
            "options": [
                "affect",
                "manage",
                "compare"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rasmiy",
            "RightAnswer": "official",
            "options": [
                "current",
                "due",
                "total"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "moliyaviy",
            "RightAnswer": "financial",
            "options": [
                "recent",
                "foreign",
                "poor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'tkazib yubormoq",
            "RightAnswer": "miss",
            "options": [
                "drop",
                "finish",
                "pick"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sanâ€™at",
            "RightAnswer": "art",
            "options": [
                "factor",
                "article",
                "cell"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashkiliy harakat",
            "RightAnswer": "campaign",
            "options": [
                "feature",
                "surprise",
                "attack"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xususiy",
            "RightAnswer": "private",
            "options": [
                "official",
                "current",
                "due"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "toâ€˜xtatish, pauza",
            "RightAnswer": "pause",
            "options": [
                "campaign",
                "feature",
                "surprise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hamma",
            "RightAnswer": "everyone",
            "options": [
                "itself",
                "themselves",
                "himself"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 14": [
        {
            "Question": "unutmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "forget",
            "options": [
                "relate",
                "affect",
                "manage"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sahifa",
            "RightAnswer": "page",
            "options": [
                "pause",
                "campaign",
                "feature"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xavotirlanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "worry",
            "options": [
                "page",
                "pause",
                "campaign"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yoz",
            "RightAnswer": "summer",
            "options": [
                "art",
                "factor",
                "article"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ichimlik",
            "RightAnswer": "drink",
            "options": [
                "worry",
                "page",
                "pause"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "fikr",
            "RightAnswer": "opinion",
            "options": [
                "summer",
                "art",
                "factor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hiyobon, mashinani joylashtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "park",
            "options": [
                "drink",
                "worry",
                "page"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vakil boâ€˜lmoq, ifodalamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "represent",
            "options": [
                "forget",
                "relate",
                "affect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kalit, muhim",
            "RightAnswer": "key",
            "options": [
                "firm",
                "patient",
                "material"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ichida",
            "RightAnswer": "inside",
            "options": [
                "alongside",
                "regardless",
                "beneath"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "menejer",
            "RightAnswer": "manager",
            "options": [
                "opinion",
                "summer",
                "art"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xalqaro",
            "RightAnswer": "international",
            "options": [
                "financial",
                "recent",
                "foreign"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oâ€˜z ichiga olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "contain",
            "options": [
                "represent",
                "forget",
                "relate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "eâ€™tibor, bildirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "notice",
            "options": [
                "park",
                "drink",
                "worry"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hayron boâ€˜lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "wonder",
            "options": [
                "notice",
                "park",
                "drink"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tabiat",
            "RightAnswer": "nature",
            "options": [
                "manager",
                "opinion",
                "summer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tuzilma",
            "RightAnswer": "structure",
            "options": [
                "wonder",
                "notice",
                "park"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boâ€˜lim",
            "RightAnswer": "section",
            "options": [
                "nature",
                "manager",
                "opinion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oâ€˜zim",
            "RightAnswer": "myself",
            "options": [
                "everyone",
                "itself",
                "themselves"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aniq",
            "RightAnswer": "exactly",
            "options": [
                "recently",
                "simply",
                "particularly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oâ€˜simlik, zavod",
            "RightAnswer": "plant",
            "options": [
                "structure",
                "wonder",
                "notice"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boâ€˜yoq, boâ€˜yamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "paint",
            "options": [
                "plant",
                "structure",
                "wonder"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishchi",
            "RightAnswer": "worker",
            "options": [
                "section",
                "nature",
                "manager"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bosma, press",
            "RightAnswer": "press",
            "options": [
                "paint",
                "plant",
                "structure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nima bo'lsa ham",
            "RightAnswer": "whatever",
            "options": [
                "self",
                "ourselves",
                "anybody"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zarur",
            "RightAnswer": "necessary",
            "options": [
                "international",
                "financial",
                "recent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mintaqa",
            "RightAnswer": "region",
            "options": [
                "worker",
                "section",
                "nature"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oâ€˜sish",
            "RightAnswer": "growth",
            "options": [
                "region",
                "worker",
                "section"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kechki vaqt",
            "RightAnswer": "evening",
            "options": [
                "key",
                "firm",
                "patient"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta'sir",
            "RightAnswer": "influence",
            "options": [
                "press",
                "paint",
                "plant"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hurmat",
            "RightAnswer": "respect",
            "options": [
                "influence",
                "press",
                "paint"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "turli",
            "RightAnswer": "various",
            "options": [
                "necessary",
                "international",
                "financial"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ushlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "catch",
            "options": [
                "miss",
                "drop",
                "finish"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shuning uchun",
            "RightAnswer": "thus",
            "options": [
                "exactly",
                "recently",
                "simply"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "koâ€˜nikma",
            "RightAnswer": "skill",
            "options": [
                "growth",
                "region",
                "worker"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "urinish",
            "RightAnswer": "attempt",
            "options": [
                "respect",
                "influence",
                "press"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oâ€˜gâ€˜il",
            "RightAnswer": "son",
            "options": [
                "skill",
                "growth",
                "region"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oddiy",
            "RightAnswer": "simple",
            "options": [
                "various",
                "necessary",
                "international"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oâ€˜rta",
            "RightAnswer": "medium",
            "options": [
                "evening",
                "key",
                "firm"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oâ€˜rtacha",
            "RightAnswer": "average",
            "options": [
                "private",
                "official",
                "current"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ombor, aksiyalar",
            "RightAnswer": "stock",
            "options": [
                "light",
                "past",
                "east"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshqaruv",
            "RightAnswer": "management",
            "options": [
                "son",
                "skill",
                "growth"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xarakter, belgi",
            "RightAnswer": "character",
            "options": [
                "management",
                "son",
                "skill"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yotoq",
            "RightAnswer": "bed",
            "options": [
                "character",
                "management",
                "son"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "urmoq, zarba",
            "RightAnswer": "hit",
            "options": [
                "catch",
                "miss",
                "drop"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashkil qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "establish",
            "options": [
                "contain",
                "represent",
                "forget"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haqiqatan",
            "RightAnswer": "indeed",
            "options": [
                "thus",
                "exactly",
                "recently"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yakuniy",
            "RightAnswer": "final",
            "options": [
                "average",
                "private",
                "official"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "iqtisodiyot",
            "RightAnswer": "economy",
            "options": [
                "bed",
                "character",
                "management"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mos kelmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "fit",
            "options": [
                "moderate",
                "mature",
                "alter"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 15": [
        {
            "Question": "yigit",
            "RightAnswer": "guy",
            "options": [
                "economy",
                "bed",
                "character"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "funksiya, vazifa",
            "RightAnswer": "function",
            "options": [
                "attempt",
                "respect",
                "influence"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kecha",
            "RightAnswer": "yesterday",
            "options": [
                "today",
                "home",
                "bottom"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rasm, tasvir",
            "RightAnswer": "image",
            "options": [
                "function",
                "attempt",
                "respect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oâ€˜lcham",
            "RightAnswer": "size",
            "options": [
                "image",
                "function",
                "attempt"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xulq-atvor",
            "RightAnswer": "behavior",
            "options": [
                "guy",
                "economy",
                "bed"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qoâ€˜shimcha",
            "RightAnswer": "addition",
            "options": [
                "behavior",
                "guy",
                "economy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "belgilamoq, aniqlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "determine",
            "options": [
                "establish",
                "contain",
                "represent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "stansiya",
            "RightAnswer": "station",
            "options": [
                "addition",
                "behavior",
                "guy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aholi",
            "RightAnswer": "population",
            "options": [
                "station",
                "addition",
                "behavior"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uddasidan chiqmaslik",
            "RightAnswer": "fail",
            "options": [
                "hit",
                "catch",
                "miss"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muhit",
            "RightAnswer": "environment",
            "options": [
                "population",
                "station",
                "addition"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishlab chiqarish",
            "RightAnswer": "production",
            "options": [
                "environment",
                "population",
                "station"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shartnoma, qisqartmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "contract",
            "options": [
                "size",
                "image",
                "function"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oâ€˜yinchi",
            "RightAnswer": "player",
            "options": [
                "production",
                "environment",
                "population"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "izoh, fikr bildirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "comment",
            "options": [
                "contract",
                "size",
                "image"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "enter",
            "options": [
                "determine",
                "establish",
                "contain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uchrab turmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "occur",
            "options": [
                "enter",
                "determine",
                "establish"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yolgâ€˜iz",
            "RightAnswer": "alone",
            "options": [
                "pretty",
                "likely",
                "short"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muhim, ahamiyatli",
            "RightAnswer": "significant",
            "options": [
                "simple",
                "various",
                "necessary"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dori",
            "RightAnswer": "drug",
            "options": [
                "player",
                "production",
                "environment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "devor",
            "RightAnswer": "wall",
            "options": [
                "drug",
                "player",
                "production"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "seriya",
            "RightAnswer": "series",
            "options": [
                "wall",
                "drug",
                "player"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "toâ€˜gâ€˜ridan-toâ€˜gâ€˜ri, boshqarish",
            "RightAnswer": "direct",
            "options": [
                "complete",
                "clear",
                "open"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muvaffaqiyat",
            "RightAnswer": "success",
            "options": [
                "series",
                "wall",
                "drug"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ertaga",
            "RightAnswer": "tomorrow",
            "options": [
                "yesterday",
                "today",
                "home"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshliq",
            "RightAnswer": "director",
            "options": [
                "success",
                "series",
                "wall"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aniq, ravshan",
            "RightAnswer": "clearly",
            "options": [
                "indeed",
                "thus",
                "exactly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yetishmaslik",
            "RightAnswer": "lack",
            "options": [
                "comment",
                "contract",
                "size"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "koâ€˜rib chiqmoq, sharh",
            "RightAnswer": "review",
            "options": [
                "lack",
                "comment",
                "contract"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bogâ€˜liq boâ€˜lish",
            "RightAnswer": "depend",
            "options": [
                "occur",
                "enter",
                "determine"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "irq, poyga",
            "RightAnswer": "race",
            "options": [
                "review",
                "lack",
                "comment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanimoq",
            "RightAnswer": "recognize",
            "options": [
                "depend",
                "occur",
                "enter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "deraza",
            "RightAnswer": "window",
            "options": [
                "director",
                "success",
                "series"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maqsad",
            "RightAnswer": "purpose",
            "options": [
                "window",
                "director",
                "success"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boâ€˜lim",
            "RightAnswer": "department",
            "options": [
                "purpose",
                "window",
                "director"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "erishmoq, foyda olish",
            "RightAnswer": "gain",
            "options": [
                "race",
                "review",
                "lack"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "daraxt",
            "RightAnswer": "tree",
            "options": [
                "department",
                "purpose",
                "window"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kollej",
            "RightAnswer": "college",
            "options": [
                "tree",
                "department",
                "purpose"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bahslashmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "argue",
            "options": [
                "recognize",
                "depend",
                "occur"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taxta",
            "RightAnswer": "board",
            "options": [
                "gain",
                "race",
                "review"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta'til",
            "RightAnswer": "holiday",
            "options": [
                "college",
                "tree",
                "department"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "belgi",
            "RightAnswer": "mark",
            "options": [
                "board",
                "gain",
                "race"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "cherkov",
            "RightAnswer": "church",
            "options": [
                "holiday",
                "college",
                "tree"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qurilma",
            "RightAnswer": "machine",
            "options": [
                "church",
                "holiday",
                "college"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "erishmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "achieve",
            "options": [
                "argue",
                "recognize",
                "depend"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "buyum, narsalar",
            "RightAnswer": "item",
            "options": [
                "machine",
                "church",
                "holiday"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "isbotlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "prove",
            "options": [
                "achieve",
                "argue",
                "recognize"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sent",
            "RightAnswer": "cent",
            "options": [
                "item",
                "machine",
                "church"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "fasl",
            "RightAnswer": "season",
            "options": [
                "cent",
                "item",
                "machine"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 16": [
        {
            "Question": "pol, qavat",
            "RightAnswer": "floor",
            "options": [
                "mark",
                "board",
                "gain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "narsalar",
            "RightAnswer": "stuff",
            "options": [
                "floor",
                "mark",
                "board"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "keng",
            "RightAnswer": "wide",
            "options": [
                "alone",
                "pretty",
                "likely"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "har kim",
            "RightAnswer": "anyone",
            "options": [
                "myself",
                "everyone",
                "itself"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "usul",
            "RightAnswer": "method",
            "options": [
                "season",
                "cent",
                "item"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tahlil",
            "RightAnswer": "analysis",
            "options": [
                "method",
                "season",
                "cent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "saylov",
            "RightAnswer": "election",
            "options": [
                "analysis",
                "method",
                "season"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "harbiy",
            "RightAnswer": "military",
            "options": [
                "final",
                "average",
                "private"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mehmonxona",
            "RightAnswer": "hotel",
            "options": [
                "election",
                "analysis",
                "method"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "klub",
            "RightAnswer": "club",
            "options": [
                "stuff",
                "floor",
                "mark"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "pastda",
            "RightAnswer": "below",
            "options": [
                "behind",
                "above",
                "along"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "film",
            "RightAnswer": "movie",
            "options": [
                "hotel",
                "election",
                "analysis"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shifokor",
            "RightAnswer": "doctor",
            "options": [
                "club",
                "stuff",
                "floor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muhokama",
            "RightAnswer": "discussion",
            "options": [
                "movie",
                "hotel",
                "election"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uzr",
            "RightAnswer": "sorry",
            "options": [
                "significant",
                "simple",
                "various"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chaqiriq, qiyinchilik",
            "RightAnswer": "challenge",
            "options": [
                "doctor",
                "club",
                "stuff"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "millat",
            "RightAnswer": "nation",
            "options": [
                "discussion",
                "movie",
                "hotel"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "deyarli",
            "RightAnswer": "nearly",
            "options": [
                "clearly",
                "indeed",
                "thus"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bayonot",
            "RightAnswer": "statement",
            "options": [
                "nation",
                "discussion",
                "movie"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bogâ€˜lanish, havola",
            "RightAnswer": "link",
            "options": [
                "challenge",
                "doctor",
                "club"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qaramasdan",
            "RightAnswer": "despite",
            "options": [
                "upon",
                "toward",
                "among"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanishtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "introduce",
            "options": [
                "prove",
                "achieve",
                "argue"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "afzallik",
            "RightAnswer": "advantage",
            "options": [
                "statement",
                "nation",
                "discussion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tayyor",
            "RightAnswer": "ready",
            "options": [
                "wide",
                "alone",
                "pretty"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "turmush qurmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "marry",
            "options": [
                "introduce",
                "prove",
                "achieve"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zarba",
            "RightAnswer": "strike",
            "options": [
                "fail",
                "hit",
                "catch"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mil",
            "RightAnswer": "mile",
            "options": [
                "advantage",
                "statement",
                "nation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "izlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "seek",
            "options": [
                "marry",
                "introduce",
                "prove"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qobiliyat",
            "RightAnswer": "ability",
            "options": [
                "mile",
                "advantage",
                "statement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "birlik",
            "RightAnswer": "unit",
            "options": [
                "ability",
                "mile",
                "advantage"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "karta",
            "RightAnswer": "card",
            "options": [
                "unit",
                "ability",
                "mile"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shifoxona",
            "RightAnswer": "hospital",
            "options": [
                "card",
                "unit",
                "ability"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tezda",
            "RightAnswer": "quickly",
            "options": [
                "nearly",
                "clearly",
                "indeed"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "suhbat",
            "RightAnswer": "interview",
            "options": [
                "link",
                "challenge",
                "doctor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kelishuv",
            "RightAnswer": "agreement",
            "options": [
                "hospital",
                "card",
                "unit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ozod qilmoq, chiqarish",
            "RightAnswer": "release",
            "options": [
                "interview",
                "link",
                "challenge"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "soliq",
            "RightAnswer": "tax",
            "options": [
                "release",
                "interview",
                "link"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yechim",
            "RightAnswer": "solution",
            "options": [
                "agreement",
                "hospital",
                "card"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "poytaxt",
            "RightAnswer": "capital",
            "options": [
                "medium",
                "evening",
                "key"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mashhur",
            "RightAnswer": "popular",
            "options": [
                "sorry",
                "significant",
                "simple"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aniq, maxsus",
            "RightAnswer": "specific",
            "options": [
                "popular",
                "sorry",
                "significant"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chiroyli",
            "RightAnswer": "beautiful",
            "options": [
                "specific",
                "popular",
                "sorry"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qoâ€˜rquv",
            "RightAnswer": "fear",
            "options": [
                "tax",
                "release",
                "interview"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maqsad",
            "RightAnswer": "aim",
            "options": [
                "fear",
                "tax",
                "release"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "televizor",
            "RightAnswer": "television",
            "options": [
                "solution",
                "agreement",
                "hospital"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jiddiy",
            "RightAnswer": "serious",
            "options": [
                "beautiful",
                "specific",
                "popular"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maqsad",
            "RightAnswer": "target",
            "options": [
                "aim",
                "fear",
                "tax"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "daraja",
            "RightAnswer": "degree",
            "options": [
                "television",
                "solution",
                "agreement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tortmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "pull",
            "options": [
                "strike",
                "fail",
                "hit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qizil",
            "RightAnswer": "red",
            "options": [
                "military",
                "final",
                "average"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 17": [
        {
            "Question": "er",
            "RightAnswer": "husband",
            "options": [
                "degree",
                "television",
                "solution"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kirish imkoniyati",
            "RightAnswer": "access",
            "options": [
                "target",
                "aim",
                "fear"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "harakat",
            "RightAnswer": "movement",
            "options": [
                "husband",
                "degree",
                "television"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "davolamoq, munosabatda bo'lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "treat",
            "options": [
                "pull",
                "strike",
                "fail"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aniqlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "identify",
            "options": [
                "seek",
                "marry",
                "introduce"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yoâ€˜qotish",
            "RightAnswer": "loss",
            "options": [
                "movement",
                "husband",
                "degree"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zamonaviy",
            "RightAnswer": "modern",
            "options": [
                "serious",
                "beautiful",
                "specific"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bosim",
            "RightAnswer": "pressure",
            "options": [
                "access",
                "target",
                "aim"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "avtobus",
            "RightAnswer": "bus",
            "options": [
                "loss",
                "movement",
                "husband"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "davolash",
            "RightAnswer": "treatment",
            "options": [
                "bus",
                "loss",
                "movement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "konferensiya",
            "RightAnswer": "conference",
            "options": [
                "treatment",
                "bus",
                "loss"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oâ€˜zingiz",
            "RightAnswer": "yourself",
            "options": [
                "anyone",
                "myself",
                "everyone"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta'minlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "supply",
            "options": [
                "pressure",
                "access",
                "target"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qishloq",
            "RightAnswer": "village",
            "options": [
                "conference",
                "treatment",
                "bus"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiymatli",
            "RightAnswer": "worth",
            "options": [
                "red",
                "military",
                "final"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tabiiy",
            "RightAnswer": "natural",
            "options": [
                "modern",
                "serious",
                "beautiful"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ifodalamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "express",
            "options": [
                "close",
                "mean",
                "insure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "koâ€˜rsatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "indicate",
            "options": [
                "identify",
                "seek",
                "marry"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qatnashmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "attend",
            "options": [
                "indicate",
                "identify",
                "seek"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aka, uka",
            "RightAnswer": "brother",
            "options": [
                "village",
                "conference",
                "treatment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "investitsiya",
            "RightAnswer": "investment",
            "options": [
                "brother",
                "village",
                "conference"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ball, natija",
            "RightAnswer": "score",
            "options": [
                "supply",
                "pressure",
                "access"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashkil qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "organize",
            "options": [
                "attend",
                "indicate",
                "identify"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "safar, sayohat",
            "RightAnswer": "trip",
            "options": [
                "score",
                "supply",
                "pressure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ortda, tashqarida",
            "RightAnswer": "beyond",
            "options": [
                "below",
                "behind",
                "above"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uxlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "sleep",
            "options": [
                "trip",
                "score",
                "supply"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "baliq",
            "RightAnswer": "fish",
            "options": [
                "sleep",
                "trip",
                "score"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "va'da",
            "RightAnswer": "promise",
            "options": [
                "fish",
                "sleep",
                "trip"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "potentsial",
            "RightAnswer": "potential",
            "options": [
                "worth",
                "red",
                "military"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "energiya",
            "RightAnswer": "energy",
            "options": [
                "investment",
                "brother",
                "village"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muammo",
            "RightAnswer": "trouble",
            "options": [
                "promise",
                "fish",
                "sleep"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "munosabat",
            "RightAnswer": "relation",
            "options": [
                "energy",
                "investment",
                "brother"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "teginmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "touch",
            "options": [
                "trouble",
                "promise",
                "fish"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "fayl",
            "RightAnswer": "file",
            "options": [
                "touch",
                "trouble",
                "promise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oâ€˜rtasi",
            "RightAnswer": "middle",
            "options": [
                "royal",
                "voluntary",
                "experimental"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ustun",
            "RightAnswer": "bar",
            "options": [
                "file",
                "touch",
                "trouble"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "azob chekmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "suffer",
            "options": [
                "organize",
                "attend",
                "indicate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "strategiya",
            "RightAnswer": "strategy",
            "options": [
                "relation",
                "energy",
                "investment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chuqur",
            "RightAnswer": "deep",
            "options": [
                "ready",
                "wide",
                "alone"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "â€¦ dan tashqari",
            "RightAnswer": "except",
            "options": [
                "until",
                "since",
                "before"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tozalamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "clean",
            "options": [
                "direct",
                "complete",
                "clear"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "moyillik koâ€˜rsatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "tend",
            "options": [
                "suffer",
                "organize",
                "attend"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oldinga yurmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "advance",
            "options": [
                "space",
                "subject",
                "blog"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "toâ€˜ldirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "fill",
            "options": [
                "treat",
                "pull",
                "strike"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yulduz",
            "RightAnswer": "star",
            "options": [
                "bar",
                "file",
                "touch"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tarmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "network",
            "options": [
                "star",
                "bar",
                "file"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "odatda",
            "RightAnswer": "generally",
            "options": [
                "quickly",
                "nearly",
                "clearly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "operatsiya",
            "RightAnswer": "operation",
            "options": [
                "strategy",
                "relation",
                "energy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mos kelmoq, oâ€˜yin",
            "RightAnswer": "match",
            "options": [
                "network",
                "star",
                "bar"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chetlab oâ€˜tmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "avoid",
            "options": [
                "tend",
                "suffer",
                "organize"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 18": [
        {
            "Question": "oâ€˜rindiq",
            "RightAnswer": "seat",
            "options": [
                "match",
                "network",
                "star"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "otmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "throw",
            "options": [
                "fill",
                "treat",
                "pull"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vazifa",
            "RightAnswer": "task",
            "options": [
                "operation",
                "strategy",
                "relation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "odatiy",
            "RightAnswer": "normal",
            "options": [
                "potential",
                "worth",
                "red"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maqsad",
            "RightAnswer": "goal",
            "options": [
                "task",
                "operation",
                "strategy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bogâ€˜lanmoq, sherik",
            "RightAnswer": "associate",
            "options": [
                "throw",
                "fill",
                "treat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "koâ€˜k",
            "RightAnswer": "blue",
            "options": [
                "normal",
                "potential",
                "worth"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ijobiy",
            "RightAnswer": "positive",
            "options": [
                "blue",
                "normal",
                "potential"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "variant, tanlov",
            "RightAnswer": "option",
            "options": [
                "goal",
                "task",
                "operation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "quti",
            "RightAnswer": "box",
            "options": [
                "seat",
                "match",
                "network"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ulkan",
            "RightAnswer": "huge",
            "options": [
                "natural",
                "modern",
                "serious"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xabar",
            "RightAnswer": "message",
            "options": [
                "option",
                "goal",
                "task"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "misol",
            "RightAnswer": "instance",
            "options": [
                "message",
                "option",
                "goal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uslub",
            "RightAnswer": "style",
            "options": [
                "box",
                "seat",
                "match"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "murojaat qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "refer",
            "options": [
                "avoid",
                "tend",
                "suffer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sovuq",
            "RightAnswer": "cold",
            "options": [
                "middle",
                "royal",
                "voluntary"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "itarmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "push",
            "options": [
                "associate",
                "throw",
                "fill"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chorak",
            "RightAnswer": "quarter",
            "options": [
                "stock",
                "light",
                "past"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "faraz qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "assume",
            "options": [
                "refer",
                "avoid",
                "tend"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chaqaloq",
            "RightAnswer": "baby",
            "options": [
                "capital",
                "medium",
                "evening"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muvaffaqiyatli",
            "RightAnswer": "successful",
            "options": [
                "huge",
                "natural",
                "modern"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kuylamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "sing",
            "options": [
                "assume",
                "refer",
                "avoid"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shubha",
            "RightAnswer": "doubt",
            "options": [
                "style",
                "box",
                "seat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "raqobat",
            "RightAnswer": "competition",
            "options": [
                "instance",
                "message",
                "option"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nazariya",
            "RightAnswer": "theory",
            "options": [
                "competition",
                "instance",
                "message"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taklif qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "propose",
            "options": [
                "sing",
                "assume",
                "refer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maâ€™lumotnoma, havola",
            "RightAnswer": "reference",
            "options": [
                "doubt",
                "style",
                "box"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bahs, dalil",
            "RightAnswer": "argument",
            "options": [
                "theory",
                "competition",
                "instance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kattalar",
            "RightAnswer": "adult",
            "options": [
                "baby",
                "capital",
                "medium"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uchmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "fly",
            "options": [
                "push",
                "associate",
                "throw"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hujjat",
            "RightAnswer": "document",
            "options": [
                "reference",
                "doubt",
                "style"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "naqsh",
            "RightAnswer": "pattern",
            "options": [
                "document",
                "reference",
                "doubt"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ariza, dastur",
            "RightAnswer": "application",
            "options": [
                "argument",
                "theory",
                "competition"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "issiq",
            "RightAnswer": "hot",
            "options": [
                "deep",
                "ready",
                "wide"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "albatta",
            "RightAnswer": "obviously",
            "options": [
                "generally",
                "quickly",
                "nearly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "noaniq",
            "RightAnswer": "unclear",
            "options": [
                "successful",
                "huge",
                "natural"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uy to'lovi",
            "RightAnswer": "bill",
            "options": [
                "pattern",
                "document",
                "reference"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qidirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "search",
            "options": [
                "bill",
                "pattern",
                "document"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ajratmoq, alohida",
            "RightAnswer": "separate",
            "options": [
                "clean",
                "direct",
                "complete"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "markaziy",
            "RightAnswer": "central",
            "options": [
                "unclear",
                "successful",
                "huge"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kasbiy faoliyat",
            "RightAnswer": "career",
            "options": [
                "application",
                "argument",
                "theory"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nima bolsa ham",
            "RightAnswer": "anyway",
            "options": [
                "obviously",
                "generally",
                "quickly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nutq",
            "RightAnswer": "speech",
            "options": [
                "career",
                "application",
                "argument"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "it",
            "RightAnswer": "dog",
            "options": [
                "speech",
                "career",
                "application"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ofitser",
            "RightAnswer": "officer",
            "options": [
                "dog",
                "speech",
                "career"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boâ€˜ylab, davomida",
            "RightAnswer": "throughout",
            "options": [
                "beyond",
                "below",
                "behind"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "neft, yogâ€˜",
            "RightAnswer": "oil",
            "options": [
                "officer",
                "dog",
                "speech"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "libos, kiymoq",
            "RightAnswer": "dress",
            "options": [
                "fly",
                "push",
                "associate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "foyda",
            "RightAnswer": "profit",
            "options": [
                "search",
                "bill",
                "pattern"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taxmin qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "guess",
            "options": [
                "dress",
                "fly",
                "push"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 19": [
        {
            "Question": "ko'ngilochar, qiziqarli",
            "RightAnswer": "fun",
            "options": [
                "oil",
                "officer",
                "dog"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "himoya qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "protect",
            "options": [
                "propose",
                "sing",
                "assume"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "manba",
            "RightAnswer": "resource",
            "options": [
                "profit",
                "search",
                "bill"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ilm-fan",
            "RightAnswer": "science",
            "options": [
                "fun",
                "oil",
                "officer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kasallik",
            "RightAnswer": "disease",
            "options": [
                "science",
                "fun",
                "oil"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muvozanat",
            "RightAnswer": "balance",
            "options": [
                "resource",
                "profit",
                "search"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zarar yetkazmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "damage",
            "options": [
                "balance",
                "resource",
                "profit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asos",
            "RightAnswer": "basis",
            "options": [
                "disease",
                "science",
                "fun"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muallif",
            "RightAnswer": "author",
            "options": [
                "basis",
                "disease",
                "science"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asosiy",
            "RightAnswer": "basic",
            "options": [
                "central",
                "unclear",
                "successful"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rag'batlantirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "encourage",
            "options": [
                "protect",
                "propose",
                "sing"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "soch",
            "RightAnswer": "hair",
            "options": [
                "author",
                "basis",
                "disease"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "erkak",
            "RightAnswer": "male",
            "options": [
                "positive",
                "blue",
                "normal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "faoliyat yuritmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "operate",
            "options": [
                "encourage",
                "protect",
                "propose"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aks ettirmoq, fikr yuritmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "reflect",
            "options": [
                "guess",
                "dress",
                "fly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mashq",
            "RightAnswer": "exercise",
            "options": [
                "damage",
                "balance",
                "resource"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "foydali",
            "RightAnswer": "useful",
            "options": [
                "basic",
                "central",
                "unclear"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "restoran",
            "RightAnswer": "restaurant",
            "options": [
                "hair",
                "author",
                "basis"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "daromad",
            "RightAnswer": "income",
            "options": [
                "restaurant",
                "hair",
                "author"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mulk",
            "RightAnswer": "property",
            "options": [
                "income",
                "restaurant",
                "hair"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oldingi",
            "RightAnswer": "previous",
            "options": [
                "hot",
                "deep",
                "ready"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qorong'u",
            "RightAnswer": "dark",
            "options": [
                "cold",
                "middle",
                "royal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tasavvur qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "imagine",
            "options": [
                "operate",
                "encourage",
                "protect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaxshi",
            "RightAnswer": "okay",
            "options": [
                "monthly",
                "weekly",
                "mad"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "daromad topmoq, ishlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "earn",
            "options": [
                "imagine",
                "operate",
                "encourage"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiz farzand",
            "RightAnswer": "daughter",
            "options": [
                "property",
                "income",
                "restaurant"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "pochta, lavozim",
            "RightAnswer": "post",
            "options": [
                "exercise",
                "damage",
                "balance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "gazeta",
            "RightAnswer": "newspaper",
            "options": [
                "daughter",
                "property",
                "income"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta'riflamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "define",
            "options": [
                "earn",
                "imagine",
                "operate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xulosa",
            "RightAnswer": "conclusion",
            "options": [
                "newspaper",
                "daughter",
                "property"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "soat",
            "RightAnswer": "clock",
            "options": [
                "post",
                "exercise",
                "damage"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hamma",
            "RightAnswer": "everybody",
            "options": [
                "yourself",
                "anyone",
                "myself"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dam olish kuni",
            "RightAnswer": "weekend",
            "options": [
                "conclusion",
                "newspaper",
                "daughter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bajarmoq, ijro etmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "perform",
            "options": [
                "define",
                "earn",
                "imagine"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "professional, kasbiy",
            "RightAnswer": "professional",
            "options": [
                "male",
                "positive",
                "blue"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kon, meniki",
            "RightAnswer": "mine",
            "options": [
                "neither",
                "none",
                "whatever"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bahs",
            "RightAnswer": "debate",
            "options": [
                "clock",
                "post",
                "exercise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xotira",
            "RightAnswer": "memory",
            "options": [
                "weekend",
                "conclusion",
                "newspaper"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yashil",
            "RightAnswer": "green",
            "options": [
                "fine",
                "present",
                "tall"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'shiq",
            "RightAnswer": "song",
            "options": [
                "memory",
                "weekend",
                "conclusion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "obyekt, narsa",
            "RightAnswer": "object",
            "options": [
                "debate",
                "clock",
                "post"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "saqlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "maintain",
            "options": [
                "perform",
                "define",
                "earn"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishonch",
            "RightAnswer": "credit",
            "options": [
                "object",
                "debate",
                "clock"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uzuk, halqa",
            "RightAnswer": "ring",
            "options": [
                "credit",
                "object",
                "debate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kashf qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "discover",
            "options": [
                "maintain",
                "perform",
                "define"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'lik",
            "RightAnswer": "dead",
            "options": [
                "professional",
                "male",
                "positive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tushdan keyin",
            "RightAnswer": "afternoon",
            "options": [
                "song",
                "memory",
                "weekend"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "afzal ko'rmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "prefer",
            "options": [
                "discover",
                "maintain",
                "perform"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kengaytirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "extend",
            "options": [
                "prefer",
                "discover",
                "maintain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "imkoniyat",
            "RightAnswer": "possibility",
            "options": [
                "afternoon",
                "song",
                "memory"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 20": [
        {
            "Question": "yo'nalish",
            "RightAnswer": "direction",
            "options": [
                "possibility",
                "afternoon",
                "song"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "imkoniyat, qulaylik",
            "RightAnswer": "facility",
            "options": [
                "direction",
                "possibility",
                "afternoon"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "turli-tumanlik",
            "RightAnswer": "variety",
            "options": [
                "facility",
                "direction",
                "possibility"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "har kuni, kundalik",
            "RightAnswer": "daily",
            "options": [
                "fast",
                "wrong",
                "right"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kiyimlar",
            "RightAnswer": "clothes",
            "options": [
                "variety",
                "facility",
                "direction"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ekran, to'siq",
            "RightAnswer": "screen",
            "options": [
                "ring",
                "credit",
                "object"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yo'l, trek",
            "RightAnswer": "track",
            "options": [
                "screen",
                "ring",
                "credit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "raqs",
            "RightAnswer": "dance",
            "options": [
                "track",
                "screen",
                "ring"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'liq, butunlay",
            "RightAnswer": "completely",
            "options": [
                "anyway",
                "obviously",
                "generally"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ayol",
            "RightAnswer": "female",
            "options": [
                "dead",
                "professional",
                "male"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mas'uliyat",
            "RightAnswer": "responsibility",
            "options": [
                "clothes",
                "variety",
                "facility"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asl",
            "RightAnswer": "original",
            "options": [
                "female",
                "dead",
                "professional"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "opa-singil",
            "RightAnswer": "sister",
            "options": [
                "responsibility",
                "clothes",
                "variety"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tosh",
            "RightAnswer": "rock",
            "options": [
                "dance",
                "track",
                "screen"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tush, orzu",
            "RightAnswer": "dream",
            "options": [
                "rock",
                "dance",
                "track"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... ham emas",
            "RightAnswer": "nor",
            "options": [
                "although",
                "whether",
                "because"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "universitet",
            "RightAnswer": "university",
            "options": [
                "sister",
                "responsibility",
                "clothes"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "osonlikcha",
            "RightAnswer": "easily",
            "options": [
                "completely",
                "anyway",
                "obviously"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "agentlik",
            "RightAnswer": "agency",
            "options": [
                "university",
                "sister",
                "responsibility"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bog'",
            "RightAnswer": "garden",
            "options": [
                "agency",
                "university",
                "sister"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tuzatmoq, o'rnatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "fix",
            "options": [
                "reflect",
                "guess",
                "dress"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oldinga",
            "RightAnswer": "ahead",
            "options": [
                "forward",
                "far",
                "still"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kesishmoq, xoch",
            "RightAnswer": "cross",
            "options": [
                "fit",
                "moderate",
                "mature"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nomzod",
            "RightAnswer": "candidate",
            "options": [
                "garden",
                "agency",
                "university"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vazn",
            "RightAnswer": "weight",
            "options": [
                "dream",
                "rock",
                "dance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yuridik, qonuniy",
            "RightAnswer": "legal",
            "options": [
                "useful",
                "basic",
                "central"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taklif",
            "RightAnswer": "proposal",
            "options": [
                "candidate",
                "garden",
                "agency"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "versiya",
            "RightAnswer": "version",
            "options": [
                "proposal",
                "candidate",
                "garden"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "suhbat",
            "RightAnswer": "conversation",
            "options": [
                "version",
                "proposal",
                "candidate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kimdir",
            "RightAnswer": "somebody",
            "options": [
                "everybody",
                "yourself",
                "anyone"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "funt, qoqmoq ",
            "RightAnswer": "pound",
            "options": [
                "weight",
                "dream",
                "rock"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jurnal",
            "RightAnswer": "magazine",
            "options": [
                "conversation",
                "version",
                "proposal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shakl, forma",
            "RightAnswer": "shape",
            "options": [
                "pound",
                "weight",
                "dream"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dengiz",
            "RightAnswer": "sea",
            "options": [
                "magazine",
                "conversation",
                "version"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "darhol",
            "RightAnswer": "immediately",
            "options": [
                "easily",
                "completely",
                "anyway"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaxshi kutib olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "welcome",
            "options": [
                "advance",
                "space",
                "subject"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tabassum",
            "RightAnswer": "smile",
            "options": [
                "shape",
                "pound",
                "weight"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muloqot",
            "RightAnswer": "communication",
            "options": [
                "sea",
                "magazine",
                "conversation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "an'anaviy",
            "RightAnswer": "traditional",
            "options": [
                "legal",
                "useful",
                "basic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "almashtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "replace",
            "options": [
                "extend",
                "prefer",
                "discover"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sudya, baholamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "judge",
            "options": [
                "smile",
                "shape",
                "pound"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'zi",
            "RightAnswer": "herself",
            "options": [
                "somebody",
                "everybody",
                "yourself"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "birdaniga",
            "RightAnswer": "suddenly",
            "options": [
                "immediately",
                "easily",
                "completely"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "avlod",
            "RightAnswer": "generation",
            "options": [
                "communication",
                "sea",
                "magazine"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taxmin qilmoq, baholamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "estimate",
            "options": [
                "judge",
                "smile",
                "shape"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sevimli",
            "RightAnswer": "favorite",
            "options": [
                "original",
                "female",
                "dead"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiyinchilik",
            "RightAnswer": "difficulty",
            "options": [
                "generation",
                "communication",
                "sea"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sotib olish",
            "RightAnswer": "purchase",
            "options": [
                "estimate",
                "judge",
                "smile"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "otmoq, suratga olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "shoot",
            "options": [
                "fix",
                "reflect",
                "guess"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "e'lon qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "announce",
            "options": [
                "replace",
                "extend",
                "prefer"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 21": [
        {
            "Question": "agar ... bo'lmasa",
            "RightAnswer": "unless",
            "options": [
                "nor",
                "although",
                "whether"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mustaqil",
            "RightAnswer": "independent",
            "options": [
                "traditional",
                "legal",
                "useful"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tavsiya qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "recommend",
            "options": [
                "announce",
                "replace",
                "extend"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "so'rov, tekshiruv",
            "RightAnswer": "survey",
            "options": [
                "purchase",
                "estimate",
                "judge"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'pchilik",
            "RightAnswer": "majority",
            "options": [
                "difficulty",
                "generation",
                "communication"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tayoq, ushlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "stick",
            "options": [
                "shoot",
                "fix",
                "reflect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "so'rov, talab",
            "RightAnswer": "request",
            "options": [
                "survey",
                "purchase",
                "estimate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boy",
            "RightAnswer": "rich",
            "options": [
                "independent",
                "traditional",
                "legal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shamol",
            "RightAnswer": "wind",
            "options": [
                "request",
                "survey",
                "purchase"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hech biri",
            "RightAnswer": "none",
            "options": [
                "whatever",
                "self",
                "ourselves"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "almashmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "exchange",
            "options": [
                "wind",
                "request",
                "survey"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "byudjet",
            "RightAnswer": "budget",
            "options": [
                "exchange",
                "wind",
                "request"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mashhur",
            "RightAnswer": "famous",
            "options": [
                "rich",
                "independent",
                "traditional"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qon",
            "RightAnswer": "blood",
            "options": [
                "majority",
                "difficulty",
                "generation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mos, tegishli",
            "RightAnswer": "appropriate",
            "options": [
                "separate",
                "clean",
                "direct"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "blok, to'siq",
            "RightAnswer": "block",
            "options": [
                "budget",
                "exchange",
                "wind"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "issiq, iliq",
            "RightAnswer": "warm",
            "options": [
                "thin",
                "narrow",
                "frequent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hisoblamoq, sanamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "count",
            "options": [
                "stick",
                "shoot",
                "fix"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sahna, manzara",
            "RightAnswer": "scene",
            "options": [
                "blood",
                "majority",
                "difficulty"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yozuvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "writer",
            "options": [
                "scene",
                "blood",
                "majority"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mazmun, tarkib",
            "RightAnswer": "content",
            "options": [
                "adult",
                "baby",
                "capital"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oldini olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "prevent",
            "options": [
                "recommend",
                "announce",
                "replace"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xavfsiz",
            "RightAnswer": "safe",
            "options": [
                "favorite",
                "original",
                "female"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taklif qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "invite",
            "options": [
                "prevent",
                "recommend",
                "announce"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aralashtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "mix",
            "options": [
                "count",
                "stick",
                "shoot"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "unsur",
            "RightAnswer": "element",
            "options": [
                "writer",
                "scene",
                "blood"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "samarali",
            "RightAnswer": "effective",
            "options": [
                "famous",
                "rich",
                "independent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'g'ri",
            "RightAnswer": "correct",
            "options": [
                "appropriate",
                "separate",
                "clean"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tibbiy",
            "RightAnswer": "medical",
            "options": [
                "effective",
                "famous",
                "rich"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qabul qilmoq, tan olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "admit",
            "options": [
                "invite",
                "prevent",
                "recommend"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "urmoq, g'alaba qozonmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "beat",
            "options": [
                "mix",
                "count",
                "stick"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "telefon",
            "RightAnswer": "telephone",
            "options": [
                "block",
                "budget",
                "exchange"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nusxa, ko'chirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "copy",
            "options": [
                "telephone",
                "block",
                "budget"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'mita",
            "RightAnswer": "committee",
            "options": [
                "element",
                "writer",
                "scene"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xabardor",
            "RightAnswer": "aware",
            "options": [
                "medical",
                "effective",
                "famous"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maslahat",
            "RightAnswer": "advice",
            "options": [
                "committee",
                "element",
                "writer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tutqich, boshqarmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "handle",
            "options": [
                "beat",
                "mix",
                "count"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "stakan, shisha",
            "RightAnswer": "glass",
            "options": [
                "copy",
                "telephone",
                "block"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sud jarayoni, sinov",
            "RightAnswer": "trial",
            "options": [
                "content",
                "adult",
                "baby"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bosim",
            "RightAnswer": "stress",
            "options": [
                "glass",
                "copy",
                "telephone"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ma'muriyat",
            "RightAnswer": "administration",
            "options": [
                "advice",
                "committee",
                "element"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "murakkab, kompleks",
            "RightAnswer": "complex",
            "options": [
                "safe",
                "favorite",
                "original"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "matn",
            "RightAnswer": "text",
            "options": [
                "stress",
                "glass",
                "copy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mazmun, ma'no",
            "RightAnswer": "context",
            "options": [
                "administration",
                "advice",
                "committee"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "minmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "ride",
            "options": [
                "handle",
                "beat",
                "mix"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'g'ridan-to'g'ri",
            "RightAnswer": "directly",
            "options": [
                "suddenly",
                "immediately",
                "easily"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "og'ir",
            "RightAnswer": "heavy",
            "options": [
                "previous",
                "hot",
                "deep"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "olib tashlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "remove",
            "options": [
                "admit",
                "invite",
                "prevent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "olib borish, xulq-atvor",
            "RightAnswer": "conduct",
            "options": [
                "ride",
                "handle",
                "beat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uskuna",
            "RightAnswer": "equipment",
            "options": [
                "context",
                "administration",
                "advice"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 22": [
        {
            "Question": "aks holda",
            "RightAnswer": "otherwise",
            "options": [
                "yet",
                "once",
                "however"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sarlavha, lavozim",
            "RightAnswer": "title",
            "options": [
                "text",
                "stress",
                "glass"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'shimcha",
            "RightAnswer": "extra",
            "options": [
                "complex",
                "safe",
                "favorite"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ijrochi",
            "RightAnswer": "executive",
            "options": [
                "extra",
                "complex",
                "safe"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "stul, rais",
            "RightAnswer": "chair",
            "options": [
                "title",
                "text",
                "stress"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qimmat",
            "RightAnswer": "expensive",
            "options": [
                "aware",
                "medical",
                "effective"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "namuna",
            "RightAnswer": "sample",
            "options": [
                "chair",
                "title",
                "text"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yetkazib bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "deliver",
            "options": [
                "remove",
                "admit",
                "invite"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ulanish",
            "RightAnswer": "connection",
            "options": [
                "equipment",
                "context",
                "administration"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "birinchi, asosiy",
            "RightAnswer": "primary",
            "options": [
                "executive",
                "extra",
                "complex"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ob-havo",
            "RightAnswer": "weather",
            "options": [
                "sample",
                "chair",
                "title"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yig'moq",
            "RightAnswer": "collect",
            "options": [
                "deliver",
                "remove",
                "admit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xabardor qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "inform",
            "options": [
                "collect",
                "deliver",
                "remove"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tamoyil",
            "RightAnswer": "principle",
            "options": [
                "connection",
                "equipment",
                "context"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'g'ri",
            "RightAnswer": "straight",
            "options": [
                "daily",
                "fast",
                "wrong"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "murojaat qilmoq, jozibadorlik",
            "RightAnswer": "appeal",
            "options": [
                "weather",
                "sample",
                "chair"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yuqori darajada",
            "RightAnswer": "highly",
            "options": [
                "directly",
                "suddenly",
                "immediately"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishonch, ishonmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "trust",
            "options": [
                "appeal",
                "weather",
                "sample"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ajoyib",
            "RightAnswer": "wonderful",
            "options": [
                "expensive",
                "aware",
                "medical"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tekis, kvartira",
            "RightAnswer": "flat",
            "options": [
                "distant",
                "wise",
                "eastern"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mutlaqo",
            "RightAnswer": "absolutely",
            "options": [
                "highly",
                "directly",
                "suddenly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oqim, oqmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "flow",
            "options": [
                "conduct",
                "ride",
                "handle"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "adolatli, chiroyli",
            "RightAnswer": "fair",
            "options": [
                "rare",
                "straight",
                "daily"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'shimcha",
            "RightAnswer": "additional",
            "options": [
                "wonderful",
                "expensive",
                "aware"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mas'ul",
            "RightAnswer": "responsible",
            "options": [
                "additional",
                "wonderful",
                "expensive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ferma",
            "RightAnswer": "farm",
            "options": [
                "trust",
                "appeal",
                "weather"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'plam",
            "RightAnswer": "collection",
            "options": [
                "principle",
                "connection",
                "equipment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "osmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "hang",
            "options": [
                "flow",
                "conduct",
                "ride"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "salbiy",
            "RightAnswer": "negative",
            "options": [
                "primary",
                "executive",
                "extra"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "guruh",
            "RightAnswer": "band",
            "options": [
                "farm",
                "trust",
                "appeal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qarindosh",
            "RightAnswer": "relative",
            "options": [
                "negative",
                "primary",
                "executive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sayohat, ekskursiya",
            "RightAnswer": "tour",
            "options": [
                "band",
                "farm",
                "trust"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muqobil",
            "RightAnswer": "alternative",
            "options": [
                "relative",
                "negative",
                "primary"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dasturiy ta'minot",
            "RightAnswer": "software",
            "options": [
                "collection",
                "principle",
                "connection"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "juft",
            "RightAnswer": "pair",
            "options": [
                "tour",
                "band",
                "farm"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kema",
            "RightAnswer": "ship",
            "options": [
                "pair",
                "tour",
                "band"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "munosabat",
            "RightAnswer": "attitude",
            "options": [
                "software",
                "collection",
                "principle"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "arzon",
            "RightAnswer": "cheap",
            "options": [
                "heavy",
                "previous",
                "hot"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ikki barobar",
            "RightAnswer": "double",
            "options": [
                "warm",
                "thin",
                "narrow"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oyoq",
            "RightAnswer": "leg",
            "options": [
                "attitude",
                "software",
                "collection"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kuzatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "observe",
            "options": [
                "inform",
                "collect",
                "deliver"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "gap, jumla",
            "RightAnswer": "sentence",
            "options": [
                "ship",
                "pair",
                "tour"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chop etmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "print",
            "options": [
                "hang",
                "flow",
                "conduct"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taraqqiyot",
            "RightAnswer": "progress",
            "options": [
                "sentence",
                "ship",
                "pair"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haqiqat",
            "RightAnswer": "truth",
            "options": [
                "leg",
                "attitude",
                "software"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hech kim",
            "RightAnswer": "nobody",
            "options": [
                "herself",
                "somebody",
                "everybody"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tekshirmoq, o'rganmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "examine",
            "options": [
                "observe",
                "inform",
                "collect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yotmoq, qo'ymoq",
            "RightAnswer": "lay",
            "options": [
                "print",
                "hang",
                "flow"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tezlik",
            "RightAnswer": "speed",
            "options": [
                "progress",
                "sentence",
                "ship"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "siyosat",
            "RightAnswer": "politics",
            "options": [
                "truth",
                "leg",
                "attitude"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 23": [
        {
            "Question": "javob bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "reply",
            "options": [
                "speed",
                "progress",
                "sentence"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'rsatmoq, ekran",
            "RightAnswer": "display",
            "options": [
                "reply",
                "speed",
                "progress"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'chirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "transfer",
            "options": [
                "display",
                "reply",
                "speed"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mukammal",
            "RightAnswer": "perfect",
            "options": [
                "correct",
                "appropriate",
                "separate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "biroz, ozgina",
            "RightAnswer": "slightly",
            "options": [
                "absolutely",
                "highly",
                "directly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "umumiy",
            "RightAnswer": "overall",
            "options": [
                "cheap",
                "heavy",
                "previous"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "niyat qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "intend",
            "options": [
                "examine",
                "observe",
                "inform"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "foydalanuvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "user",
            "options": [
                "politics",
                "truth",
                "leg"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "javob qaytarmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "respond",
            "options": [
                "intend",
                "examine",
                "observe"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kechki ovqat",
            "RightAnswer": "dinner",
            "options": [
                "user",
                "politics",
                "truth"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sekin",
            "RightAnswer": "slow",
            "options": [
                "fresh",
                "further",
                "free"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muntazam, odatdagi",
            "RightAnswer": "regular",
            "options": [
                "alternative",
                "relative",
                "negative"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jismoniy",
            "RightAnswer": "physical",
            "options": [
                "regular",
                "alternative",
                "relative"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "alohida, ajratilgan",
            "RightAnswer": "apart",
            "options": [
                "ahead",
                "forward",
                "far"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kostyum, mos kelmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "suit",
            "options": [
                "lay",
                "print",
                "hang"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "federativ",
            "RightAnswer": "federal",
            "options": [
                "responsible",
                "additional",
                "wonderful"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oshkor qilmoq, ko'rsatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "reveal",
            "options": [
                "respond",
                "intend",
                "examine"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "foiz",
            "RightAnswer": "percentage",
            "options": [
                "dinner",
                "user",
                "politics"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tinchlik",
            "RightAnswer": "peace",
            "options": [
                "percentage",
                "dinner",
                "user"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maqom, holat",
            "RightAnswer": "status",
            "options": [
                "peace",
                "percentage",
                "dinner"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jinoyat",
            "RightAnswer": "crime",
            "options": [
                "status",
                "peace",
                "percentage"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kamayish, inkor etmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "decline",
            "options": [
                "suit",
                "lay",
                "print"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'n yil",
            "RightAnswer": "decade",
            "options": [
                "crime",
                "status",
                "peace"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishga tushurmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "launch",
            "options": [
                "decline",
                "suit",
                "lay"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ogohlantirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "warn",
            "options": [
                "reveal",
                "respond",
                "intend"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "iste'molchi",
            "RightAnswer": "consumer",
            "options": [
                "trial",
                "content",
                "adult"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yordam, maqullamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "favor",
            "options": [
                "transfer",
                "display",
                "reply"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "quruq",
            "RightAnswer": "dry",
            "options": [
                "double",
                "warm",
                "thin"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sherik",
            "RightAnswer": "partner",
            "options": [
                "favor",
                "transfer",
                "display"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashkilot",
            "RightAnswer": "institution",
            "options": [
                "decade",
                "crime",
                "status"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "joy, payqamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "spot",
            "options": [
                "welcome",
                "advance",
                "space"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ot",
            "RightAnswer": "horse",
            "options": [
                "institution",
                "decade",
                "crime"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oxir-oqibat",
            "RightAnswer": "eventually",
            "options": [
                "slightly",
                "absolutely",
                "highly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "issiq",
            "RightAnswer": "heat",
            "options": [
                "partner",
                "favor",
                "transfer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hayratlantirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "excite",
            "options": [
                "warn",
                "reveal",
                "respond"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'quvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "reader",
            "options": [
                "horse",
                "institution",
                "decade"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ahamiyat",
            "RightAnswer": "importance",
            "options": [
                "reader",
                "horse",
                "institution"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "masofa",
            "RightAnswer": "distance",
            "options": [
                "heat",
                "partner",
                "favor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'llanma, yo'l-yo'riq",
            "RightAnswer": "guide",
            "options": [
                "launch",
                "decline",
                "suit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "grant",
            "options": [
                "guide",
                "launch",
                "decline"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taksi",
            "RightAnswer": "taxi",
            "options": [
                "distance",
                "heat",
                "partner"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boqmoq, ovqatlantirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "feed",
            "options": [
                "grant",
                "guide",
                "launch"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "og'riq",
            "RightAnswer": "pain",
            "options": [
                "importance",
                "reader",
                "horse"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "soha, bo'lim",
            "RightAnswer": "sector",
            "options": [
                "pain",
                "importance",
                "reader"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xato",
            "RightAnswer": "mistake",
            "options": [
                "taxi",
                "distance",
                "heat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta'minlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "ensure",
            "options": [
                "excite",
                "warn",
                "reveal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qoniqtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "satisfy",
            "options": [
                "ensure",
                "excite",
                "warn"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bosh, asosiy",
            "RightAnswer": "chief",
            "options": [
                "physical",
                "regular",
                "alternative"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sovuq, salqin",
            "RightAnswer": "cool",
            "options": [
                "tender",
                "pale",
                "blind"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mutaxassis",
            "RightAnswer": "expert",
            "options": [
                "consumer",
                "trial",
                "content"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 24": [
        {
            "Question": "to'lqin",
            "RightAnswer": "wave",
            "options": [
                "mistake",
                "taxi",
                "distance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "janub",
            "RightAnswer": "south",
            "options": [
                "dark",
                "cold",
                "middle"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mehnat",
            "RightAnswer": "labor",
            "options": [
                "wave",
                "mistake",
                "taxi"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sirt, yuz",
            "RightAnswer": "surface",
            "options": [
                "labor",
                "wave",
                "mistake"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kutubxona",
            "RightAnswer": "library",
            "options": [
                "sector",
                "pain",
                "importance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "a'lo, zo'r",
            "RightAnswer": "excellent",
            "options": [
                "federal",
                "responsible",
                "additional"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qirra, chekka",
            "RightAnswer": "edge",
            "options": [
                "surface",
                "labor",
                "wave"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "lager",
            "RightAnswer": "camp",
            "options": [
                "edge",
                "surface",
                "labor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "auditoriya, tomoshabinlar",
            "RightAnswer": "audience",
            "options": [
                "library",
                "sector",
                "pain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "lift, ko'tarish",
            "RightAnswer": "lift",
            "options": [
                "feed",
                "grant",
                "guide"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tartib, jarayon",
            "RightAnswer": "procedure",
            "options": [
                "audience",
                "library",
                "sector"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "elektron pochta",
            "RightAnswer": "email",
            "options": [
                "camp",
                "edge",
                "surface"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "global, jahon",
            "RightAnswer": "global",
            "options": [
                "excellent",
                "federal",
                "responsible"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kurashmoq, qiyinchilik",
            "RightAnswer": "struggle",
            "options": [
                "lift",
                "feed",
                "grant"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "reklama qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "advertise",
            "options": [
                "satisfy",
                "ensure",
                "excite"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "select",
            "options": [
                "cross",
                "fit",
                "moderate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'rab olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "surround",
            "options": [
                "struggle",
                "lift",
                "feed"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "darajada, miqdor",
            "RightAnswer": "extent",
            "options": [
                "procedure",
                "audience",
                "library"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "daryo",
            "RightAnswer": "river",
            "options": [
                "extent",
                "procedure",
                "audience"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yillik",
            "RightAnswer": "annual",
            "options": [
                "chief",
                "physical",
                "regular"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'liq",
            "RightAnswer": "fully",
            "options": [
                "eventually",
                "slightly",
                "absolutely"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qarama-qarshi, farq",
            "RightAnswer": "contrast",
            "options": [
                "email",
                "camp",
                "edge"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aylanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "roll",
            "options": [
                "surround",
                "struggle",
                "lift"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haqiqat",
            "RightAnswer": "reality",
            "options": [
                "river",
                "extent",
                "procedure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rasm",
            "RightAnswer": "photograph",
            "options": [
                "contrast",
                "email",
                "camp"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rassom, san'atkor",
            "RightAnswer": "artist",
            "options": [
                "reality",
                "river",
                "extent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nizo, mojaro",
            "RightAnswer": "conflict",
            "options": [
                "photograph",
                "contrast",
                "email"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "butun, to'liq",
            "RightAnswer": "entire",
            "options": [
                "global",
                "excellent",
                "federal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mavjudlik",
            "RightAnswer": "presence",
            "options": [
                "artist",
                "reality",
                "river"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "olamon",
            "RightAnswer": "crowd",
            "options": [
                "conflict",
                "photograph",
                "contrast"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "burchak",
            "RightAnswer": "corner",
            "options": [
                "crowd",
                "conflict",
                "photograph"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "gaz",
            "RightAnswer": "gas",
            "options": [
                "presence",
                "artist",
                "reality"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'chmoq, smena",
            "RightAnswer": "shift",
            "options": [
                "roll",
                "surround",
                "struggle"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'r, tarmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "net",
            "options": [
                "quarter",
                "stock",
                "light"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "toifalar",
            "RightAnswer": "category",
            "options": [
                "gas",
                "presence",
                "artist"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kotib",
            "RightAnswer": "secretary",
            "options": [
                "category",
                "gas",
                "presence"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mudofaa",
            "RightAnswer": "defense",
            "options": [
                "secretary",
                "category",
                "gas"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tez",
            "RightAnswer": "quick",
            "options": [
                "overall",
                "cheap",
                "heavy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "pishirmoq, oshpaz",
            "RightAnswer": "cook",
            "options": [
                "shift",
                "roll",
                "surround"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yoymoq, tarqatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "spread",
            "options": [
                "cook",
                "shift",
                "roll"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yadroviy",
            "RightAnswer": "nuclear",
            "options": [
                "entire",
                "global",
                "excellent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "masshtab, shkala",
            "RightAnswer": "scale",
            "options": [
                "corner",
                "crowd",
                "conflict"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haydovchi",
            "RightAnswer": "driver",
            "options": [
                "defense",
                "secretary",
                "category"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'p",
            "RightAnswer": "ball",
            "options": [
                "scale",
                "corner",
                "crowd"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yig'lamoq, baqirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "cry",
            "options": [
                "spread",
                "cook",
                "shift"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kirish, tanishtirish",
            "RightAnswer": "introduction",
            "options": [
                "driver",
                "defense",
                "secretary"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "talab",
            "RightAnswer": "requirement",
            "options": [
                "introduction",
                "driver",
                "defense"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shimol",
            "RightAnswer": "north",
            "options": [
                "south",
                "dark",
                "cold"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tasdiqlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "confirm",
            "options": [
                "advertise",
                "satisfy",
                "ensure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "katta, oliy",
            "RightAnswer": "senior",
            "options": [
                "annual",
                "chief",
                "physical"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 25": [
        {
            "Question": "fotosurat",
            "RightAnswer": "photo",
            "options": [
                "requirement",
                "introduction",
                "driver"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rad etmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "refuse",
            "options": [
                "cry",
                "spread",
                "cook"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "transport, yetkazib berish",
            "RightAnswer": "transport",
            "options": [
                "refuse",
                "cry",
                "spread"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "paydo bo'lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "emerge",
            "options": [
                "confirm",
                "advertise",
                "satisfy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xarita",
            "RightAnswer": "map",
            "options": [
                "ball",
                "scale",
                "corner"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tushuncha",
            "RightAnswer": "concept",
            "options": [
                "photo",
                "requirement",
                "introduction"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "orol",
            "RightAnswer": "island",
            "options": [
                "concept",
                "photo",
                "requirement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "islohot qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "reform",
            "options": [
                "map",
                "ball",
                "scale"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "na ... na ...",
            "RightAnswer": "neither",
            "options": [
                "none",
                "whatever",
                "self"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "futbol",
            "RightAnswer": "football",
            "options": [
                "island",
                "concept",
                "photo"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "omon qolmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "survive",
            "options": [
                "emerge",
                "confirm",
                "advertise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "parvoz",
            "RightAnswer": "flight",
            "options": [
                "reform",
                "map",
                "ball"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chap",
            "RightAnswer": "left",
            "options": [
                "flat",
                "distant",
                "wise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yechim topmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "solve",
            "options": [
                "survive",
                "emerge",
                "confirm"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'shni",
            "RightAnswer": "neighbor",
            "options": [
                "football",
                "island",
                "concept"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "fon, orqa fon",
            "RightAnswer": "background",
            "options": [
                "neighbor",
                "football",
                "island"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "texnika, usul",
            "RightAnswer": "technique",
            "options": [
                "background",
                "neighbor",
                "football"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qatnov",
            "RightAnswer": "traffic",
            "options": [
                "flight",
                "reform",
                "map"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaxshilanish",
            "RightAnswer": "improvement",
            "options": [
                "technique",
                "background",
                "neighbor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asbob",
            "RightAnswer": "tool",
            "options": [
                "improvement",
                "technique",
                "background"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oqibat",
            "RightAnswer": "consequence",
            "options": [
                "tool",
                "improvement",
                "technique"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vaziyat, holat",
            "RightAnswer": "circumstance",
            "options": [
                "consequence",
                "tool",
                "improvement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tutun",
            "RightAnswer": "smoke",
            "options": [
                "traffic",
                "flight",
                "reform"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "reaksiya, javob",
            "RightAnswer": "reaction",
            "options": [
                "circumstance",
                "consequence",
                "tool"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yomg'ir",
            "RightAnswer": "rain",
            "options": [
                "smoke",
                "traffic",
                "flight"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "band, mashg'ul",
            "RightAnswer": "busy",
            "options": [
                "quick",
                "overall",
                "cheap"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dars",
            "RightAnswer": "lesson",
            "options": [
                "reaction",
                "circumstance",
                "consequence"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "miya",
            "RightAnswer": "brain",
            "options": [
                "lesson",
                "reaction",
                "circumstance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "massa, katta miqdor",
            "RightAnswer": "mass",
            "options": [
                "net",
                "quarter",
                "stock"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kulgili, qiziqarli",
            "RightAnswer": "funny",
            "options": [
                "nuclear",
                "entire",
                "global"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hissa qo'shmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "contribute",
            "options": [
                "solve",
                "survive",
                "emerge"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muvaffaqiyatsizlik",
            "RightAnswer": "failure",
            "options": [
                "brain",
                "lesson",
                "reaction"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jadval",
            "RightAnswer": "schedule",
            "options": [
                "rain",
                "smoke",
                "traffic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nutq so'zlovchi",
            "RightAnswer": "speaker",
            "options": [
                "failure",
                "brain",
                "lesson"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "pastki qism",
            "RightAnswer": "bottom",
            "options": [
                "compound",
                "fat",
                "stone"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qabul qilmoq, o'zlashtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "adopt",
            "options": [
                "contribute",
                "solve",
                "survive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "birlashtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "combine",
            "options": [
                "transport",
                "refuse",
                "cry"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tog'",
            "RightAnswer": "mountain",
            "options": [
                "speaker",
                "failure",
                "brain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "isrof, qoldiq",
            "RightAnswer": "waste",
            "options": [
                "schedule",
                "rain",
                "smoke"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yashirmoq, yashirin joy",
            "RightAnswer": "hide",
            "options": [
                "combine",
                "transport",
                "refuse"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nikoh, turmush",
            "RightAnswer": "marriage",
            "options": [
                "mountain",
                "speaker",
                "failure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chipta, viza",
            "RightAnswer": "ticket",
            "options": [
                "waste",
                "schedule",
                "rain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ovqat, taom",
            "RightAnswer": "meal",
            "options": [
                "marriage",
                "mountain",
                "speaker"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hamkasb",
            "RightAnswer": "colleague",
            "options": [
                "meal",
                "marriage",
                "mountain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sumka, sumka",
            "RightAnswer": "bag",
            "options": [
                "ticket",
                "waste",
                "schedule"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "takrorlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "repeat",
            "options": [
                "hide",
                "combine",
                "transport"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "teng",
            "RightAnswer": "equal",
            "options": [
                "green",
                "fine",
                "present"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ifoda, bayonot",
            "RightAnswer": "expression",
            "options": [
                "colleague",
                "meal",
                "marriage"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'shimcha, plus",
            "RightAnswer": "plus",
            "options": [
                "versus",
                "to",
                "till"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nihoyatda",
            "RightAnswer": "extremely",
            "options": [
                "fully",
                "eventually",
                "slightly"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 26": [
        {
            "Question": "egasi",
            "RightAnswer": "owner",
            "options": [
                "expression",
                "colleague",
                "meal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "samolyot, tekislik",
            "RightAnswer": "plane",
            "options": [
                "bag",
                "ticket",
                "waste"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tijorat, reklama",
            "RightAnswer": "commercial",
            "options": [
                "senior",
                "annual",
                "chief"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ayol, xonim",
            "RightAnswer": "lady",
            "options": [
                "owner",
                "expression",
                "colleague"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vazifa, majburiyat",
            "RightAnswer": "duty",
            "options": [
                "lady",
                "owner",
                "expression"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kuch, mustahkamlik",
            "RightAnswer": "strength",
            "options": [
                "duty",
                "lady",
                "owner"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bog'lamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "connect",
            "options": [
                "adopt",
                "contribute",
                "solve"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "madaniy",
            "RightAnswer": "cultural",
            "options": [
                "funny",
                "nuclear",
                "entire"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tartibga solmoq, tashkil qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "arrange",
            "options": [
                "connect",
                "adopt",
                "contribute"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sxema, reja",
            "RightAnswer": "scheme",
            "options": [
                "plane",
                "bag",
                "ticket"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'lov",
            "RightAnswer": "payment",
            "options": [
                "strength",
                "duty",
                "lady"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "afsuski",
            "RightAnswer": "unfortunately",
            "options": [
                "extremely",
                "fully",
                "eventually"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qisqa, qisqacha",
            "RightAnswer": "brief",
            "options": [
                "equal",
                "green",
                "fine"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qush",
            "RightAnswer": "bird",
            "options": [
                "payment",
                "strength",
                "duty"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "namoyish qilmoq, ko'rsatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "demonstrate",
            "options": [
                "arrange",
                "connect",
                "adopt"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hissa",
            "RightAnswer": "contribution",
            "options": [
                "bird",
                "payment",
                "strength"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qadrlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "appreciate",
            "options": [
                "demonstrate",
                "arrange",
                "connect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bob",
            "RightAnswer": "chapter",
            "options": [
                "contribution",
                "bird",
                "payment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sir, maxfiy",
            "RightAnswer": "secret",
            "options": [
                "commercial",
                "senior",
                "annual"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'rinib turibdi",
            "RightAnswer": "apparently",
            "options": [
                "unfortunately",
                "extremely",
                "fully"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "roman, yangicha",
            "RightAnswer": "novel",
            "options": [
                "secret",
                "commercial",
                "senior"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ittifoq",
            "RightAnswer": "union",
            "options": [
                "scheme",
                "plane",
                "bag"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yonmoq, kuymoq",
            "RightAnswer": "burn",
            "options": [
                "repeat",
                "hide",
                "combine"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tendensiya, yo'nalish",
            "RightAnswer": "trend",
            "options": [
                "chapter",
                "contribution",
                "bird"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dastlabki, boshlang'ich",
            "RightAnswer": "initial",
            "options": [
                "novel",
                "secret",
                "commercial"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zavq, mamnuniyat",
            "RightAnswer": "pleasure",
            "options": [
                "trend",
                "chapter",
                "contribution"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taklif",
            "RightAnswer": "suggestion",
            "options": [
                "pleasure",
                "trend",
                "chapter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanqidiy, muhim",
            "RightAnswer": "critical",
            "options": [
                "initial",
                "novel",
                "secret"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yig'ilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "gather",
            "options": [
                "burn",
                "repeat",
                "hide"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asosan",
            "RightAnswer": "mostly",
            "options": [
                "apparently",
                "unfortunately",
                "extremely"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "Yer, yer yuzasi",
            "RightAnswer": "earth",
            "options": [
                "suggestion",
                "pleasure",
                "trend"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yorilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "pop",
            "options": [
                "gather",
                "burn",
                "repeat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muhim, zarur",
            "RightAnswer": "essential",
            "options": [
                "cultural",
                "funny",
                "nuclear"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "istak, xohish",
            "RightAnswer": "desire",
            "options": [
                "union",
                "scheme",
                "plane"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "targ'ib qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "promote",
            "options": [
                "appreciate",
                "demonstrate",
                "arrange"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hozirgi vaqtda",
            "RightAnswer": "currently",
            "options": [
                "mostly",
                "apparently",
                "unfortunately"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishga olmoq,",
            "RightAnswer": "employ",
            "options": [
                "promote",
                "appreciate",
                "demonstrate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yo'l",
            "RightAnswer": "path",
            "options": [
                "earth",
                "suggestion",
                "pleasure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mavzu",
            "RightAnswer": "topic",
            "options": [
                "path",
                "earth",
                "suggestion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "plyaj, sohil",
            "RightAnswer": "beach",
            "options": [
                "desire",
                "union",
                "scheme"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jalb qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "attract",
            "options": [
                "employ",
                "promote",
                "appreciate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jalb qilmoq, band qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "engage",
            "options": [
                "attract",
                "employ",
                "promote"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kuchli, qudratli",
            "RightAnswer": "powerful",
            "options": [
                "essential",
                "cultural",
                "funny"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "gul",
            "RightAnswer": "flower",
            "options": [
                "beach",
                "desire",
                "union"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "inqiroz",
            "RightAnswer": "crisis",
            "options": [
                "topic",
                "path",
                "earth"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'rnashmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "settle",
            "options": [
                "engage",
                "attract",
                "employ"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qayiq",
            "RightAnswer": "boat",
            "options": [
                "flower",
                "beach",
                "desire"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yordam",
            "RightAnswer": "aid",
            "options": [
                "boat",
                "flower",
                "beach"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muxlis, ventilyator",
            "RightAnswer": "fan",
            "options": [
                "aid",
                "boat",
                "flower"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oshxona",
            "RightAnswer": "kitchen",
            "options": [
                "crisis",
                "topic",
                "path"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 27": [
        {
            "Question": "ikki marta",
            "RightAnswer": "twice",
            "options": [
                "currently",
                "mostly",
                "apparently"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yangi, toza",
            "RightAnswer": "fresh",
            "options": [
                "further",
                "free",
                "rough"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kechiktirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "delay",
            "options": [
                "pop",
                "gather",
                "burn"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xavfsizlik",
            "RightAnswer": "safety",
            "options": [
                "kitchen",
                "crisis",
                "topic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muhandis",
            "RightAnswer": "engineer",
            "options": [
                "fan",
                "aid",
                "boat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jimjit, sokin",
            "RightAnswer": "quiet",
            "options": [
                "slow",
                "fresh",
                "further"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sug'urta",
            "RightAnswer": "insurance",
            "options": [
                "safety",
                "kitchen",
                "crisis"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hamshira",
            "RightAnswer": "nurse",
            "options": [
                "engineer",
                "fan",
                "aid"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bo'lib tashlamoq, ajratmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "divide",
            "options": [
                "delay",
                "pop",
                "gather"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uzunlik",
            "RightAnswer": "length",
            "options": [
                "insurance",
                "safety",
                "kitchen"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tergov, tadqiqot",
            "RightAnswer": "investigation",
            "options": [
                "length",
                "insurance",
                "safety"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "paket, jo'natma",
            "RightAnswer": "package",
            "options": [
                "nurse",
                "engineer",
                "fan"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "biror joyda",
            "RightAnswer": "somewhere",
            "options": [
                "twice",
                "currently",
                "mostly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kengaytirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "expand",
            "options": [
                "settle",
                "engage",
                "attract"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sodir qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "commit",
            "options": [
                "expand",
                "settle",
                "engage"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aniq, ravshan",
            "RightAnswer": "obvious",
            "options": [
                "powerful",
                "essential",
                "cultural"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sakramoq",
            "RightAnswer": "jump",
            "options": [
                "divide",
                "delay",
                "pop"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qurol",
            "RightAnswer": "weapon",
            "options": [
                "investigation",
                "length",
                "insurance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nisbatan",
            "RightAnswer": "relatively",
            "options": [
                "somewhere",
                "twice",
                "currently"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mezbon",
            "RightAnswer": "host",
            "options": [
                "jump",
                "divide",
                "delay"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qish",
            "RightAnswer": "winter",
            "options": [
                "weapon",
                "investigation",
                "length"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tuman, mahalla",
            "RightAnswer": "district",
            "options": [
                "winter",
                "weapon",
                "investigation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "keng",
            "RightAnswer": "broad",
            "options": [
                "busy",
                "quick",
                "overall"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shina",
            "RightAnswer": "tire",
            "options": [
                "host",
                "jump",
                "divide"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bahor",
            "RightAnswer": "spring",
            "options": [
                "spot",
                "welcome",
                "advance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ruh, kayfiyat",
            "RightAnswer": "spirit",
            "options": [
                "district",
                "winter",
                "weapon"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tushlik",
            "RightAnswer": "lunch",
            "options": [
                "package",
                "nurse",
                "engineer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haqiqiy, asl",
            "RightAnswer": "actual",
            "options": [
                "obvious",
                "powerful",
                "essential"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hovuz",
            "RightAnswer": "pool",
            "options": [
                "lunch",
                "package",
                "nurse"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jang",
            "RightAnswer": "battle",
            "options": [
                "pool",
                "lunch",
                "package"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "an'ana",
            "RightAnswer": "tradition",
            "options": [
                "spirit",
                "district",
                "winter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "naqd pul",
            "RightAnswer": "cash",
            "options": [
                "battle",
                "pool",
                "lunch"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "deyarli emas, qiyin",
            "RightAnswer": "hardly",
            "options": [
                "relatively",
                "somewhere",
                "twice"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mukofot",
            "RightAnswer": "award",
            "options": [
                "cash",
                "battle",
                "pool"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "murabbiy, avtobus",
            "RightAnswer": "coach",
            "options": [
                "award",
                "cash",
                "battle"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sinov, tajriba",
            "RightAnswer": "experiment",
            "options": [
                "coach",
                "award",
                "cash"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hisobga olish, e'tibor",
            "RightAnswer": "consideration",
            "options": [
                "tradition",
                "spirit",
                "district"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "g'alati, noodatiy",
            "RightAnswer": "strange",
            "options": [
                "actual",
                "obvious",
                "powerful"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kod, kodlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "code",
            "options": [
                "experiment",
                "coach",
                "award"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mumkin, ehtimol",
            "RightAnswer": "possibly",
            "options": [
                "hardly",
                "relatively",
                "somewhere"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tahdid",
            "RightAnswer": "threat",
            "options": [
                "consideration",
                "tradition",
                "spirit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "avariya, hodisa",
            "RightAnswer": "accident",
            "options": [
                "threat",
                "consideration",
                "tradition"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "imkonsiz",
            "RightAnswer": "impossible",
            "options": [
                "strange",
                "actual",
                "obvious"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "daromad",
            "RightAnswer": "revenue",
            "options": [
                "accident",
                "threat",
                "consideration"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "imkon yaratmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "enable",
            "options": [
                "commit",
                "expand",
                "settle"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'rqmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "afraid",
            "options": [
                "impossible",
                "strange",
                "actual"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "faol",
            "RightAnswer": "active",
            "options": [
                "afraid",
                "impossible",
                "strange"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xulosa qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "conclude",
            "options": [
                "enable",
                "commit",
                "expand"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "diniy",
            "RightAnswer": "religious",
            "options": [
                "active",
                "afraid",
                "impossible"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "saraton",
            "RightAnswer": "cancer",
            "options": [
                "revenue",
                "accident",
                "threat"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 28": [
        {
            "Question": "ishontirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "convince",
            "options": [
                "conclude",
                "enable",
                "commit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "farqlanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "vary",
            "options": [
                "convince",
                "conclude",
                "enable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "atrof-muhitga oid",
            "RightAnswer": "environmental",
            "options": [
                "religious",
                "active",
                "afraid"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "quyosh",
            "RightAnswer": "sun",
            "options": [
                "code",
                "experiment",
                "coach"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sog'lom",
            "RightAnswer": "healthy",
            "options": [
                "environmental",
                "religious",
                "active"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "esmoq, puflamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "blow",
            "options": [
                "tire",
                "host",
                "jump"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hajm, ovoz",
            "RightAnswer": "volume",
            "options": [
                "sun",
                "code",
                "experiment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "joylashuv",
            "RightAnswer": "location",
            "options": [
                "cancer",
                "revenue",
                "accident"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sarmoya kiritmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "invest",
            "options": [
                "vary",
                "convince",
                "conclude"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "davom etmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "proceed",
            "options": [
                "invest",
                "vary",
                "convince"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yuvmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "wash",
            "options": [
                "blow",
                "tire",
                "host"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aktyor",
            "RightAnswer": "actor",
            "options": [
                "location",
                "cancer",
                "revenue"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xursand",
            "RightAnswer": "glad",
            "options": [
                "healthy",
                "environmental",
                "religious"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "lenta, magnit lenta",
            "RightAnswer": "tape",
            "options": [
                "volume",
                "sun",
                "code"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bo'lsa-da",
            "RightAnswer": "whereas",
            "options": [
                "unless",
                "nor",
                "although"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qarama-qarshi",
            "RightAnswer": "opposite",
            "options": [
                "left",
                "flat",
                "distant"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tosh",
            "RightAnswer": "stone",
            "options": [
                "mass",
                "net",
                "quarter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yig'indisi, summa",
            "RightAnswer": "sum",
            "options": [
                "tape",
                "volume",
                "sun"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qotillik",
            "RightAnswer": "murder",
            "options": [
                "sum",
                "tape",
                "volume"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nazorat qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "monitor",
            "options": [
                "wash",
                "blow",
                "tire"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "askar",
            "RightAnswer": "soldier",
            "options": [
                "actor",
                "location",
                "cancer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "moliya",
            "RightAnswer": "finance",
            "options": [
                "murder",
                "sum",
                "tape"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nafrat",
            "RightAnswer": "hate",
            "options": [
                "monitor",
                "wash",
                "blow"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tuxum",
            "RightAnswer": "egg",
            "options": [
                "soldier",
                "actor",
                "location"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "konsert",
            "RightAnswer": "concert",
            "options": [
                "finance",
                "murder",
                "sum"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tebranish, hayrat",
            "RightAnswer": "shock",
            "options": [
                "concert",
                "finance",
                "murder"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qulay",
            "RightAnswer": "comfortable",
            "options": [
                "glad",
                "healthy",
                "environmental"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "odatiy",
            "RightAnswer": "usual",
            "options": [
                "critical",
                "initial",
                "novel"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ehtiyotkorlik bilan",
            "RightAnswer": "carefully",
            "options": [
                "possibly",
                "hardly",
                "relatively"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sumka, paketlash",
            "RightAnswer": "pack",
            "options": [
                "hate",
                "monitor",
                "wash"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "eslamoq, chaqirib olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "recall",
            "options": [
                "pack",
                "hate",
                "monitor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sharob",
            "RightAnswer": "wine",
            "options": [
                "shock",
                "concert",
                "finance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kamera",
            "RightAnswer": "camera",
            "options": [
                "egg",
                "soldier",
                "actor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "suzmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "swim",
            "options": [
                "recall",
                "pack",
                "hate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishlab chiqarish",
            "RightAnswer": "manufacture",
            "options": [
                "swim",
                "recall",
                "pack"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "teatr",
            "RightAnswer": "theater",
            "options": [
                "camera",
                "egg",
                "soldier"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aylana, velosiped",
            "RightAnswer": "cycle",
            "options": [
                "wine",
                "shock",
                "concert"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kofe",
            "RightAnswer": "coffee",
            "options": [
                "theater",
                "camera",
                "egg"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "butunlay",
            "RightAnswer": "totally",
            "options": [
                "carefully",
                "possibly",
                "hardly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muzey",
            "RightAnswer": "museum",
            "options": [
                "coffee",
                "theater",
                "camera"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mehmon",
            "RightAnswer": "visitor",
            "options": [
                "museum",
                "coffee",
                "theater"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "erkinlik",
            "RightAnswer": "freedom",
            "options": [
                "visitor",
                "museum",
                "coffee"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qurilish",
            "RightAnswer": "construction",
            "options": [
                "freedom",
                "visitor",
                "museum"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aziz",
            "RightAnswer": "dear",
            "options": [
                "usual",
                "critical",
                "initial"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maqsad, obyektiv",
            "RightAnswer": "objective",
            "options": [
                "brief",
                "equal",
                "green"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bundan tashqari",
            "RightAnswer": "moreover",
            "options": [
                "totally",
                "carefully",
                "possibly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ustiga",
            "RightAnswer": "onto",
            "options": [
                "despite",
                "upon",
                "toward"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tarixiy",
            "RightAnswer": "historical",
            "options": [
                "comfortable",
                "glad",
                "healthy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qarshi chiqmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "oppose",
            "options": [
                "proceed",
                "invest",
                "vary"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tarmoq, filial",
            "RightAnswer": "branch",
            "options": [
                "cycle",
                "wine",
                "shock"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 29": [
        {
            "Question": "transport vositasi",
            "RightAnswer": "vehicle",
            "options": [
                "construction",
                "freedom",
                "visitor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "olim",
            "RightAnswer": "scientist",
            "options": [
                "vehicle",
                "construction",
                "freedom"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "marshrut, yo'l",
            "RightAnswer": "route",
            "options": [
                "branch",
                "cycle",
                "wine"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bog'lamoq, o'ramoq",
            "RightAnswer": "bind",
            "options": [
                "manufacture",
                "swim",
                "recall"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tegishli bo'lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "belong",
            "options": [
                "oppose",
                "proceed",
                "invest"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta'm, tatib ko'rmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "taste",
            "options": [
                "bind",
                "manufacture",
                "swim"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bugun kechasi",
            "RightAnswer": "tonight",
            "options": [
                "tomorrow",
                "yesterday",
                "today"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "moda",
            "RightAnswer": "fashion",
            "options": [
                "spring",
                "spot",
                "welcome"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xavf",
            "RightAnswer": "danger",
            "options": [
                "scientist",
                "vehicle",
                "construction"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bomba",
            "RightAnswer": "bomb",
            "options": [
                "route",
                "branch",
                "cycle"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "harbiy kuchlar",
            "RightAnswer": "army",
            "options": [
                "danger",
                "scientist",
                "vehicle"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xavfli",
            "RightAnswer": "dangerous",
            "options": [
                "historical",
                "comfortable",
                "glad"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kamaymoq",
            "RightAnswer": "decrease",
            "options": [
                "taste",
                "bind",
                "manufacture"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jarohat yetkazmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "hurt",
            "options": [
                "grin",
                "cough",
                "fade"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kengash",
            "RightAnswer": "council",
            "options": [
                "army",
                "danger",
                "scientist"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tahrirchi",
            "RightAnswer": "editor",
            "options": [
                "council",
                "army",
                "danger"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "odatda",
            "RightAnswer": "normally",
            "options": [
                "moreover",
                "totally",
                "carefully"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'rish, manzara",
            "RightAnswer": "sight",
            "options": [
                "bomb",
                "route",
                "branch"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaratmoq, hosil qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "generate",
            "options": [
                "belong",
                "oppose",
                "proceed"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sovg'a",
            "RightAnswer": "gift",
            "options": [
                "sight",
                "bomb",
                "route"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yetkazib berish",
            "RightAnswer": "delivery",
            "options": [
                "editor",
                "council",
                "army"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "inkor qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "deny",
            "options": [
                "generate",
                "belong",
                "oppose"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mehmon",
            "RightAnswer": "guest",
            "options": [
                "delivery",
                "editor",
                "council"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "biror kim",
            "RightAnswer": "anybody",
            "options": [
                "nobody",
                "herself",
                "somebody"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yotoqxona",
            "RightAnswer": "bedroom",
            "options": [
                "guest",
                "delivery",
                "editor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "iqtibos",
            "RightAnswer": "quote",
            "options": [
                "decrease",
                "taste",
                "bind"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chiqmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "climb",
            "options": [
                "quote",
                "decrease",
                "taste"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asosan",
            "RightAnswer": "basically",
            "options": [
                "normally",
                "moreover",
                "totally"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zo'ravonlik",
            "RightAnswer": "violence",
            "options": [
                "bedroom",
                "guest",
                "delivery"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vazir",
            "RightAnswer": "minister",
            "options": [
                "violence",
                "bedroom",
                "guest"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asosan",
            "RightAnswer": "mainly",
            "options": [
                "basically",
                "normally",
                "moreover"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "og'iz",
            "RightAnswer": "mouth",
            "options": [
                "minister",
                "violence",
                "bedroom"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shovqin",
            "RightAnswer": "noise",
            "options": [
                "mouth",
                "minister",
                "violence"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xulq-atvor",
            "RightAnswer": "manner",
            "options": [
                "noise",
                "mouth",
                "minister"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qurol",
            "RightAnswer": "gun",
            "options": [
                "manner",
                "noise",
                "mouth"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kvadrat, maydon",
            "RightAnswer": "square",
            "options": [
                "objective",
                "brief",
                "equal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hodisa, bayram",
            "RightAnswer": "occasion",
            "options": [
                "gun",
                "manner",
                "noise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanish, xushmuomala",
            "RightAnswer": "familiar",
            "options": [
                "dear",
                "usual",
                "critical"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "ignore",
            "options": [
                "deny",
                "generate",
                "belong"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vayron qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "destroy",
            "options": [
                "ignore",
                "deny",
                "generate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ish, masala",
            "RightAnswer": "affair",
            "options": [
                "occasion",
                "gun",
                "manner"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "fuqarolik",
            "RightAnswer": "civil",
            "options": [
                "familiar",
                "dear",
                "usual"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "topmoq, joylashmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "locate",
            "options": [
                "destroy",
                "ignore",
                "deny"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "fuqaro",
            "RightAnswer": "citizen",
            "options": [
                "affair",
                "occasion",
                "gun"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "harorat",
            "RightAnswer": "temperature",
            "options": [
                "citizen",
                "affair",
                "occasion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oltin",
            "RightAnswer": "gold",
            "options": [
                "expert",
                "consumer",
                "trial"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ichki, uyga oid",
            "RightAnswer": "domestic",
            "options": [
                "civil",
                "familiar",
                "dear"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yuk, yuklash",
            "RightAnswer": "load",
            "options": [
                "gift",
                "sight",
                "bomb"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "e'tiqod",
            "RightAnswer": "belief",
            "options": [
                "temperature",
                "citizen",
                "affair"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "askarlar",
            "RightAnswer": "troops",
            "options": [
                "belief",
                "temperature",
                "citizen"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 30": [
        {
            "Question": "texnik",
            "RightAnswer": "technical",
            "options": [
                "dangerous",
                "historical",
                "comfortable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "eslatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "remind",
            "options": [
                "locate",
                "destroy",
                "ignore"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tartib, kelishuv",
            "RightAnswer": "arrangement",
            "options": [
                "troops",
                "belief",
                "temperature"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "teri",
            "RightAnswer": "skin",
            "options": [
                "load",
                "gift",
                "sight"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qamoqxona",
            "RightAnswer": "prison",
            "options": [
                "arrangement",
                "troops",
                "belief"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "almashtirmoq, o'zgartirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "switch",
            "options": [
                "climb",
                "quote",
                "decrease"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "egallamoq, olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "acquire",
            "options": [
                "remind",
                "locate",
                "destroy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "korporativ",
            "RightAnswer": "corporate",
            "options": [
                "technical",
                "dangerous",
                "historical"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "adolatli, munosib",
            "RightAnswer": "fairly",
            "options": [
                "mainly",
                "basically",
                "normally"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yog'och",
            "RightAnswer": "wood",
            "options": [
                "prison",
                "arrangement",
                "troops"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qatnashmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "participate",
            "options": [
                "acquire",
                "remind",
                "locate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiyin, mustahkam",
            "RightAnswer": "tough",
            "options": [
                "broad",
                "busy",
                "quick"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yirtmoq, ko'z yoshi ",
            "RightAnswer": "tear",
            "options": [
                "switch",
                "climb",
                "quote"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vakil",
            "RightAnswer": "representative",
            "options": [
                "gold",
                "expert",
                "consumer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sig'im, qobiliyat",
            "RightAnswer": "capacity",
            "options": [
                "wood",
                "prison",
                "arrangement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chegara",
            "RightAnswer": "border",
            "options": [
                "skin",
                "load",
                "gift"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "silkitmoq, titratmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "shake",
            "options": [
                "tear",
                "switch",
                "climb"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "baholash, tahlil",
            "RightAnswer": "assessment",
            "options": [
                "capacity",
                "wood",
                "prison"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "poyabzal",
            "RightAnswer": "shoe",
            "options": [
                "assessment",
                "capacity",
                "wood"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kerak, lozim",
            "RightAnswer": "ought",
            "options": [
                "must",
                "might",
                "may"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "reklama a_) : ad,",
            "RightAnswer": "ad",
            "options": [
                "shoe",
                "assessment",
                "capacity"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'lov, haq",
            "RightAnswer": "fee",
            "options": [
                "ad",
                "shoe",
                "assessment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zal",
            "RightAnswer": "hall",
            "options": [
                "fee",
                "ad",
                "shoe"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tartib-qoidalar",
            "RightAnswer": "regulation",
            "options": [
                "hall",
                "fee",
                "ad"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qochmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "escape",
            "options": [
                "shake",
                "tear",
                "switch"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "studiya",
            "RightAnswer": "studio",
            "options": [
                "regulation",
                "hall",
                "fee"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'g'ri, mos",
            "RightAnswer": "proper",
            "options": [
                "tough",
                "broad",
                "busy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dam olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "relax",
            "options": [
                "participate",
                "acquire",
                "remind"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sayyoh",
            "RightAnswer": "tourist",
            "options": [
                "studio",
                "regulation",
                "hall"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "komponent, qism",
            "RightAnswer": "component",
            "options": [
                "tourist",
                "studio",
                "regulation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qurbi yetmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "afford",
            "options": [
                "relax",
                "participate",
                "acquire"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "advokat",
            "RightAnswer": "lawyer",
            "options": [
                "component",
                "tourist",
                "studio"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shubha qilmoq, gumondor",
            "RightAnswer": "suspect",
            "options": [
                "select",
                "cross",
                "fit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "stakan, kubok",
            "RightAnswer": "cup",
            "options": [
                "border",
                "skin",
                "load"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta'rif",
            "RightAnswer": "description",
            "options": [
                "lawyer",
                "component",
                "tourist"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishonch",
            "RightAnswer": "confidence",
            "options": [
                "description",
                "lawyer",
                "component"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sanoatga oid",
            "RightAnswer": "industrial",
            "options": [
                "corporate",
                "technical",
                "dangerous"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shikoyat qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "complain",
            "options": [
                "afford",
                "relax",
                "participate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nuqtai nazar",
            "RightAnswer": "perspective",
            "options": [
                "confidence",
                "description",
                "lawyer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xato",
            "RightAnswer": "error",
            "options": [
                "perspective",
                "confidence",
                "description"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xibsga olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "arrest",
            "options": [
                "escape",
                "shake",
                "tear"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "baholamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "assess",
            "options": [
                "complain",
                "afford",
                "relax"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ro'yxatdan o'tmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "register",
            "options": [
                "arrest",
                "escape",
                "shake"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "foyda keltiruvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "asset",
            "options": [
                "error",
                "perspective",
                "confidence"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "belgi",
            "RightAnswer": "signal",
            "options": [
                "cup",
                "border",
                "skin"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "barmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "finger",
            "options": [
                "signal",
                "cup",
                "border"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tegishli, aloqador",
            "RightAnswer": "relevant",
            "options": [
                "industrial",
                "corporate",
                "technical"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'rganmoq, tadqiq qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "explore",
            "options": [
                "assess",
                "complain",
                "afford"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yetakchilik",
            "RightAnswer": "leadership",
            "options": [
                "asset",
                "error",
                "perspective"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sodiqlik, mas'uliyat",
            "RightAnswer": "commitment",
            "options": [
                "leadership",
                "asset",
                "error"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 31": [
        {
            "Question": "uyg'onmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "wake",
            "options": [
                "finger",
                "signal",
                "cup"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "talab etiladi, zarur",
            "RightAnswer": "necessarily",
            "options": [
                "fairly",
                "mainly",
                "basically"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yorqin, porloq",
            "RightAnswer": "bright",
            "options": [
                "proper",
                "tough",
                "broad"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ramka",
            "RightAnswer": "frame",
            "options": [
                "wake",
                "finger",
                "signal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sekin-asta",
            "RightAnswer": "slowly",
            "options": [
                "necessarily",
                "fairly",
                "mainly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bog'lanish, aloqa",
            "RightAnswer": "bond",
            "options": [
                "frame",
                "wake",
                "finger"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishga olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "hire",
            "options": [
                "register",
                "arrest",
                "escape"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "teshik, bo'shliq",
            "RightAnswer": "hole",
            "options": [
                "commitment",
                "leadership",
                "asset"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bog'lamoq, galstuk",
            "RightAnswer": "tie",
            "options": [
                "bond",
                "frame",
                "wake"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ichki",
            "RightAnswer": "internal",
            "options": [
                "relevant",
                "industrial",
                "corporate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zanjir",
            "RightAnswer": "chain",
            "options": [
                "tie",
                "bond",
                "frame"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "adabiyot",
            "RightAnswer": "literature",
            "options": [
                "hole",
                "commitment",
                "leadership"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qurbon",
            "RightAnswer": "victim",
            "options": [
                "literature",
                "hole",
                "commitment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tahdid qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "threaten",
            "options": [
                "explore",
                "assess",
                "complain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bo'linma, bo'lim",
            "RightAnswer": "division",
            "options": [
                "victim",
                "literature",
                "hole"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xavfsiz, mustahkam",
            "RightAnswer": "secure",
            "options": [
                "perfect",
                "correct",
                "appropriate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hayratlantirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "amaze",
            "options": [
                "threaten",
                "explore",
                "assess"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qurilma, asbob",
            "RightAnswer": "device",
            "options": [
                "division",
                "victim",
                "literature"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tug'ilish",
            "RightAnswer": "birth",
            "options": [
                "device",
                "division",
                "victim"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'rmon",
            "RightAnswer": "forest",
            "options": [
                "birth",
                "device",
                "division"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yorliq",
            "RightAnswer": "label",
            "options": [
                "chain",
                "tie",
                "bond"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ildiz",
            "RightAnswer": "root",
            "options": [
                "label",
                "chain",
                "tie"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zavod",
            "RightAnswer": "factory",
            "options": [
                "forest",
                "birth",
                "device"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xarajat",
            "RightAnswer": "expense",
            "options": [
                "root",
                "label",
                "chain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kanal",
            "RightAnswer": "channel",
            "options": [
                "expense",
                "root",
                "label"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tergov qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "investigate",
            "options": [
                "amaze",
                "threaten",
                "explore"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tavsiya",
            "RightAnswer": "recommendation",
            "options": [
                "factory",
                "forest",
                "birth"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "pog'ona, daraja",
            "RightAnswer": "rank",
            "options": [
                "channel",
                "expense",
                "root"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tipik, odatiy",
            "RightAnswer": "typical",
            "options": [
                "internal",
                "relevant",
                "industrial"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "g'arb",
            "RightAnswer": "west",
            "options": [
                "leather",
                "stranger",
                "liquid"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "do'stona",
            "RightAnswer": "friendly",
            "options": [
                "typical",
                "internal",
                "relevant"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "turuvchi, aholi",
            "RightAnswer": "resident",
            "options": [
                "representative",
                "gold",
                "expert"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta'minot",
            "RightAnswer": "provision",
            "options": [
                "recommendation",
                "factory",
                "forest"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "diqqatni qaratmoq, yig'moq",
            "RightAnswer": "concentrate",
            "options": [
                "hire",
                "register",
                "arrest"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'p",
            "RightAnswer": "plenty",
            "options": [
                "west",
                "leather",
                "stranger"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chetga sotmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "export",
            "options": [
                "rank",
                "channel",
                "expense"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "butunlay",
            "RightAnswer": "entirely",
            "options": [
                "slowly",
                "necessarily",
                "fairly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kuchli tarzda",
            "RightAnswer": "strongly",
            "options": [
                "entirely",
                "slowly",
                "necessarily"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'prik",
            "RightAnswer": "bridge",
            "options": [
                "export",
                "rank",
                "channel"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "iborat bo'lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "consist",
            "options": [
                "investigate",
                "amaze",
                "threaten"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bitiruvchi, bitirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "graduate",
            "options": [
                "concentrate",
                "hire",
                "register"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "brend",
            "RightAnswer": "brand",
            "options": [
                "bridge",
                "export",
                "rank"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "axloqiy",
            "RightAnswer": "moral",
            "options": [
                "domestic",
                "civil",
                "familiar"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qat'iyat bilan talab qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "insist",
            "options": [
                "consist",
                "investigate",
                "amaze"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kombinatsiya, aralashma",
            "RightAnswer": "combination",
            "options": [
                "provision",
                "recommendation",
                "factory"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "suiiste'mol, zo'ravonlik",
            "RightAnswer": "abuse",
            "options": [
                "brand",
                "bridge",
                "export"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muz",
            "RightAnswer": "ice",
            "options": [
                "abuse",
                "brand",
                "bridge"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asosiy, direktor",
            "RightAnswer": "principal",
            "options": [
                "moral",
                "domestic",
                "civil"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ustoz, boshliq",
            "RightAnswer": "master",
            "options": [
                "fashion",
                "spring",
                "spot"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aniq, albatta",
            "RightAnswer": "definitely",
            "options": [
                "strongly",
                "entirely",
                "slowly"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 32": [
        {
            "Question": "sessiya",
            "RightAnswer": "session",
            "options": [
                "combination",
                "provision",
                "recommendation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "daraja, sinf",
            "RightAnswer": "grade",
            "options": [
                "ice",
                "abuse",
                "brand"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shunga qaramay",
            "RightAnswer": "nevertheless",
            "options": [
                "therefore",
                "though",
                "whereas"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bashorat qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "predict",
            "options": [
                "insist",
                "consist",
                "investigate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oldin, ilgari",
            "RightAnswer": "previously",
            "options": [
                "definitely",
                "strongly",
                "entirely"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "himoya",
            "RightAnswer": "protection",
            "options": [
                "session",
                "combination",
                "provision"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asosan",
            "RightAnswer": "largely",
            "options": [
                "previously",
                "definitely",
                "strongly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uylanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "wed",
            "options": [
                "predict",
                "insist",
                "consist"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ijaraga olmoq, ijara",
            "RightAnswer": "rent",
            "options": [
                "grade",
                "ice",
                "abuse"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zarba, otish",
            "RightAnswer": "shot",
            "options": [
                "rent",
                "grade",
                "ice"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'rinish",
            "RightAnswer": "appearance",
            "options": [
                "protection",
                "session",
                "combination"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mantiqan to'g'ri, oqilona",
            "RightAnswer": "reasonable",
            "options": [
                "friendly",
                "typical",
                "internal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kafolat",
            "RightAnswer": "guarantee",
            "options": [
                "shot",
                "rent",
                "grade"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "gacha",
            "RightAnswer": "till",
            "options": [
                "except",
                "until",
                "since"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mavzu, tema",
            "RightAnswer": "theme",
            "options": [
                "appearance",
                "protection",
                "session"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hukm, baholash",
            "RightAnswer": "judgment",
            "options": [
                "theme",
                "appearance",
                "protection"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "g'alati",
            "RightAnswer": "odd",
            "options": [
                "north",
                "south",
                "dark"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tasdiqlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "approve",
            "options": [
                "wed",
                "predict",
                "insist"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kredit, qarz",
            "RightAnswer": "loan",
            "options": [
                "guarantee",
                "shot",
                "rent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta'rif",
            "RightAnswer": "definition",
            "options": [
                "judgment",
                "theme",
                "appearance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "saylamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "elect",
            "options": [
                "express",
                "close",
                "mean"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "atmosfera, havo",
            "RightAnswer": "atmosphere",
            "options": [
                "definition",
                "judgment",
                "theme"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dehqon",
            "RightAnswer": "farmer",
            "options": [
                "atmosphere",
                "definition",
                "judgment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taqqoslash",
            "RightAnswer": "comparison",
            "options": [
                "farmer",
                "atmosphere",
                "definition"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xususiyat",
            "RightAnswer": "characteristic",
            "options": [
                "principal",
                "moral",
                "domestic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "litsenziya, ruxsatnoma",
            "RightAnswer": "license",
            "options": [
                "loan",
                "guarantee",
                "shot"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tayanmoq, ishonmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "rely",
            "options": [
                "approve",
                "wed",
                "predict"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tor",
            "RightAnswer": "narrow",
            "options": [
                "frequent",
                "keen",
                "exact"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muvaffaqiyat qozonmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "succeed",
            "options": [
                "rely",
                "approve",
                "wed"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shaxsi",
            "RightAnswer": "identity",
            "options": [
                "comparison",
                "farmer",
                "atmosphere"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ish stoli",
            "RightAnswer": "desk",
            "options": [
                "identity",
                "comparison",
                "farmer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ruxsat, lisenziya",
            "RightAnswer": "permit",
            "options": [
                "graduate",
                "concentrate",
                "hire"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jiddiylik bilan",
            "RightAnswer": "seriously",
            "options": [
                "largely",
                "previously",
                "definitely"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yovvoyi",
            "RightAnswer": "wild",
            "options": [
                "quiet",
                "slow",
                "fresh"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bo'sh",
            "RightAnswer": "empty",
            "options": [
                "dry",
                "double",
                "warm"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'mita, komissiya",
            "RightAnswer": "commission",
            "options": [
                "license",
                "loan",
                "guarantee"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'ziga xos, yagona",
            "RightAnswer": "unique",
            "options": [
                "reasonable",
                "friendly",
                "typical"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "assotsiatsiya, uyushma",
            "RightAnswer": "association",
            "options": [
                "desk",
                "identity",
                "comparison"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asbob, jihoz",
            "RightAnswer": "instrument",
            "options": [
                "association",
                "desk",
                "identity"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sarmoyador",
            "RightAnswer": "investor",
            "options": [
                "instrument",
                "association",
                "desk"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "amaliy, foydali",
            "RightAnswer": "practical",
            "options": [
                "characteristic",
                "principal",
                "moral"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "choy",
            "RightAnswer": "tea",
            "options": [
                "investor",
                "instrument",
                "association"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chiroyli, yoqimli",
            "RightAnswer": "lovely",
            "options": [
                "bright",
                "proper",
                "tough"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yumshoq",
            "RightAnswer": "soft",
            "options": [
                "fair",
                "rare",
                "straight"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qator, chiziq",
            "RightAnswer": "row",
            "options": [
                "commission",
                "license",
                "loan"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yoshlar, yoshlik",
            "RightAnswer": "youth",
            "options": [
                "tea",
                "investor",
                "instrument"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qulf",
            "RightAnswer": "lock",
            "options": [
                "row",
                "commission",
                "license"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yoqilg'i",
            "RightAnswer": "fuel",
            "options": [
                "lock",
                "row",
                "commission"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kutish, umid",
            "RightAnswer": "expectation",
            "options": [
                "youth",
                "tea",
                "investor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ish bilan ta'minlash, bandlik",
            "RightAnswer": "employment",
            "options": [
                "expectation",
                "youth",
                "tea"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 33": [
        {
            "Question": "bayram qilmoq, nishonlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "celebrate",
            "options": [
                "succeed",
                "rely",
                "approve"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yelka",
            "RightAnswer": "shoulder",
            "options": [
                "fuel",
                "lock",
                "row"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nafas",
            "RightAnswer": "breath",
            "options": [
                "employment",
                "expectation",
                "youth"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tobora ko'proq",
            "RightAnswer": "increasingly",
            "options": [
                "seriously",
                "largely",
                "previously"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chetdan sotib olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "import",
            "options": [
                "shoulder",
                "fuel",
                "lock"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shisha idish",
            "RightAnswer": "bottle",
            "options": [
                "import",
                "shoulder",
                "fuel"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'zimiz",
            "RightAnswer": "ourselves",
            "options": [
                "anybody",
                "nobody",
                "herself"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "varoq, choyshab",
            "RightAnswer": "sheet",
            "options": [
                "bottle",
                "import",
                "shoulder"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dvigatel, motor",
            "RightAnswer": "engine",
            "options": [
                "breath",
                "employment",
                "expectation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uloqtirmoq, otmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "cast",
            "options": [
                "permit",
                "graduate",
                "concentrate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "g'oya, tushuncha",
            "RightAnswer": "notion",
            "options": [
                "engine",
                "breath",
                "employment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "konservativ, an'anaviy",
            "RightAnswer": "conservative",
            "options": [
                "unique",
                "reasonable",
                "friendly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sayohat, safar",
            "RightAnswer": "journey",
            "options": [
                "sheet",
                "bottle",
                "import"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qarshilik",
            "RightAnswer": "opposition",
            "options": [
                "notion",
                "engine",
                "breath"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yengillik",
            "RightAnswer": "relief",
            "options": [
                "opposition",
                "notion",
                "engine"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qarz",
            "RightAnswer": "debt",
            "options": [
                "relief",
                "opposition",
                "notion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sharaf, hurmat",
            "RightAnswer": "honor",
            "options": [
                "journey",
                "sheet",
                "bottle"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "natija",
            "RightAnswer": "outcome",
            "options": [
                "debt",
                "relief",
                "opposition"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ayblamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "blame",
            "options": [
                "honor",
                "journey",
                "sheet"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tushuntirish",
            "RightAnswer": "explanation",
            "options": [
                "outcome",
                "debt",
                "relief"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yuzaga kelmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "arise",
            "options": [
                "celebrate",
                "succeed",
                "rely"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "musiqiy",
            "RightAnswer": "musical",
            "options": [
                "practical",
                "characteristic",
                "principal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tiklanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "recover",
            "options": [
                "arise",
                "celebrate",
                "succeed"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ota",
            "RightAnswer": "dad",
            "options": [
                "explanation",
                "outcome",
                "debt"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "cho'zilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "stretch",
            "options": [
                "cast",
                "permit",
                "graduate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "e'lon qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "declare",
            "options": [
                "recover",
                "arise",
                "celebrate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nafaqaga chiqmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "retire",
            "options": [
                "declare",
                "recover",
                "arise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "juda kichik",
            "RightAnswer": "tiny",
            "options": [
                "conservative",
                "unique",
                "reasonable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ehtiyotkor",
            "RightAnswer": "careful",
            "options": [
                "tiny",
                "conservative",
                "unique"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mos, qulay",
            "RightAnswer": "suitable",
            "options": [
                "careful",
                "tiny",
                "conservative"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mahalliy, ona tiliga oid",
            "RightAnswer": "native",
            "options": [
                "musical",
                "practical",
                "characteristic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "meva",
            "RightAnswer": "fruit",
            "options": [
                "blame",
                "honor",
                "journey"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tahlil qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "analyze",
            "options": [
                "retire",
                "declare",
                "recover"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "guvoh bo'lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "witness",
            "options": [
                "fruit",
                "blame",
                "honor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "pochta",
            "RightAnswer": "mail",
            "options": [
                "witness",
                "fruit",
                "blame"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dahshatli",
            "RightAnswer": "terrible",
            "options": [
                "suitable",
                "careful",
                "tiny"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tadqiqotchi",
            "RightAnswer": "researcher",
            "options": [
                "dad",
                "explanation",
                "outcome"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "odatiy",
            "RightAnswer": "ordinary",
            "options": [
                "native",
                "musical",
                "practical"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanlov",
            "RightAnswer": "selection",
            "options": [
                "researcher",
                "dad",
                "explanation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "har qanday joyda",
            "RightAnswer": "anywhere",
            "options": [
                "there",
                "instead",
                "down"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aqliy",
            "RightAnswer": "mental",
            "options": [
                "terrible",
                "suitable",
                "careful"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishtirokchi",
            "RightAnswer": "participant",
            "options": [
                "selection",
                "researcher",
                "dad"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'rish, orzu",
            "RightAnswer": "vision",
            "options": [
                "participant",
                "selection",
                "researcher"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shaxsiyat",
            "RightAnswer": "personality",
            "options": [
                "vision",
                "participant",
                "selection"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aynan, asosan",
            "RightAnswer": "specifically",
            "options": [
                "increasingly",
                "seriously",
                "largely"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yog'",
            "RightAnswer": "fat",
            "options": [
                "stone",
                "mass",
                "net"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kirish",
            "RightAnswer": "entry",
            "options": [
                "mail",
                "witness",
                "fruit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hamkasb, sherik",
            "RightAnswer": "fellow",
            "options": [
                "resident",
                "representative",
                "gold"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kimyoviy",
            "RightAnswer": "chemical",
            "options": [
                "ordinary",
                "native",
                "musical"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ushlamoq, qo'lga kiritmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "capture",
            "options": [
                "stretch",
                "cast",
                "permit"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 34": [
        {
            "Question": "uch, maslahat",
            "RightAnswer": "tip",
            "options": [
                "entry",
                "mail",
                "witness"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chegirma",
            "RightAnswer": "discount",
            "options": [
                "tip",
                "entry",
                "mail"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "cho'qqi",
            "RightAnswer": "peak",
            "options": [
                "discount",
                "tip",
                "entry"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rais",
            "RightAnswer": "chairman",
            "options": [
                "personality",
                "vision",
                "participant"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nisbat, ulush",
            "RightAnswer": "proportion",
            "options": [
                "chairman",
                "personality",
                "vision"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "quloq",
            "RightAnswer": "ear",
            "options": [
                "proportion",
                "chairman",
                "personality"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yo'qolmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "disappear",
            "options": [
                "analyze",
                "retire",
                "declare"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "baqirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "shout",
            "options": [
                "capture",
                "stretch",
                "cast"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yarim metr, maydon",
            "RightAnswer": "yard",
            "options": [
                "ear",
                "proportion",
                "chairman"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "doimiy",
            "RightAnswer": "constant",
            "options": [
                "chemical",
                "ordinary",
                "native"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sezilarli darajada",
            "RightAnswer": "significantly",
            "options": [
                "specifically",
                "increasingly",
                "seriously"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tepalik",
            "RightAnswer": "hill",
            "options": [
                "yard",
                "ear",
                "proportion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sezilarli, katta",
            "RightAnswer": "considerable",
            "options": [
                "mental",
                "terrible",
                "suitable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'rsatma, dars",
            "RightAnswer": "instruction",
            "options": [
                "hill",
                "yard",
                "ear"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aql, ong",
            "RightAnswer": "intelligence",
            "options": [
                "instruction",
                "hill",
                "yard"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mukammal",
            "RightAnswer": "ideal",
            "options": [
                "constant",
                "chemical",
                "ordinary"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xalq",
            "RightAnswer": "folk",
            "options": [
                "intelligence",
                "instruction",
                "hill"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "albatta, ishonch bilan",
            "RightAnswer": "surely",
            "options": [
                "significantly",
                "specifically",
                "increasingly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "himoya qilmoq, qo'riqchi",
            "RightAnswer": "guard",
            "options": [
                "shout",
                "capture",
                "stretch"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mushuk",
            "RightAnswer": "cat",
            "options": [
                "folk",
                "intelligence",
                "instruction"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "biroz",
            "RightAnswer": "somewhat",
            "options": [
                "surely",
                "significantly",
                "specifically"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'pmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "kiss",
            "options": [
                "guard",
                "shout",
                "capture"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taqdimot, ko'rsatma",
            "RightAnswer": "presentation",
            "options": [
                "cat",
                "folk",
                "intelligence"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'shma, bog'lanish",
            "RightAnswer": "joint",
            "options": [
                "ideal",
                "constant",
                "chemical"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "raqobat qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "compete",
            "options": [
                "disappear",
                "analyze",
                "retire"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "so'rovnoma, saylov",
            "RightAnswer": "poll",
            "options": [
                "peak",
                "discount",
                "tip"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zaif",
            "RightAnswer": "weak",
            "options": [
                "lovely",
                "bright",
                "proper"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "e'tiqod, ishonch",
            "RightAnswer": "faith",
            "options": [
                "presentation",
                "cat",
                "folk"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kamayish, qisqartirish",
            "RightAnswer": "reduction",
            "options": [
                "faith",
                "presentation",
                "cat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zaxira",
            "RightAnswer": "reserve",
            "options": [
                "kiss",
                "guard",
                "shout"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shikoyat",
            "RightAnswer": "complaint",
            "options": [
                "reduction",
                "faith",
                "presentation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zerikmoq, burg'ulamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "bore",
            "options": [
                "reserve",
                "kiss",
                "guard"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "missiya, vazifa",
            "RightAnswer": "mission",
            "options": [
                "complaint",
                "reduction",
                "faith"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qandaydir, biroz",
            "RightAnswer": "somehow",
            "options": [
                "somewhat",
                "surely",
                "significantly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ohang",
            "RightAnswer": "tone",
            "options": [
                "mission",
                "complaint",
                "reduction"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mahalla",
            "RightAnswer": "neighborhood",
            "options": [
                "tone",
                "mission",
                "complaint"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yo'lovchi",
            "RightAnswer": "passenger",
            "options": [
                "neighborhood",
                "tone",
                "mission"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "adolat",
            "RightAnswer": "justice",
            "options": [
                "passenger",
                "neighborhood",
                "tone"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bosqich, davr",
            "RightAnswer": "phase",
            "options": [
                "justice",
                "passenger",
                "neighborhood"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oriq, yupqa",
            "RightAnswer": "thin",
            "options": [
                "narrow",
                "frequent",
                "keen"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shoshilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "rush",
            "options": [
                "bore",
                "reserve",
                "kiss"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rasmiy",
            "RightAnswer": "formal",
            "options": [
                "joint",
                "ideal",
                "constant"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "din",
            "RightAnswer": "religion",
            "options": [
                "phase",
                "justice",
                "passenger"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ish beruvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "employer",
            "options": [
                "religion",
                "phase",
                "justice"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rad etmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "reject",
            "options": [
                "rush",
                "bore",
                "reserve"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ikkinchi, so'nggi",
            "RightAnswer": "latter",
            "options": [
                "sharp",
                "round",
                "abstract"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tarelka",
            "RightAnswer": "plate",
            "options": [
                "poll",
                "peak",
                "discount"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taqiqlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "ban",
            "options": [
                "plate",
                "poll",
                "peak"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'g'irlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "steal",
            "options": [
                "reject",
                "rush",
                "bore"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "norozilik, namoyish",
            "RightAnswer": "protest",
            "options": [
                "steal",
                "reject",
                "rush"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 35": [
        {
            "Question": "indeks, ko'rsatkich",
            "RightAnswer": "index",
            "options": [
                "ban",
                "plate",
                "poll"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qayg'uli, g'amgin",
            "RightAnswer": "sad",
            "options": [
                "considerable",
                "mental",
                "terrible"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tez-tez",
            "RightAnswer": "frequently",
            "options": [
                "somehow",
                "somewhat",
                "surely"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "doira, aylana",
            "RightAnswer": "circle",
            "options": [
                "index",
                "ban",
                "plate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "foydali, yordam beruvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "helpful",
            "options": [
                "sad",
                "considerable",
                "mental"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "buyrug', boshqarish",
            "RightAnswer": "command",
            "options": [
                "protest",
                "steal",
                "reject"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jozibali, chiroyli",
            "RightAnswer": "attractive",
            "options": [
                "helpful",
                "sad",
                "considerable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kasal",
            "RightAnswer": "sick",
            "options": [
                "square",
                "objective",
                "brief"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taassurot",
            "RightAnswer": "impression",
            "options": [
                "employer",
                "religion",
                "phase"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qodir emas",
            "RightAnswer": "unable",
            "options": [
                "attractive",
                "helpful",
                "sad"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hazil, kulgili so'z",
            "RightAnswer": "joke",
            "options": [
                "circle",
                "index",
                "ban"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "osmon",
            "RightAnswer": "sky",
            "options": [
                "impression",
                "employer",
                "religion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ustun, kolonka",
            "RightAnswer": "column",
            "options": [
                "sky",
                "impression",
                "employer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "elektron",
            "RightAnswer": "electronic",
            "options": [
                "unable",
                "attractive",
                "helpful"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "majbur qilmoq, qo'ymoq",
            "RightAnswer": "impose",
            "options": [
                "compete",
                "disappear",
                "analyze"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jinoyatchi",
            "RightAnswer": "criminal",
            "options": [
                "formal",
                "joint",
                "ideal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bundan tashqari, shuningdek",
            "RightAnswer": "besides",
            "options": [
                "throughout",
                "beyond",
                "below"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'g'ri, mos ravishda",
            "RightAnswer": "properly",
            "options": [
                "frequently",
                "somehow",
                "somewhat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qadimgi",
            "RightAnswer": "ancient",
            "options": [
                "criminal",
                "formal",
                "joint"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qirg'oq",
            "RightAnswer": "coast",
            "options": [
                "joke",
                "circle",
                "index"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jiddiy kasal",
            "RightAnswer": "ill",
            "options": [
                "ancient",
                "criminal",
                "formal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "otmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "kick",
            "options": [
                "command",
                "protest",
                "steal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaqin, yaqindan",
            "RightAnswer": "closely",
            "options": [
                "properly",
                "frequently",
                "somehow"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'p, bir nechta",
            "RightAnswer": "multiple",
            "options": [
                "ill",
                "ancient",
                "criminal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hosil, berish",
            "RightAnswer": "yield",
            "options": [
                "kick",
                "command",
                "protest"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "orqali, yondashuv",
            "RightAnswer": "via",
            "options": [
                "onto",
                "despite",
                "upon"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qonunchilik",
            "RightAnswer": "legislation",
            "options": [
                "column",
                "sky",
                "impression"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tuman, viloyat",
            "RightAnswer": "county",
            "options": [
                "legislation",
                "column",
                "sky"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'xshamagan, farqli",
            "RightAnswer": "unlike",
            "options": [
                "via",
                "onto",
                "despite"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mobil, harakatlanuvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "mobile",
            "options": [
                "multiple",
                "ill",
                "ancient"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yordamchi",
            "RightAnswer": "assistant",
            "options": [
                "county",
                "legislation",
                "column"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "amalga oshirmoq, asbob",
            "RightAnswer": "implement",
            "options": [
                "yield",
                "kick",
                "command"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "diagramma, jadval",
            "RightAnswer": "chart",
            "options": [
                "coast",
                "joke",
                "circle"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'shmoq, ilova qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "attach",
            "options": [
                "impose",
                "compete",
                "disappear"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "do'zax",
            "RightAnswer": "hell",
            "options": [
                "assistant",
                "county",
                "legislation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hamma joyda",
            "RightAnswer": "everywhere",
            "options": [
                "closely",
                "properly",
                "frequently"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maslahat bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "advise",
            "options": [
                "attach",
                "impose",
                "compete"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uy xo'jaligi",
            "RightAnswer": "household",
            "options": [
                "fellow",
                "resident",
                "representative"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tan olmoq, e'tirof etmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "acknowledge",
            "options": [
                "advise",
                "attach",
                "impose"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mukofot",
            "RightAnswer": "reward",
            "options": [
                "chart",
                "coast",
                "joke"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sharq",
            "RightAnswer": "east",
            "options": [
                "plenty",
                "west",
                "leather"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shlyapa",
            "RightAnswer": "hat",
            "options": [
                "hell",
                "assistant",
                "county"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "akademik, ilmiy",
            "RightAnswer": "academic",
            "options": [
                "mobile",
                "multiple",
                "ill"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "saylovchi",
            "RightAnswer": "voter",
            "options": [
                "hat",
                "hell",
                "assistant"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shu vaqtda, o'shanda",
            "RightAnswer": "meanwhile",
            "options": [
                "less",
                "most",
                "more"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bundan tashqari, shuningdek",
            "RightAnswer": "furthermore",
            "options": [
                "everywhere",
                "closely",
                "properly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ayblamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "accuse",
            "options": [
                "acknowledge",
                "advise",
                "attach"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ilmiy",
            "RightAnswer": "scientific",
            "options": [
                "electronic",
                "unable",
                "attractive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maosh, ish haqi",
            "RightAnswer": "wage",
            "options": [
                "reward",
                "chart",
                "coast"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yo'qlik, qoldirish",
            "RightAnswer": "absence",
            "options": [
                "voter",
                "hat",
                "hell"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 36": [
        {
            "Question": "qurmoq, tuzmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "construct",
            "options": [
                "implement",
                "yield",
                "kick"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "izoh, mulohaza",
            "RightAnswer": "remark",
            "options": [
                "construct",
                "implement",
                "yield"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dori-darmon",
            "RightAnswer": "medicine",
            "options": [
                "absence",
                "voter",
                "hat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "professor",
            "RightAnswer": "professor",
            "options": [
                "medicine",
                "absence",
                "voter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kamdan-kam, nodir",
            "RightAnswer": "rare",
            "options": [
                "straight",
                "daily",
                "fast"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "niyat, maqsad",
            "RightAnswer": "intention",
            "options": [
                "professor",
                "medicine",
                "absence"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'n ikkita",
            "RightAnswer": "dozen",
            "options": [
                "intention",
                "professor",
                "medicine"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yerlashish, kelishuv",
            "RightAnswer": "settlement",
            "options": [
                "dozen",
                "intention",
                "professor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bo'shliq, teshik",
            "RightAnswer": "gap",
            "options": [
                "settlement",
                "dozen",
                "intention"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "keng tarqalgan, keng doirada",
            "RightAnswer": "widely",
            "options": [
                "furthermore",
                "everywhere",
                "closely"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "minimal, eng kam",
            "RightAnswer": "minimum",
            "options": [
                "household",
                "fellow",
                "resident"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shimoliy",
            "RightAnswer": "northern",
            "options": [
                "academic",
                "mobile",
                "multiple"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mulk, yer",
            "RightAnswer": "estate",
            "options": [
                "gap",
                "settlement",
                "dozen"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "teng ravishda",
            "RightAnswer": "equally",
            "options": [
                "widely",
                "furthermore",
                "everywhere"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ochib berish, ko'rsatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "expose",
            "options": [
                "accuse",
                "acknowledge",
                "advise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jonli, tirik",
            "RightAnswer": "alive",
            "options": [
                "scientific",
                "electronic",
                "unable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yopmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "shut",
            "options": [
                "suspect",
                "select",
                "cross"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "g'alaba",
            "RightAnswer": "victory",
            "options": [
                "estate",
                "gap",
                "settlement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hal qilmoq, yechim topmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "resolve",
            "options": [
                "remark",
                "construct",
                "implement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanqidchi",
            "RightAnswer": "critic",
            "options": [
                "victory",
                "estate",
                "gap"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'zgaruvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "variable",
            "options": [
                "northern",
                "academic",
                "mobile"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ulkan, katta",
            "RightAnswer": "enormous",
            "options": [
                "alive",
                "scientific",
                "electronic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shirin",
            "RightAnswer": "sweet",
            "options": [
                "sick",
                "square",
                "objective"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "doimiy",
            "RightAnswer": "permanent",
            "options": [
                "variable",
                "northern",
                "academic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "his-tuyg'u",
            "RightAnswer": "emotion",
            "options": [
                "critic",
                "victory",
                "estate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "izlamoq, orzu qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "pursue",
            "options": [
                "expose",
                "accuse",
                "acknowledge"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "baland",
            "RightAnswer": "tall",
            "options": [
                "opposite",
                "left",
                "flat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shoshilmoq, rag'batlantirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "urge",
            "options": [
                "resolve",
                "remark",
                "construct"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dushman",
            "RightAnswer": "enemy",
            "options": [
                "emotion",
                "critic",
                "victory"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tayinlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "appoint",
            "options": [
                "pursue",
                "expose",
                "accuse"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sut",
            "RightAnswer": "milk",
            "options": [
                "wage",
                "reward",
                "chart"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "iste'dod",
            "RightAnswer": "talent",
            "options": [
                "enemy",
                "emotion",
                "critic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hid, hidlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "smell",
            "options": [
                "urge",
                "resolve",
                "remark"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "avvalgi, oldingi",
            "RightAnswer": "prior",
            "options": [
                "permanent",
                "variable",
                "northern"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ustuvorlik, birinchi navbatda",
            "RightAnswer": "priority",
            "options": [
                "talent",
                "enemy",
                "emotion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "onlayn, internet orqali",
            "RightAnswer": "online",
            "options": [
                "weak",
                "lovely",
                "bright"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ibora, jumla",
            "RightAnswer": "phrase",
            "options": [
                "milk",
                "wage",
                "reward"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uchuvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "pilot",
            "options": [
                "phrase",
                "milk",
                "wage"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "barqaror",
            "RightAnswer": "stable",
            "options": [
                "prior",
                "permanent",
                "variable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "faqatgina, oddiygina",
            "RightAnswer": "merely",
            "options": [
                "equally",
                "widely",
                "furthermore"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yechim, qaror",
            "RightAnswer": "resolution",
            "options": [
                "priority",
                "talent",
                "enemy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muloqot qilmoq, yetkazmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "communicate",
            "options": [
                "appoint",
                "pursue",
                "expose"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jarohat",
            "RightAnswer": "injury",
            "options": [
                "resolution",
                "priority",
                "talent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "katta, keng",
            "RightAnswer": "vast",
            "options": [
                "enormous",
                "alive",
                "scientific"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'rgazma",
            "RightAnswer": "exhibition",
            "options": [
                "injury",
                "resolution",
                "priority"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishlab chiqaruvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "producer",
            "options": [
                "exhibition",
                "injury",
                "resolution"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mintaqaviy",
            "RightAnswer": "regional",
            "options": [
                "vast",
                "enormous",
                "alive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "darhol, zudlik bilan",
            "RightAnswer": "immediate",
            "options": [
                "stable",
                "prior",
                "permanent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hodisa, voqea",
            "RightAnswer": "incident",
            "options": [
                "producer",
                "exhibition",
                "injury"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bolalik",
            "RightAnswer": "childhood",
            "options": [
                "incident",
                "producer",
                "exhibition"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 37": [
        {
            "Question": "loyiha, chizma",
            "RightAnswer": "draft",
            "options": [
                "pilot",
                "phrase",
                "milk"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sirpanish, qochmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "slip",
            "options": [
                "smell",
                "urge",
                "resolve"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hamroh bo'lmoq, olib kelmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "accompany",
            "options": [
                "communicate",
                "appoint",
                "pursue"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "siyosatchi",
            "RightAnswer": "politician",
            "options": [
                "childhood",
                "incident",
                "producer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "g'azablangan",
            "RightAnswer": "angry",
            "options": [
                "regional",
                "vast",
                "enormous"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taqqilatmoq, urmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "knock",
            "options": [
                "slip",
                "smell",
                "urge"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "urug'",
            "RightAnswer": "seed",
            "options": [
                "draft",
                "pilot",
                "phrase"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maosh",
            "RightAnswer": "salary",
            "options": [
                "politician",
                "childhood",
                "incident"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tasvirlamoq, misol keltirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "illustrate",
            "options": [
                "accompany",
                "communicate",
                "appoint"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sha'ma qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "imply",
            "options": [
                "illustrate",
                "accompany",
                "communicate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nonushta",
            "RightAnswer": "breakfast",
            "options": [
                "salary",
                "politician",
                "childhood"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vaqtincha",
            "RightAnswer": "temporary",
            "options": [
                "immediate",
                "stable",
                "prior"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "erkin fikrlovchi",
            "RightAnswer": "liberal",
            "options": [
                "temporary",
                "immediate",
                "stable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'l",
            "RightAnswer": "lake",
            "options": [
                "breakfast",
                "salary",
                "politician"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "malakali bo'lmoq, mos kelmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "qualify",
            "options": [
                "imply",
                "illustrate",
                "accompany"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "raqobatbardosh",
            "RightAnswer": "competitive",
            "options": [
                "angry",
                "regional",
                "vast"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haqiqatan, chin dildan",
            "RightAnswer": "truly",
            "options": [
                "merely",
                "equally",
                "widely"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "salom h_) : hi,",
            "RightAnswer": "hi",
            "options": [
                "each",
                "another",
                "both"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sariq",
            "RightAnswer": "yellow",
            "options": [
                "liberal",
                "temporary",
                "immediate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "odat, xulq",
            "RightAnswer": "habit",
            "options": [
                "lake",
                "breakfast",
                "salary"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tekis, aylana narsa",
            "RightAnswer": "disk",
            "options": [
                "habit",
                "lake",
                "breakfast"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yadro, asos",
            "RightAnswer": "core",
            "options": [
                "disk",
                "habit",
                "lake"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hissiy",
            "RightAnswer": "emotional",
            "options": [
                "competitive",
                "angry",
                "regional"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "samolyot",
            "RightAnswer": "aircraft",
            "options": [
                "core",
                "disk",
                "habit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'zi",
            "RightAnswer": "self",
            "options": [
                "ourselves",
                "anybody",
                "nobody"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "metal",
            "RightAnswer": "metal",
            "options": [
                "aircraft",
                "core",
                "disk"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mavjudlik",
            "RightAnswer": "existence",
            "options": [
                "metal",
                "aircraft",
                "core"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "suyak",
            "RightAnswer": "bone",
            "options": [
                "existence",
                "metal",
                "aircraft"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "panel, panjara",
            "RightAnswer": "panel",
            "options": [
                "seed",
                "draft",
                "pilot"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asosiy, birinchi darajali",
            "RightAnswer": "prime",
            "options": [
                "sweet",
                "sick",
                "square"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tayinlash, uchrashuv",
            "RightAnswer": "appointment",
            "options": [
                "bone",
                "existence",
                "metal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta'kidlash, urg'u berish",
            "RightAnswer": "emphasize",
            "options": [
                "qualify",
                "imply",
                "illustrate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maksimal, eng katta",
            "RightAnswer": "maximum",
            "options": [
                "minimum",
                "household",
                "fellow"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "samarali tarzda",
            "RightAnswer": "effectively",
            "options": [
                "truly",
                "merely",
                "equally"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshqa joyda",
            "RightAnswer": "elsewhere",
            "options": [
                "effectively",
                "truly",
                "merely"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashvishlanmoq, aralashmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "bother",
            "options": [
                "knock",
                "slip",
                "smell"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashabbus",
            "RightAnswer": "initiative",
            "options": [
                "appointment",
                "bone",
                "existence"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'tkir, tez",
            "RightAnswer": "sharp",
            "options": [
                "round",
                "abstract",
                "concrete"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "parhez, dieta",
            "RightAnswer": "diet",
            "options": [
                "panel",
                "seed",
                "draft"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "harakat, tuzatish",
            "RightAnswer": "motion",
            "options": [
                "diet",
                "panel",
                "seed"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kulrang",
            "RightAnswer": "gray",
            "options": [
                "yellow",
                "liberal",
                "temporary"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "plastik",
            "RightAnswer": "plastic",
            "options": [
                "gray",
                "yellow",
                "liberal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "murakkablashtirmoq, qiyinlashtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "complicate",
            "options": [
                "emphasize",
                "qualify",
                "imply"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "intizom",
            "RightAnswer": "discipline",
            "options": [
                "motion",
                "diet",
                "panel"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kutgandek chiqmaslik, ko'nglini qoldirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "disappoint",
            "options": [
                "complicate",
                "emphasize",
                "qualify"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rahbar, ish beruvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "boss",
            "options": [
                "discipline",
                "motion",
                "diet"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taxmin, faraz",
            "RightAnswer": "assumption",
            "options": [
                "initiative",
                "appointment",
                "bone"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muzlamoq, muzlatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "freeze",
            "options": [
                "bother",
                "knock",
                "slip"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ekstremal, haddan tashqari",
            "RightAnswer": "extreme",
            "options": [
                "plastic",
                "gray",
                "yellow"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'tish, matn",
            "RightAnswer": "passage",
            "options": [
                "assumption",
                "initiative",
                "appointment"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 38": [
        {
            "Question": "obro', sha'n",
            "RightAnswer": "reputation",
            "options": [
                "passage",
                "assumption",
                "initiative"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oldinga",
            "RightAnswer": "forth",
            "options": [
                "meanwhile",
                "less",
                "most"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muzokara, kelishuv",
            "RightAnswer": "negotiation",
            "options": [
                "reputation",
                "passage",
                "assumption"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mexanizm, usul",
            "RightAnswer": "mechanism",
            "options": [
                "negotiation",
                "reputation",
                "passage"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "paltolar, poyabzal",
            "RightAnswer": "coat",
            "options": [
                "boss",
                "discipline",
                "motion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "demokratiya",
            "RightAnswer": "democracy",
            "options": [
                "mechanism",
                "negotiation",
                "reputation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "cho'ntak",
            "RightAnswer": "pocket",
            "options": [
                "coat",
                "boss",
                "discipline"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "omadli",
            "RightAnswer": "lucky",
            "options": [
                "online",
                "weak",
                "lovely"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'qnashuv, avariya",
            "RightAnswer": "crash",
            "options": [
                "freeze",
                "bother",
                "knock"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kuzatuv",
            "RightAnswer": "observation",
            "options": [
                "democracy",
                "mechanism",
                "negotiation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "go'sht",
            "RightAnswer": "meat",
            "options": [
                "observation",
                "democracy",
                "mechanism"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "diqqat, e'tibor",
            "RightAnswer": "concentration",
            "options": [
                "meat",
                "observation",
                "democracy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "natija, oqibat",
            "RightAnswer": "implication",
            "options": [
                "concentration",
                "meat",
                "observation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "munosib bo'lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "deserve",
            "options": [
                "disappoint",
                "complicate",
                "emphasize"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "noodatiy, g'alati",
            "RightAnswer": "unusual",
            "options": [
                "emotional",
                "competitive",
                "angry"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "himoya qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "defend",
            "options": [
                "deserve",
                "disappoint",
                "complicate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "klassik, an'anaviy",
            "RightAnswer": "classic",
            "options": [
                "extreme",
                "plastic",
                "gray"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "podshoh",
            "RightAnswer": "king",
            "options": [
                "implication",
                "concentration",
                "meat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'zaro aloqalar, muloqot",
            "RightAnswer": "interaction",
            "options": [
                "king",
                "implication",
                "concentration"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta'mirlash, tuzatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "repair",
            "options": [
                "crash",
                "freeze",
                "bother"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qulab tushmoq, yiqilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "collapse",
            "options": [
                "repair",
                "crash",
                "freeze"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qarz olmoq, olib turmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "borrow",
            "options": [
                "defend",
                "deserve",
                "disappoint"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asosiy, fundamental",
            "RightAnswer": "fundamental",
            "options": [
                "classic",
                "extreme",
                "plastic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taom, idish",
            "RightAnswer": "dish",
            "options": [
                "pocket",
                "coat",
                "boss"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xorijda, chet elda",
            "RightAnswer": "abroad",
            "options": [
                "apart",
                "ahead",
                "forward"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jon, ruh",
            "RightAnswer": "soul",
            "options": [
                "interaction",
                "king",
                "implication"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qodir, imkoniyatga ega",
            "RightAnswer": "capable",
            "options": [
                "unusual",
                "emotional",
                "competitive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yutmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "defeat",
            "options": [
                "collapse",
                "repair",
                "crash"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "prezidentga oid",
            "RightAnswer": "presidential",
            "options": [
                "capable",
                "unusual",
                "emotional"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mukammal tarzda",
            "RightAnswer": "perfectly",
            "options": [
                "elsewhere",
                "effectively",
                "truly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kuchaytirmoq, yaxshilamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "enhance",
            "options": [
                "borrow",
                "defend",
                "deserve"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "faxrlanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "proud",
            "options": [
                "presidential",
                "capable",
                "unusual"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "favqulodda vaziyat",
            "RightAnswer": "emergency",
            "options": [
                "soul",
                "interaction",
                "king"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta'limga oid",
            "RightAnswer": "educational",
            "options": [
                "proud",
                "presidential",
                "capable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "farqlamoq, ajrata olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "distinguish",
            "options": [
                "enhance",
                "borrow",
                "defend"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sezilarli, muhim",
            "RightAnswer": "substantial",
            "options": [
                "fundamental",
                "classic",
                "extreme"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaqin",
            "RightAnswer": "nearby",
            "options": [
                "lucky",
                "online",
                "weak"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishlab chiqaruvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "manufacturer",
            "options": [
                "emergency",
                "soul",
                "interaction"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sirpanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "slide",
            "options": [
                "defeat",
                "collapse",
                "repair"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qimmatli",
            "RightAnswer": "valuable",
            "options": [
                "substantial",
                "fundamental",
                "classic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shaxsan",
            "RightAnswer": "personally",
            "options": [
                "perfectly",
                "elsewhere",
                "effectively"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiyinchiliklarga bardosh bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "cope",
            "options": [
                "distinguish",
                "enhance",
                "borrow"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taxminan",
            "RightAnswer": "approximately",
            "options": [
                "personally",
                "perfectly",
                "elsewhere"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "joylashuv, turar joy",
            "RightAnswer": "accommodation",
            "options": [
                "manufacturer",
                "emergency",
                "soul"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ajratib ko'rsatmoq, urg'u bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "highlight",
            "options": [
                "slide",
                "defeat",
                "collapse"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sharxlovchi",
            "RightAnswer": "reporter",
            "options": [
                "accommodation",
                "manufacturer",
                "emergency"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "iqlim",
            "RightAnswer": "climate",
            "options": [
                "reporter",
                "accommodation",
                "manufacturer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'ylak",
            "RightAnswer": "shirt",
            "options": [
                "climate",
                "reporter",
                "accommodation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "istisno",
            "RightAnswer": "exception",
            "options": [
                "shirt",
                "climate",
                "reporter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "korporatsiya, kompaniya",
            "RightAnswer": "corporation",
            "options": [
                "exception",
                "shirt",
                "climate"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 39": [
        {
            "Question": "bo'lak",
            "RightAnswer": "chip",
            "options": [
                "dish",
                "pocket",
                "coat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "g'olib",
            "RightAnswer": "winner",
            "options": [
                "corporation",
                "exception",
                "shirt"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "duch kelmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "encounter",
            "options": [
                "highlight",
                "slide",
                "defeat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jigarrang",
            "RightAnswer": "brown",
            "options": [
                "valuable",
                "substantial",
                "fundamental"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nafas olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "breathe",
            "options": [
                "cope",
                "distinguish",
                "enhance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uzr, bahona",
            "RightAnswer": "excuse",
            "options": [
                "encounter",
                "highlight",
                "slide"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qisman",
            "RightAnswer": "partly",
            "options": [
                "approximately",
                "personally",
                "perfectly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tennis",
            "RightAnswer": "tennis",
            "options": [
                "winner",
                "corporation",
                "exception"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shahar bilan bog'liq",
            "RightAnswer": "urban",
            "options": [
                "brown",
                "valuable",
                "substantial"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chalkashtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "confuse",
            "options": [
                "breathe",
                "cope",
                "distinguish"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "janubiy",
            "RightAnswer": "southern",
            "options": [
                "odd",
                "north",
                "south"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chiqim, hosil",
            "RightAnswer": "output",
            "options": [
                "chip",
                "dish",
                "pocket"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "go'zallik",
            "RightAnswer": "beauty",
            "options": [
                "tennis",
                "winner",
                "corporation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ulkan, katta",
            "RightAnswer": "massive",
            "options": [
                "urban",
                "brown",
                "valuable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'rnatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "install",
            "options": [
                "confuse",
                "breathe",
                "cope"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hisoblamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "calculate",
            "options": [
                "install",
                "confuse",
                "breathe"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sichqon, sichqoncha",
            "RightAnswer": "mouse",
            "options": [
                "beauty",
                "tennis",
                "winner"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "matematika",
            "RightAnswer": "mathematics",
            "options": [
                "mouse",
                "beauty",
                "tennis"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yuqori",
            "RightAnswer": "upper",
            "options": [
                "southern",
                "odd",
                "north"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaratish, yaratilish",
            "RightAnswer": "creation",
            "options": [
                "mathematics",
                "mouse",
                "beauty"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "egallamoq, band qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "occupy",
            "options": [
                "calculate",
                "install",
                "confuse"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yuzaki tushuntirmoq, kontur",
            "RightAnswer": "outline",
            "options": [
                "excuse",
                "encounter",
                "highlight"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yetarli",
            "RightAnswer": "sufficient",
            "options": [
                "educational",
                "proud",
                "presidential"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yangilamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "update",
            "options": [
                "outline",
                "excuse",
                "encounter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "omad",
            "RightAnswer": "luck",
            "options": [
                "creation",
                "mathematics",
                "mouse"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "saqlamoq, himoya qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "preserve",
            "options": [
                "update",
                "outline",
                "excuse"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ajratmoq, bo'lishmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "split",
            "options": [
                "preserve",
                "update",
                "outline"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tebranmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "swing",
            "options": [
                "split",
                "preserve",
                "update"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kasallik",
            "RightAnswer": "illness",
            "options": [
                "luck",
                "creation",
                "mathematics"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jurnalist",
            "RightAnswer": "journalist",
            "options": [
                "illness",
                "luck",
                "creation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "birdaniga, kutilmaganda",
            "RightAnswer": "sudden",
            "options": [
                "upper",
                "southern",
                "odd"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "reklama",
            "RightAnswer": "advertisement",
            "options": [
                "journalist",
                "illness",
                "luck"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "izchil, muntazam",
            "RightAnswer": "consistent",
            "options": [
                "sufficient",
                "educational",
                "proud"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dastlab, aslida",
            "RightAnswer": "originally",
            "options": [
                "partly",
                "approximately",
                "personally"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yon taraf, chetga",
            "RightAnswer": "aside",
            "options": [
                "forth",
                "meanwhile",
                "less"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qulaylik, tasalli",
            "RightAnswer": "comfort",
            "options": [
                "output",
                "chip",
                "dish"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ikkinchi navbatda",
            "RightAnswer": "secondly",
            "options": [
                "originally",
                "partly",
                "approximately"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jiddiy, og'ir",
            "RightAnswer": "severe",
            "options": [
                "consistent",
                "sufficient",
                "educational"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "gen",
            "RightAnswer": "gene",
            "options": [
                "advertisement",
                "journalist",
                "illness"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "istiqbollar, kelajak",
            "RightAnswer": "prospect",
            "options": [
                "comfort",
                "output",
                "chip"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qor",
            "RightAnswer": "snow",
            "options": [
                "prospect",
                "comfort",
                "output"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "syujet, rejalashtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "plot",
            "options": [
                "snow",
                "prospect",
                "comfort"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bo'yin",
            "RightAnswer": "neck",
            "options": [
                "gene",
                "advertisement",
                "journalist"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "me'zon, talablar",
            "RightAnswer": "criteria",
            "options": [
                "thirst",
                "hunger",
                "noun"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asosan",
            "RightAnswer": "primarily",
            "options": [
                "secondly",
                "originally",
                "partly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "integratsiya qilmoq, birlashtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "integrate",
            "options": [
                "occupy",
                "calculate",
                "install"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanqid",
            "RightAnswer": "criticism",
            "options": [
                "neck",
                "gene",
                "advertisement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "anjuman, kelishuv",
            "RightAnswer": "convention",
            "options": [
                "criticism",
                "neck",
                "gene"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "pul tikmoq, garov",
            "RightAnswer": "bet",
            "options": [
                "swing",
                "split",
                "preserve"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "saqlab qolmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "retain",
            "options": [
                "integrate",
                "occupy",
                "calculate"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 40": [
        {
            "Question": "ketma-ketlik",
            "RightAnswer": "sequence",
            "options": [
                "convention",
                "criticism",
                "neck"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oddiy, tekis",
            "RightAnswer": "plain",
            "options": [
                "massive",
                "urban",
                "brown"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'ngilli",
            "RightAnswer": "volunteer",
            "options": [
                "bet",
                "swing",
                "split"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qishloq bilan bog'liq",
            "RightAnswer": "rural",
            "options": [
                "severe",
                "consistent",
                "sufficient"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tinch",
            "RightAnswer": "calm",
            "options": [
                "empty",
                "dry",
                "double"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tark etmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "abandon",
            "options": [
                "retain",
                "integrate",
                "occupy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "imtihon, tekshiruv",
            "RightAnswer": "examination",
            "options": [
                "sequence",
                "convention",
                "criticism"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jimlik",
            "RightAnswer": "silence",
            "options": [
                "plot",
                "snow",
                "prospect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tezda",
            "RightAnswer": "rapidly",
            "options": [
                "primarily",
                "secondly",
                "originally"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "samarali",
            "RightAnswer": "efficient",
            "options": [
                "rural",
                "severe",
                "consistent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "inqilob",
            "RightAnswer": "revolution",
            "options": [
                "examination",
                "sequence",
                "convention"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zavq, mamnuniyat",
            "RightAnswer": "delight",
            "options": [
                "silence",
                "plot",
                "snow"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sehr, imlo",
            "RightAnswer": "spell",
            "options": [
                "volunteer",
                "bet",
                "swing"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asosiy fikr, bosh g'oya",
            "RightAnswer": "premise",
            "options": [
                "revolution",
                "examination",
                "sequence"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "moyil bo'lmoq, cho'zilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "lean",
            "options": [
                "shut",
                "suspect",
                "select"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dramatik, hayajonli",
            "RightAnswer": "dramatic",
            "options": [
                "efficient",
                "rural",
                "severe"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "farqlanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "differ",
            "options": [
                "abandon",
                "retain",
                "integrate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "minnatdor",
            "RightAnswer": "grateful",
            "options": [
                "dramatic",
                "efficient",
                "rural"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oqsil",
            "RightAnswer": "protein",
            "options": [
                "premise",
                "revolution",
                "examination"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "velosiped",
            "RightAnswer": "bike",
            "options": [
                "delight",
                "silence",
                "plot"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taqsimlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "distribute",
            "options": [
                "differ",
                "abandon",
                "retain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aqliy",
            "RightAnswer": "intellectual",
            "options": [
                "plain",
                "massive",
                "urban"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kelib chiqmoq, olinmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "derive",
            "options": [
                "distribute",
                "differ",
                "abandon"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muhim, hal qiluvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "crucial",
            "options": [
                "grateful",
                "dramatic",
                "efficient"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishsizlik",
            "RightAnswer": "unemployment",
            "options": [
                "protein",
                "premise",
                "revolution"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "g'ildirak",
            "RightAnswer": "wheel",
            "options": [
                "unemployment",
                "protein",
                "premise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hosil, ekin",
            "RightAnswer": "crop",
            "options": [
                "bike",
                "delight",
                "silence"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ozchilik",
            "RightAnswer": "minority",
            "options": [
                "wheel",
                "unemployment",
                "protein"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kelib chiqish, asl manba",
            "RightAnswer": "origin",
            "options": [
                "minority",
                "wheel",
                "unemployment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "talqin, izoh",
            "RightAnswer": "interpretation",
            "options": [
                "origin",
                "minority",
                "wheel"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "janob, hurmatli erkak",
            "RightAnswer": "gentleman",
            "options": [
                "interpretation",
                "origin",
                "minority"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "drama, sahna san'ati",
            "RightAnswer": "drama",
            "options": [
                "gentleman",
                "interpretation",
                "origin"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "landshaft, manzara",
            "RightAnswer": "landscape",
            "options": [
                "drama",
                "gentleman",
                "interpretation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta'lim berish, o'rgatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "educate",
            "options": [
                "derive",
                "distribute",
                "differ"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'yinchoq",
            "RightAnswer": "toy",
            "options": [
                "crop",
                "bike",
                "delight"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xato, nuqson",
            "RightAnswer": "fault",
            "options": [
                "toy",
                "crop",
                "bike"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'rsatmoq, namoyish qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "exhibit",
            "options": [
                "spell",
                "volunteer",
                "bet"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kichik, muhim bo'lmagan",
            "RightAnswer": "minor",
            "options": [
                "intellectual",
                "plain",
                "massive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ovlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "hunt",
            "options": [
                "exhibit",
                "spell",
                "volunteer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bo'ron",
            "RightAnswer": "storm",
            "options": [
                "fault",
                "toy",
                "crop"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qalin",
            "RightAnswer": "thick",
            "options": [
                "nearby",
                "lucky",
                "online"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yutuq, erishuv",
            "RightAnswer": "achievement",
            "options": [
                "landscape",
                "drama",
                "gentleman"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muzokara qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "negotiate",
            "options": [
                "educate",
                "derive",
                "distribute"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hukmronlik qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "dominate",
            "options": [
                "negotiate",
                "educate",
                "derive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta'minotchi",
            "RightAnswer": "supplier",
            "options": [
                "achievement",
                "landscape",
                "drama"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mukofot",
            "RightAnswer": "prize",
            "options": [
                "storm",
                "fault",
                "toy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "odatda",
            "RightAnswer": "typically",
            "options": [
                "rapidly",
                "primarily",
                "secondly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tengdosh",
            "RightAnswer": "peer",
            "options": [
                "prize",
                "storm",
                "fault"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "pensiya, nafaqa",
            "RightAnswer": "pension",
            "options": [
                "supplier",
                "achievement",
                "landscape"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qanot",
            "RightAnswer": "wing",
            "options": [
                "peer",
                "prize",
                "storm"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 41": [
        {
            "Question": "egallash, sotib olish",
            "RightAnswer": "acquisition",
            "options": [
                "pension",
                "supplier",
                "achievement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kulgu",
            "RightAnswer": "laughter",
            "options": [
                "acquisition",
                "pension",
                "supplier"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chuqur",
            "RightAnswer": "deeply",
            "options": [
                "typically",
                "rapidly",
                "primarily"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tan olmoq, e'tirof",
            "RightAnswer": "recognition",
            "options": [
                "laughter",
                "acquisition",
                "pension"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "elektr",
            "RightAnswer": "electricity",
            "options": [
                "recognition",
                "laughter",
                "acquisition"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yordam",
            "RightAnswer": "assistance",
            "options": [
                "electricity",
                "recognition",
                "laughter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tom",
            "RightAnswer": "roof",
            "options": [
                "assistance",
                "electricity",
                "recognition"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nafaqaga chiqish",
            "RightAnswer": "retirement",
            "options": [
                "roof",
                "assistance",
                "electricity"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mos ravishda",
            "RightAnswer": "respectively",
            "options": [
                "deeply",
                "typically",
                "rapidly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'zgarish, farq",
            "RightAnswer": "variation",
            "options": [
                "retirement",
                "roof",
                "assistance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nihoyat",
            "RightAnswer": "ultimately",
            "options": [
                "respectively",
                "deeply",
                "typically"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dalil, isbot",
            "RightAnswer": "proof",
            "options": [
                "maximum",
                "minimum",
                "household"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tuproq",
            "RightAnswer": "soil",
            "options": [
                "wing",
                "peer",
                "prize"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aqlli, aqlli ko'rinish",
            "RightAnswer": "smart",
            "options": [
                "secure",
                "perfect",
                "correct"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qatlam",
            "RightAnswer": "layer",
            "options": [
                "soil",
                "wing",
                "peer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "g'azablangan, qayg'u",
            "RightAnswer": "upset",
            "options": [
                "hurt",
                "grin",
                "cough"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tish",
            "RightAnswer": "tooth",
            "options": [
                "variation",
                "retirement",
                "roof"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vakillik, namoyon etish",
            "RightAnswer": "representation",
            "options": [
                "tooth",
                "variation",
                "retirement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tayyorgarlik",
            "RightAnswer": "preparation",
            "options": [
                "representation",
                "tooth",
                "variation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bahs, nizolar",
            "RightAnswer": "dispute",
            "options": [
                "layer",
                "soil",
                "wing"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kun tartibi",
            "RightAnswer": "agenda",
            "options": [
                "preparation",
                "representation",
                "tooth"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "urg'u, ta'kidlash",
            "RightAnswer": "emphasis",
            "options": [
                "agenda",
                "preparation",
                "representation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nashr, adad",
            "RightAnswer": "edition",
            "options": [
                "emphasis",
                "agenda",
                "preparation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kumush",
            "RightAnswer": "silver",
            "options": [
                "proof",
                "maximum",
                "minimum"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'ngilochar mashg'ulot",
            "RightAnswer": "entertainment",
            "options": [
                "edition",
                "emphasis",
                "agenda"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "halol, rostgo'y",
            "RightAnswer": "honest",
            "options": [
                "crucial",
                "grateful",
                "dramatic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshlamoq, qo'lga kiritmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "undertake",
            "options": [
                "dominate",
                "negotiate",
                "educate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chakana savdo",
            "RightAnswer": "retail",
            "options": [
                "silver",
                "proof",
                "maximum"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sim",
            "RightAnswer": "wire",
            "options": [
                "dispute",
                "layer",
                "soil"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ehtimoldan yiroq",
            "RightAnswer": "unlikely",
            "options": [
                "honest",
                "crucial",
                "grateful"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nashr, e'lon",
            "RightAnswer": "publication",
            "options": [
                "entertainment",
                "edition",
                "emphasis"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "biroz",
            "RightAnswer": "slight",
            "options": [
                "prime",
                "sweet",
                "sick"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "noma'lum",
            "RightAnswer": "unknown",
            "options": [
                "minor",
                "intellectual",
                "plain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asos, tuzilma",
            "RightAnswer": "framework",
            "options": [
                "publication",
                "entertainment",
                "edition"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zona, hudud",
            "RightAnswer": "zone",
            "options": [
                "framework",
                "publication",
                "entertainment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "cheklamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "restrict",
            "options": [
                "undertake",
                "dominate",
                "negotiate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "iz, izlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "trace",
            "options": [
                "wire",
                "dispute",
                "layer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dyum",
            "RightAnswer": "inch",
            "options": [
                "trace",
                "wire",
                "dispute"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "teng ekvivalent",
            "RightAnswer": "equivalent",
            "options": [
                "retail",
                "silver",
                "proof"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mustahkam, qattiq",
            "RightAnswer": "solid",
            "options": [
                "slight",
                "prime",
                "sweet"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "korxona, biznes",
            "RightAnswer": "enterprise",
            "options": [
                "zone",
                "framework",
                "publication"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "keksa",
            "RightAnswer": "elderly",
            "options": [
                "unknown",
                "minor",
                "intellectual"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qarz olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "owe",
            "options": [
                "restrict",
                "undertake",
                "dominate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "gubernator, hokim",
            "RightAnswer": "governor",
            "options": [
                "enterprise",
                "zone",
                "framework"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bir xil, uniforma",
            "RightAnswer": "uniform",
            "options": [
                "elderly",
                "unknown",
                "minor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bandargoh",
            "RightAnswer": "port",
            "options": [
                "inch",
                "trace",
                "wire"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mum, ovoz kuchi, maydon",
            "RightAnswer": "pitch",
            "options": [
                "port",
                "inch",
                "trace"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yetib kelish",
            "RightAnswer": "arrival",
            "options": [
                "governor",
                "enterprise",
                "zone"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zamonaviy, hozirgi davrga oid",
            "RightAnswer": "contemporary",
            "options": [
                "uniform",
                "elderly",
                "unknown"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "darvoza, eshik",
            "RightAnswer": "gate",
            "options": [
                "arrival",
                "governor",
                "enterprise"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 42": [
        {
            "Question": "yengillik, qulaylik",
            "RightAnswer": "ease",
            "options": [
                "pitch",
                "port",
                "inch"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "pivo",
            "RightAnswer": "beer",
            "options": [
                "gate",
                "arrival",
                "governor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mutaxassis",
            "RightAnswer": "specialist",
            "options": [
                "beer",
                "gate",
                "arrival"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishonch bermoq, kafolatlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "assure",
            "options": [
                "owe",
                "restrict",
                "undertake"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "profil, tavsif",
            "RightAnswer": "profile",
            "options": [
                "ease",
                "pitch",
                "port"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kayfiyat, holat",
            "RightAnswer": "mood",
            "options": [
                "specialist",
                "beer",
                "gate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "epizod, voqea",
            "RightAnswer": "episode",
            "options": [
                "mood",
                "specialist",
                "beer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yoriq",
            "RightAnswer": "crack",
            "options": [
                "hunt",
                "exhibit",
                "spell"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'p",
            "RightAnswer": "numerous",
            "options": [
                "unlikely",
                "honest",
                "crucial"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "topshirmoq, qabul qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "submit",
            "options": [
                "assure",
                "owe",
                "restrict"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "alomat, belgi",
            "RightAnswer": "symptom",
            "options": [
                "episode",
                "mood",
                "specialist"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "deyarli, amalda",
            "RightAnswer": "virtually",
            "options": [
                "ultimately",
                "respectively",
                "deeply"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "davr, asr",
            "RightAnswer": "era",
            "options": [
                "symptom",
                "episode",
                "mood"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qamrab olmoq, yoritish",
            "RightAnswer": "coverage",
            "options": [
                "era",
                "symptom",
                "episode"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "siqilish, taranglik",
            "RightAnswer": "tension",
            "options": [
                "coverage",
                "era",
                "symptom"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kabel, sim",
            "RightAnswer": "cable",
            "options": [
                "tension",
                "coverage",
                "era"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tasirchan",
            "RightAnswer": "sensitive",
            "options": [
                "numerous",
                "unlikely",
                "honest"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asabiy",
            "RightAnswer": "nervous",
            "options": [
                "sensitive",
                "numerous",
                "unlikely"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kirish, ma'lumot",
            "RightAnswer": "input",
            "options": [
                "profile",
                "ease",
                "pitch"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ajratmoq, izolyatsiya qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "isolate",
            "options": [
                "submit",
                "assure",
                "owe"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maxbus",
            "RightAnswer": "prisoner",
            "options": [
                "cable",
                "tension",
                "coverage"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yo'qotmoq, bartaraf etmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "eliminate",
            "options": [
                "isolate",
                "submit",
                "assure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tor, qattiq",
            "RightAnswer": "tight",
            "options": [
                "wild",
                "quiet",
                "slow"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ho'l",
            "RightAnswer": "wet",
            "options": [
                "calm",
                "empty",
                "dry"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ikkinchi, qo'shimcha",
            "RightAnswer": "secondary",
            "options": [
                "contemporary",
                "uniform",
                "elderly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "farovonlik, ijtimoiy ko'mak",
            "RightAnswer": "welfare",
            "options": [
                "prisoner",
                "cable",
                "tension"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishga qabul qilmoq, ro'yxatdan o'tmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "recruit",
            "options": [
                "crack",
                "hunt",
                "exhibit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kiritmaslik, chiqarib tashlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "exclude",
            "options": [
                "eliminate",
                "isolate",
                "submit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ip",
            "RightAnswer": "string",
            "options": [
                "input",
                "profile",
                "ease"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bulut",
            "RightAnswer": "cloud",
            "options": [
                "string",
                "input",
                "profile"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishontirmoq, rag'batlantirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "persuade",
            "options": [
                "exclude",
                "eliminate",
                "isolate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ilhomlantirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "inspire",
            "options": [
                "persuade",
                "exclude",
                "eliminate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "katta, ajoyib",
            "RightAnswer": "grand",
            "options": [
                "secondary",
                "contemporary",
                "uniform"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shuning uchun",
            "RightAnswer": "hence",
            "options": [
                "otherwise",
                "yet",
                "once"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ekipaj, jamoa",
            "RightAnswer": "crew",
            "options": [
                "cloud",
                "string",
                "input"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hodisa, voqea",
            "RightAnswer": "phenomenon",
            "options": [
                "welfare",
                "prisoner",
                "cable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'quvchi, qorachiq",
            "RightAnswer": "pupil",
            "options": [
                "phenomenon",
                "welfare",
                "prisoner"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "notoâ€™gâ€™ri, sohta",
            "RightAnswer": "false",
            "options": [
                "grand",
                "secondary",
                "contemporary"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yordam bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "assist",
            "options": [
                "inspire",
                "persuade",
                "exclude"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tiklamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "restore",
            "options": [
                "assist",
                "inspire",
                "persuade"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "formula",
            "RightAnswer": "formula",
            "options": [
                "pupil",
                "phenomenon",
                "welfare"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'zgartirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "alter",
            "options": [
                "elect",
                "express",
                "close"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sezmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "perceive",
            "options": [
                "restore",
                "assist",
                "inspire"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kundalik tartib",
            "RightAnswer": "routine",
            "options": [
                "equivalent",
                "retail",
                "silver"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ho'l yuvish idishi",
            "RightAnswer": "sink",
            "options": [
                "recruit",
                "crack",
                "hunt"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qaramoq",
            "RightAnswer": "stare",
            "options": [
                "sink",
                "recruit",
                "crack"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "endi",
            "RightAnswer": "anymore",
            "options": [
                "anywhere",
                "there",
                "instead"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qahramon",
            "RightAnswer": "hero",
            "options": [
                "formula",
                "pupil",
                "phenomenon"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'llab-quvvatlovchi",
            "RightAnswer": "supporter",
            "options": [
                "hero",
                "formula",
                "pupil"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aylantirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "convert",
            "options": [
                "stare",
                "sink",
                "recruit"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 43": [
        {
            "Question": "barqaror",
            "RightAnswer": "steady",
            "options": [
                "smart",
                "secure",
                "perfect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "metr",
            "RightAnswer": "meter",
            "options": [
                "supporter",
                "hero",
                "formula"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yuk mashinasi",
            "RightAnswer": "truck",
            "options": [
                "crew",
                "cloud",
                "string"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "burun",
            "RightAnswer": "nose",
            "options": [
                "truck",
                "crew",
                "cloud"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yonida",
            "RightAnswer": "beside",
            "options": [
                "besides",
                "throughout",
                "beyond"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qayiq yelkasi",
            "RightAnswer": "sail",
            "options": [
                "convert",
                "stare",
                "sink"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "falokat",
            "RightAnswer": "disaster",
            "options": [
                "meter",
                "supporter",
                "hero"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tezlik",
            "RightAnswer": "pace",
            "options": [
                "nose",
                "truck",
                "crew"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "og'irlik bilan",
            "RightAnswer": "heavily",
            "options": [
                "virtually",
                "ultimately",
                "respectively"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bag'ishlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "devote",
            "options": [
                "perceive",
                "restore",
                "assist"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "terrorchi",
            "RightAnswer": "terrorist",
            "options": [
                "disaster",
                "meter",
                "supporter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asoslamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "justify",
            "options": [
                "devote",
                "perceive",
                "restore"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zaruriy",
            "RightAnswer": "vital",
            "options": [
                "false",
                "grand",
                "secondary"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hayratlantirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "fascinate",
            "options": [
                "justify",
                "devote",
                "perceive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashqi",
            "RightAnswer": "external",
            "options": [
                "nervous",
                "sensitive",
                "numerous"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ortiqcha",
            "RightAnswer": "spare",
            "options": [
                "wet",
                "calm",
                "empty"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qachonki",
            "RightAnswer": "whenever",
            "options": [
                "nevertheless",
                "therefore",
                "though"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "depressiya",
            "RightAnswer": "depression",
            "options": [
                "terrorist",
                "disaster",
                "meter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aybdor",
            "RightAnswer": "guilty",
            "options": [
                "external",
                "nervous",
                "sensitive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "poydevor bo'lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "underlie",
            "options": [
                "fascinate",
                "justify",
                "devote"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ona",
            "RightAnswer": "mom",
            "options": [
                "depression",
                "terrorist",
                "disaster"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "farq",
            "RightAnswer": "distinction",
            "options": [
                "mom",
                "depression",
                "terrorist"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qoniqish",
            "RightAnswer": "satisfaction",
            "options": [
                "distinction",
                "mom",
                "depression"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "birlashtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "incorporate",
            "options": [
                "underlie",
                "fascinate",
                "justify"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'kmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "pour",
            "options": [
                "sail",
                "convert",
                "stare"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chang yutmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "sweep",
            "options": [
                "pour",
                "sail",
                "convert"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "majburiyat",
            "RightAnswer": "obligation",
            "options": [
                "satisfaction",
                "distinction",
                "mom"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "janob",
            "RightAnswer": "sir",
            "options": [
                "outside",
                "tonight",
                "tomorrow"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "baholamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "evaluate",
            "options": [
                "incorporate",
                "underlie",
                "fascinate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "g'azab",
            "RightAnswer": "anger",
            "options": [
                "obligation",
                "satisfaction",
                "distinction"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qovoqxona",
            "RightAnswer": "pub",
            "options": [
                "anger",
                "obligation",
                "satisfaction"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qabul qilish",
            "RightAnswer": "perception",
            "options": [
                "pub",
                "anger",
                "obligation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tabiiy ravishda",
            "RightAnswer": "naturally",
            "options": [
                "heavily",
                "virtually",
                "ultimately"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "valuta",
            "RightAnswer": "currency",
            "options": [
                "perception",
                "pub",
                "anger"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ma'lumotlar bazasi",
            "RightAnswer": "database",
            "options": [
                "currency",
                "perception",
                "pub"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dastlab",
            "RightAnswer": "initially",
            "options": [
                "naturally",
                "heavily",
                "virtually"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hudud",
            "RightAnswer": "territory",
            "options": [
                "database",
                "currency",
                "perception"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "daryo",
            "RightAnswer": "stream",
            "options": [
                "pace",
                "nose",
                "truck"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kamdan-kam",
            "RightAnswer": "rarely",
            "options": [
                "initially",
                "naturally",
                "heavily"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "balandlik",
            "RightAnswer": "height",
            "options": [
                "territory",
                "database",
                "currency"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ravshan",
            "RightAnswer": "apparent",
            "options": [
                "guilty",
                "external",
                "nervous"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "g'arbiy",
            "RightAnswer": "western",
            "options": [
                "sudden",
                "upper",
                "southern"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kengayish",
            "RightAnswer": "expansion",
            "options": [
                "height",
                "territory",
                "database"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "doimo",
            "RightAnswer": "constantly",
            "options": [
                "rarely",
                "initially",
                "naturally"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mushak",
            "RightAnswer": "muscle",
            "options": [
                "expansion",
                "height",
                "territory"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'rqitmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "scare",
            "options": [
                "sweep",
                "pour",
                "sail"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yomon",
            "RightAnswer": "badly",
            "options": [
                "abroad",
                "apart",
                "ahead"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kundalik",
            "RightAnswer": "everyday",
            "options": [
                "vital",
                "false",
                "grand"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chegara",
            "RightAnswer": "boundary",
            "options": [
                "muscle",
                "expansion",
                "height"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nisbat",
            "RightAnswer": "ratio",
            "options": [
                "boundary",
                "muscle",
                "expansion"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 44": [
        {
            "Question": "insho",
            "RightAnswer": "essay",
            "options": [
                "stream",
                "pace",
                "nose"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "baqirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "scream",
            "options": [
                "scare",
                "sweep",
                "pour"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chekinmoq, chiqarib olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "withdraw",
            "options": [
                "evaluate",
                "incorporate",
                "underlie"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ifloslanish",
            "RightAnswer": "pollution",
            "options": [
                "ratio",
                "boundary",
                "muscle"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tartibsizlik",
            "RightAnswer": "disorder",
            "options": [
                "essay",
                "stream",
                "pace"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mebel",
            "RightAnswer": "furniture",
            "options": [
                "pollution",
                "ratio",
                "boundary"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ramz",
            "RightAnswer": "symbol",
            "options": [
                "furniture",
                "pollution",
                "ratio"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kvartira",
            "RightAnswer": "apartment",
            "options": [
                "symbol",
                "furniture",
                "pollution"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "namoyish",
            "RightAnswer": "demonstration",
            "options": [
                "apartment",
                "symbol",
                "furniture"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tahlilchi",
            "RightAnswer": "analyst",
            "options": [
                "demonstration",
                "apartment",
                "symbol"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "platforma",
            "RightAnswer": "platform",
            "options": [
                "analyst",
                "demonstration",
                "apartment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "po'lat",
            "RightAnswer": "steel",
            "options": [
                "disorder",
                "essay",
                "stream"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tort",
            "RightAnswer": "cake",
            "options": [
                "steel",
                "disorder",
                "essay"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'zgartirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "transform",
            "options": [
                "withdraw",
                "evaluate",
                "incorporate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yara, jarohat",
            "RightAnswer": "wound",
            "options": [
                "cake",
                "steel",
                "disorder"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "cheklov",
            "RightAnswer": "restriction",
            "options": [
                "platform",
                "analyst",
                "demonstration"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "poydevor",
            "RightAnswer": "foundation",
            "options": [
                "restriction",
                "platform",
                "analyst"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dizayner",
            "RightAnswer": "designer",
            "options": [
                "foundation",
                "restriction",
                "platform"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taranglik, bosim",
            "RightAnswer": "strain",
            "options": [
                "wound",
                "cake",
                "steel"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "innovatsiya",
            "RightAnswer": "innovation",
            "options": [
                "designer",
                "foundation",
                "restriction"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "albom",
            "RightAnswer": "album",
            "options": [
                "innovation",
                "designer",
                "foundation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'shiqchi",
            "RightAnswer": "singer",
            "options": [
                "album",
                "innovation",
                "designer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "iz",
            "RightAnswer": "trail",
            "options": [
                "strain",
                "wound",
                "cake"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tuzoq",
            "RightAnswer": "trap",
            "options": [
                "trail",
                "strain",
                "wound"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bo'sh, tarang emas",
            "RightAnswer": "loose",
            "options": [
                "steady",
                "smart",
                "secure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kengayish, kattalashish",
            "RightAnswer": "extension",
            "options": [
                "singer",
                "album",
                "innovation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boylik",
            "RightAnswer": "wealth",
            "options": [
                "extension",
                "singer",
                "album"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asta-sekin",
            "RightAnswer": "gradually",
            "options": [
                "constantly",
                "rarely",
                "initially"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yoqilg'i baki",
            "RightAnswer": "tank",
            "options": [
                "trap",
                "trail",
                "strain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yomon, yovuz",
            "RightAnswer": "evil",
            "options": [
                "everyday",
                "vital",
                "false"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ajoyib, e'tiborga molik",
            "RightAnswer": "remarkable",
            "options": [
                "apparent",
                "guilty",
                "external"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ohang",
            "RightAnswer": "tune",
            "options": [
                "tank",
                "trap",
                "trail"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o't",
            "RightAnswer": "grass",
            "options": [
                "tune",
                "tank",
                "trap"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taklif, taklifnoma",
            "RightAnswer": "invitation",
            "options": [
                "wealth",
                "extension",
                "singer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'tish",
            "RightAnswer": "transition",
            "options": [
                "grass",
                "tune",
                "tank"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'rqitmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "frighten",
            "options": [
                "transform",
                "withdraw",
                "evaluate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taklif",
            "RightAnswer": "bid",
            "options": [
                "scream",
                "scare",
                "sweep"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yetishtirmoq, zot",
            "RightAnswer": "breed",
            "options": [
                "bid",
                "scream",
                "scare"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "noodatiy",
            "RightAnswer": "extraordinary",
            "options": [
                "remarkable",
                "apparent",
                "guilty"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ajoyib",
            "RightAnswer": "brilliant",
            "options": [
                "extraordinary",
                "remarkable",
                "apparent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maslahatchi",
            "RightAnswer": "adviser",
            "options": [
                "invitation",
                "wealth",
                "extension"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tayoq, poya",
            "RightAnswer": "stem",
            "options": [
                "transition",
                "grass",
                "tune"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "teskari",
            "RightAnswer": "reverse",
            "options": [
                "upset",
                "hurt",
                "grin"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rejim",
            "RightAnswer": "mode",
            "options": [
                "stem",
                "transition",
                "grass"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oyna",
            "RightAnswer": "mirror",
            "options": [
                "mode",
                "stem",
                "transition"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dahshatli, juda yomon",
            "RightAnswer": "awful",
            "options": [
                "brilliant",
                "extraordinary",
                "remarkable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "poza, holat",
            "RightAnswer": "pose",
            "options": [
                "breed",
                "bid",
                "scream"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "moslashtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "adjust",
            "options": [
                "frighten",
                "transform",
                "withdraw"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ijodiy",
            "RightAnswer": "creative",
            "options": [
                "awful",
                "brilliant",
                "extraordinary"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hozirgi kunda",
            "RightAnswer": "nowadays",
            "options": [
                "aside",
                "forth",
                "meanwhile"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 45": [
        {
            "Question": "she'r",
            "RightAnswer": "poem",
            "options": [
                "adviser",
                "invitation",
                "wealth"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qishloq xo'jaligiga oid",
            "RightAnswer": "agricultural",
            "options": [
                "creative",
                "awful",
                "brilliant"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "raqobatchi",
            "RightAnswer": "competitor",
            "options": [
                "poem",
                "adviser",
                "invitation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "alkogol",
            "RightAnswer": "alcohol",
            "options": [
                "competitor",
                "poem",
                "adviser"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "festival",
            "RightAnswer": "festival",
            "options": [
                "alcohol",
                "competitor",
                "poem"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sabzavot",
            "RightAnswer": "vegetable",
            "options": [
                "festival",
                "alcohol",
                "competitor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "furgon",
            "RightAnswer": "van",
            "options": [
                "vegetable",
                "festival",
                "alcohol"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dadil, o'ziga ishongan",
            "RightAnswer": "confident",
            "options": [
                "agricultural",
                "creative",
                "awful"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sayyora",
            "RightAnswer": "planet",
            "options": [
                "van",
                "vegetable",
                "festival"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "burilmoq, qayrilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "curve",
            "options": [
                "mirror",
                "mode",
                "stem"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tizza",
            "RightAnswer": "knee",
            "options": [
                "planet",
                "van",
                "vegetable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yengib o'tmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "overcome",
            "options": [
                "adjust",
                "frighten",
                "transform"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'r",
            "RightAnswer": "web",
            "options": [
                "curve",
                "mirror",
                "mode"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chuqurlik",
            "RightAnswer": "depth",
            "options": [
                "knee",
                "planet",
                "van"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kirish",
            "RightAnswer": "entrance",
            "options": [
                "web",
                "curve",
                "mirror"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yozib bormoq, xoda",
            "RightAnswer": "log",
            "options": [
                "entrance",
                "web",
                "curve"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ulkan",
            "RightAnswer": "giant",
            "options": [
                "evil",
                "everyday",
                "vital"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xudo",
            "RightAnswer": "god",
            "options": [
                "depth",
                "knee",
                "planet"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qism",
            "RightAnswer": "portion",
            "options": [
                "god",
                "depth",
                "knee"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "modda",
            "RightAnswer": "substance",
            "options": [
                "portion",
                "god",
                "depth"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "keng",
            "RightAnswer": "extensive",
            "options": [
                "confident",
                "agricultural",
                "creative"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "talqin qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "interpret",
            "options": [
                "overcome",
                "adjust",
                "frighten"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mustaqillik",
            "RightAnswer": "independence",
            "options": [
                "substance",
                "portion",
                "god"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shakar",
            "RightAnswer": "sugar",
            "options": [
                "independence",
                "substance",
                "portion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ichki",
            "RightAnswer": "inner",
            "options": [
                "giant",
                "evil",
                "everyday"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zarar",
            "RightAnswer": "harm",
            "options": [
                "log",
                "entrance",
                "web"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maslahat qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "consult",
            "options": [
                "pose",
                "breed",
                "bid"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "pushti",
            "RightAnswer": "pink",
            "options": [
                "inner",
                "giant",
                "evil"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "soya",
            "RightAnswer": "shadow",
            "options": [
                "harm",
                "log",
                "entrance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "lenta",
            "RightAnswer": "strip",
            "options": [
                "consult",
                "pose",
                "breed"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "silliq",
            "RightAnswer": "smooth",
            "options": [
                "loose",
                "steady",
                "smart"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aralashuv",
            "RightAnswer": "intervention",
            "options": [
                "sugar",
                "independence",
                "substance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taassurot qoldirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "impress",
            "options": [
                "interpret",
                "overcome",
                "adjust"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "imtihon",
            "RightAnswer": "exam",
            "options": [
                "intervention",
                "sugar",
                "independence"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "illat",
            "RightAnswer": "vice",
            "options": [
                "exam",
                "intervention",
                "sugar"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "keskin",
            "RightAnswer": "radical",
            "options": [
                "pink",
                "inner",
                "giant"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shunga o'xshab, shu tarzda",
            "RightAnswer": "similarly",
            "options": [
                "gradually",
                "constantly",
                "rarely"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'zini tutmoq, ",
            "RightAnswer": "behave",
            "options": [
                "impress",
                "interpret",
                "overcome"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "baland",
            "RightAnswer": "loud",
            "options": [
                "thick",
                "nearby",
                "lucky"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'lcham",
            "RightAnswer": "dimension",
            "options": [
                "vice",
                "exam",
                "intervention"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "keyingi",
            "RightAnswer": "subsequent",
            "options": [
                "extensive",
                "confident",
                "agricultural"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "infektsiya",
            "RightAnswer": "infection",
            "options": [
                "dimension",
                "vice",
                "exam"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kurtka",
            "RightAnswer": "jacket",
            "options": [
                "infection",
                "dimension",
                "vice"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "samaradorlik",
            "RightAnswer": "efficiency",
            "options": [
                "jacket",
                "infection",
                "dimension"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "iflos",
            "RightAnswer": "dirty",
            "options": [
                "smooth",
                "loose",
                "steady"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "statistika",
            "RightAnswer": "statistic",
            "options": [
                "efficiency",
                "jacket",
                "infection"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muntazam ravishda",
            "RightAnswer": "regularly",
            "options": [
                "similarly",
                "gradually",
                "constantly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kurort, yechim",
            "RightAnswer": "resort",
            "options": [
                "strip",
                "consult",
                "pose"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "temir",
            "RightAnswer": "iron",
            "options": [
                "shadow",
                "harm",
                "log"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "efirga uzatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "broadcast",
            "options": [
                "resort",
                "strip",
                "consult"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 46": [
        {
            "Question": "a'zolik",
            "RightAnswer": "membership",
            "options": [
                "statistic",
                "efficiency",
                "jacket"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "non",
            "RightAnswer": "bread",
            "options": [
                "membership",
                "statistic",
                "efficiency"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'zi ojiz",
            "RightAnswer": "blind",
            "options": [
                "spare",
                "wet",
                "calm"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sof",
            "RightAnswer": "pure",
            "options": [
                "subsequent",
                "extensive",
                "confident"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qonli",
            "RightAnswer": "bloody",
            "options": [
                "loud",
                "thick",
                "nearby"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ittifoqchi",
            "RightAnswer": "ally",
            "options": [
                "iron",
                "shadow",
                "harm"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "miqdor",
            "RightAnswer": "quantity",
            "options": [
                "bread",
                "membership",
                "statistic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "egilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "bend",
            "options": [
                "broadcast",
                "resort",
                "strip"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "pishgan",
            "RightAnswer": "mature",
            "options": [
                "alter",
                "elect",
                "express"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qisqacha",
            "RightAnswer": "briefly",
            "options": [
                "regularly",
                "similarly",
                "gradually"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "signal, ogohlantirish",
            "RightAnswer": "alarm",
            "options": [
                "ally",
                "iron",
                "shadow"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bezovta qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "disturb",
            "options": [
                "behave",
                "impress",
                "interpret"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "saqlab turmoq, ",
            "RightAnswer": "sustain",
            "options": [
                "disturb",
                "behave",
                "impress"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "toshqin",
            "RightAnswer": "flood",
            "options": [
                "alarm",
                "ally",
                "iron"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kambag'allik",
            "RightAnswer": "poverty",
            "options": [
                "quantity",
                "bread",
                "membership"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aqldan ozgan",
            "RightAnswer": "crazy",
            "options": [
                "pure",
                "subsequent",
                "extensive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "iqtibos keltirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "cite",
            "options": [
                "sustain",
                "disturb",
                "behave"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yangicha",
            "RightAnswer": "newly",
            "options": [
                "briefly",
                "regularly",
                "similarly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "parallel",
            "RightAnswer": "parallel",
            "options": [
                "solid",
                "slight",
                "prime"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jins",
            "RightAnswer": "gender",
            "options": [
                "poverty",
                "quantity",
                "bread"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "homiy",
            "RightAnswer": "sponsor",
            "options": [
                "flood",
                "alarm",
                "ally"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "etik",
            "RightAnswer": "boots",
            "options": [
                "sponsor",
                "flood",
                "alarm"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aniq",
            "RightAnswer": "accurate",
            "options": [
                "crazy",
                "pure",
                "subsequent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sotuvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "dealer",
            "options": [
                "gender",
                "poverty",
                "quantity"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tugma",
            "RightAnswer": "button",
            "options": [
                "boots",
                "sponsor",
                "flood"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yuk",
            "RightAnswer": "burden",
            "options": [
                "button",
                "boots",
                "sponsor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "cho'l",
            "RightAnswer": "desert",
            "options": [
                "burden",
                "button",
                "boots"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sherik, oshno",
            "RightAnswer": "mate",
            "options": [
                "bend",
                "broadcast",
                "resort"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ba'zida",
            "RightAnswer": "occasionally",
            "options": [
                "newly",
                "briefly",
                "regularly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aktsiyador",
            "RightAnswer": "shareholder",
            "options": [
                "dealer",
                "gender",
                "poverty"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kosa",
            "RightAnswer": "bowl",
            "options": [
                "desert",
                "burden",
                "button"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kashfiyot",
            "RightAnswer": "discovery",
            "options": [
                "shareholder",
                "dealer",
                "gender"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qarshilik",
            "RightAnswer": "resistance",
            "options": [
                "discovery",
                "shareholder",
                "dealer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vanna",
            "RightAnswer": "bath",
            "options": [
                "bowl",
                "desert",
                "burden"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chastota",
            "RightAnswer": "frequency",
            "options": [
                "resistance",
                "discovery",
                "shareholder"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanqid qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "criticize",
            "options": [
                "cite",
                "sustain",
                "disturb"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jumrak, tappilatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "tap",
            "options": [
                "mate",
                "bend",
                "broadcast"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "falsafa",
            "RightAnswer": "philosophy",
            "options": [
                "frequency",
                "resistance",
                "discovery"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "lab",
            "RightAnswer": "lip",
            "options": [
                "philosophy",
                "frequency",
                "resistance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xususiyat",
            "RightAnswer": "attribute",
            "options": [
                "tap",
                "mate",
                "bend"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uzr so'ramoq",
            "RightAnswer": "apologize",
            "options": [
                "criticize",
                "cite",
                "sustain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tasdiqlash",
            "RightAnswer": "approval",
            "options": [
                "lip",
                "philosophy",
                "frequency"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ushlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "grab",
            "options": [
                "attribute",
                "tap",
                "mate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ruxsat bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "entitle",
            "options": [
                "apologize",
                "criticize",
                "cite"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qarz bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "lend",
            "options": [
                "entitle",
                "apologize",
                "criticize"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishtirok",
            "RightAnswer": "involvement",
            "options": [
                "approval",
                "lip",
                "philosophy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "namoyish",
            "RightAnswer": "exposure",
            "options": [
                "involvement",
                "approval",
                "lip"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "an'anaviy",
            "RightAnswer": "conventional",
            "options": [
                "accurate",
                "crazy",
                "pure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "raqamli",
            "RightAnswer": "digital",
            "options": [
                "conventional",
                "accurate",
                "crazy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tarjima qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "translate",
            "options": [
                "lend",
                "entitle",
                "apologize"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 47": [
        {
            "Question": "tahrir qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "edit",
            "options": [
                "grab",
                "attribute",
                "tap"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shakllanish",
            "RightAnswer": "formation",
            "options": [
                "exposure",
                "involvement",
                "approval"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "omonat",
            "RightAnswer": "deposit",
            "options": [
                "edit",
                "grab",
                "attribute"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yoqimli",
            "RightAnswer": "pleasant",
            "options": [
                "digital",
                "conventional",
                "accurate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chet el",
            "RightAnswer": "overseas",
            "options": [
                "bloody",
                "loud",
                "thick"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tarafdor",
            "RightAnswer": "advocate",
            "options": [
                "deposit",
                "edit",
                "grab"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muassasa",
            "RightAnswer": "establishment",
            "options": [
                "formation",
                "exposure",
                "involvement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xulosa",
            "RightAnswer": "summary",
            "options": [
                "establishment",
                "formation",
                "exposure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiyin, dag'al, qo'pol",
            "RightAnswer": "rough",
            "options": [
                "soft",
                "fair",
                "rare"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ruchka",
            "RightAnswer": "pen",
            "options": [
                "bath",
                "bowl",
                "desert"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tiklanish, tuzalish",
            "RightAnswer": "recovery",
            "options": [
                "summary",
                "establishment",
                "formation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mahkamlamoq, muhr",
            "RightAnswer": "seal",
            "options": [
                "advocate",
                "deposit",
                "edit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "truba",
            "RightAnswer": "tube",
            "options": [
                "recovery",
                "summary",
                "establishment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "minora",
            "RightAnswer": "tower",
            "options": [
                "tube",
                "recovery",
                "summary"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta'riflamoq, ifodalamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "characterize",
            "options": [
                "translate",
                "lend",
                "entitle"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aniq koâ€˜rsatmoq, batafsil tushuntirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "specify",
            "options": [
                "characterize",
                "translate",
                "lend"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aniq",
            "RightAnswer": "exact",
            "options": [
                "dirty",
                "smooth",
                "loose"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aylantirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "spin",
            "options": [
                "seal",
                "advocate",
                "deposit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshqaruvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "operator",
            "options": [
                "tower",
                "tube",
                "recovery"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chaqaloq",
            "RightAnswer": "infant",
            "options": [
                "operator",
                "tower",
                "tube"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qazimoq",
            "RightAnswer": "dig",
            "options": [
                "spin",
                "seal",
                "advocate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tortmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "drag",
            "options": [
                "dig",
                "spin",
                "seal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'rnatmoq, chiqmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "mount",
            "options": [
                "drag",
                "dig",
                "spin"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'ramoq",
            "RightAnswer": "wrap",
            "options": [
                "mount",
                "drag",
                "dig"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kutmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "anticipate",
            "options": [
                "specify",
                "characterize",
                "translate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qaram",
            "RightAnswer": "dependent",
            "options": [
                "radical",
                "pink",
                "inner"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ixtisoslashmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "specialize",
            "options": [
                "anticipate",
                "specify",
                "characterize"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "burchak",
            "RightAnswer": "angle",
            "options": [
                "pen",
                "bath",
                "bowl"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tovuq",
            "RightAnswer": "chicken",
            "options": [
                "infant",
                "operator",
                "tower"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashvish, qo'rquv",
            "RightAnswer": "anxiety",
            "options": [
                "chicken",
                "infant",
                "operator"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "virus",
            "RightAnswer": "virus",
            "options": [
                "anxiety",
                "chicken",
                "infant"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aniq",
            "RightAnswer": "precisely",
            "options": [
                "occasionally",
                "newly",
                "briefly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "raqib",
            "RightAnswer": "rival",
            "options": [
                "angle",
                "pen",
                "bath"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jinoyat",
            "RightAnswer": "offense",
            "options": [
                "virus",
                "anxiety",
                "chicken"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aniqlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "detect",
            "options": [
                "specialize",
                "anticipate",
                "specify"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'smir",
            "RightAnswer": "teenager",
            "options": [
                "offense",
                "virus",
                "anxiety"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hurmat qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "admire",
            "options": [
                "detect",
                "specialize",
                "anticipate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'rtacha",
            "RightAnswer": "moderate",
            "options": [
                "mature",
                "alter",
                "elect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jarrohlik",
            "RightAnswer": "surgery",
            "options": [
                "teenager",
                "offense",
                "virus"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "musiqachi",
            "RightAnswer": "musician",
            "options": [
                "surgery",
                "teenager",
                "offense"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ahamiyat",
            "RightAnswer": "significance",
            "options": [
                "musician",
                "surgery",
                "teenager"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dush",
            "RightAnswer": "shower",
            "options": [
                "rival",
                "angle",
                "pen"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "noqonuniy",
            "RightAnswer": "illegal",
            "options": [
                "pleasant",
                "digital",
                "conventional"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xayriya",
            "RightAnswer": "charity",
            "options": [
                "significance",
                "musician",
                "surgery"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "universal",
            "RightAnswer": "universal",
            "options": [
                "dependent",
                "radical",
                "pink"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sigaret",
            "RightAnswer": "cigarette",
            "options": [
                "charity",
                "significance",
                "musician"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashkil etmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "constitute",
            "options": [
                "admire",
                "detect",
                "specialize"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yetarli",
            "RightAnswer": "adequate",
            "options": [
                "illegal",
                "pleasant",
                "digital"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maslahatchi",
            "RightAnswer": "consultant",
            "options": [
                "cigarette",
                "charity",
                "significance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tarixchi",
            "RightAnswer": "historian",
            "options": [
                "consultant",
                "cigarette",
                "charity"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 48": [
        {
            "Question": "amaki/tog'a/amma/xolavachcha",
            "RightAnswer": "cousin",
            "options": [
                "historian",
                "consultant",
                "cigarette"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'rish bilan bog'liq",
            "RightAnswer": "visual",
            "options": [
                "universal",
                "dependent",
                "radical"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ahmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "stupid",
            "options": [
                "adequate",
                "illegal",
                "pleasant"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishtiyoqmand",
            "RightAnswer": "keen",
            "options": [
                "exact",
                "dirty",
                "smooth"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "etnik",
            "RightAnswer": "ethnic",
            "options": [
                "stupid",
                "adequate",
                "illegal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "egizak",
            "RightAnswer": "twin",
            "options": [
                "routine",
                "equivalent",
                "retail"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "klinik",
            "RightAnswer": "clinical",
            "options": [
                "ethnic",
                "stupid",
                "adequate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sharqiy",
            "RightAnswer": "eastern",
            "options": [
                "western",
                "sudden",
                "upper"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bashorat",
            "RightAnswer": "forecast",
            "options": [
                "wrap",
                "mount",
                "drag"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bo'lim",
            "RightAnswer": "segment",
            "options": [
                "shower",
                "rival",
                "angle"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "odat",
            "RightAnswer": "custom",
            "options": [
                "twin",
                "routine",
                "equivalent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "moslashtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "adapt",
            "options": [
                "constitute",
                "admire",
                "detect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qum",
            "RightAnswer": "sand",
            "options": [
                "segment",
                "shower",
                "rival"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qalpoq, kepka",
            "RightAnswer": "cap",
            "options": [
                "sand",
                "segment",
                "shower"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tezkor",
            "RightAnswer": "prompt",
            "options": [
                "reverse",
                "upset",
                "hurt"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "joziba",
            "RightAnswer": "charm",
            "options": [
                "cap",
                "sand",
                "segment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "reaksiyaga kirishmoq, javob qaytarmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "react",
            "options": [
                "adapt",
                "constitute",
                "admire"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ma'ruza",
            "RightAnswer": "lecture",
            "options": [
                "charm",
                "cap",
                "sand"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tavakkal qilmoq, sarguzasht",
            "RightAnswer": "venture",
            "options": [
                "forecast",
                "wrap",
                "mount"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "murakkab",
            "RightAnswer": "compound",
            "options": [
                "fat",
                "stone",
                "mass"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qutqarmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "rescue",
            "options": [
                "venture",
                "forecast",
                "wrap"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tartibsizlik",
            "RightAnswer": "mess",
            "options": [
                "rescue",
                "venture",
                "forecast"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "afzal ko'rish",
            "RightAnswer": "preference",
            "options": [
                "cousin",
                "historian",
                "consultant"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "keng qamrovli",
            "RightAnswer": "comprehensive",
            "options": [
                "clinical",
                "ethnic",
                "stupid"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rag'batlantirish",
            "RightAnswer": "incentive",
            "options": [
                "preference",
                "cousin",
                "historian"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "liga, turnir",
            "RightAnswer": "league",
            "options": [
                "incentive",
                "preference",
                "cousin"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dialog, suhbat",
            "RightAnswer": "dialog",
            "options": [
                "lecture",
                "charm",
                "cap"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "krem",
            "RightAnswer": "cream",
            "options": [
                "dialog",
                "lecture",
                "charm"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tez",
            "RightAnswer": "rapid",
            "options": [
                "visual",
                "universal",
                "dependent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bekor qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "cancel",
            "options": [
                "react",
                "adapt",
                "constitute"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "afsuslanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "regret",
            "options": [
                "mess",
                "rescue",
                "venture"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishdan bo'shatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "dismiss",
            "options": [
                "cancel",
                "react",
                "adapt"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chegara",
            "RightAnswer": "margin",
            "options": [
                "league",
                "incentive",
                "preference"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ostida",
            "RightAnswer": "beneath",
            "options": [
                "beside",
                "besides",
                "throughout"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "raqib",
            "RightAnswer": "opponent",
            "options": [
                "margin",
                "league",
                "incentive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qarshilik qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "resist",
            "options": [
                "dismiss",
                "cancel",
                "react"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qobiliyat",
            "RightAnswer": "capability",
            "options": [
                "opponent",
                "margin",
                "league"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mutlaq",
            "RightAnswer": "absolute",
            "options": [
                "rapid",
                "visual",
                "universal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mos kelmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "correspond",
            "options": [
                "resist",
                "dismiss",
                "cancel"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "insult",
            "RightAnswer": "stroke",
            "options": [
                "regret",
                "mess",
                "rescue"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jasorat qilmoq, haddi sig'moq",
            "RightAnswer": "dare",
            "options": [
                "stroke",
                "regret",
                "mess"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'siq",
            "RightAnswer": "barrier",
            "options": [
                "capability",
                "opponent",
                "margin"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tozalamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "rid",
            "options": [
                "correspond",
                "resist",
                "dismiss"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ajralish",
            "RightAnswer": "divorce",
            "options": [
                "cream",
                "dialog",
                "lecture"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vayron qilmoq, vayrona",
            "RightAnswer": "ruin",
            "options": [
                "divorce",
                "cream",
                "dialog"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dafn qilmoq, ko'mmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "bury",
            "options": [
                "rid",
                "correspond",
                "resist"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maslahat",
            "RightAnswer": "counsel",
            "options": [
                "ruin",
                "divorce",
                "cream"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tendensiya",
            "RightAnswer": "tendency",
            "options": [
                "barrier",
                "capability",
                "opponent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tez-tez",
            "RightAnswer": "frequent",
            "options": [
                "keen",
                "exact",
                "dirty"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dvigatel",
            "RightAnswer": "motor",
            "options": [
                "custom",
                "twin",
                "routine"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 49": [
        {
            "Question": "omon qolish",
            "RightAnswer": "survival",
            "options": [
                "tendency",
                "barrier",
                "capability"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qarshi",
            "RightAnswer": "counter",
            "options": [
                "counsel",
                "ruin",
                "divorce"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "egallamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "possess",
            "options": [
                "bury",
                "rid",
                "correspond"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ruxsat",
            "RightAnswer": "permission",
            "options": [
                "survival",
                "tendency",
                "barrier"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vodiy",
            "RightAnswer": "valley",
            "options": [
                "permission",
                "survival",
                "tendency"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "suzmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "float",
            "options": [
                "dare",
                "stroke",
                "regret"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aqldan ozgan",
            "RightAnswer": "mad",
            "options": [
                "overseas",
                "bloody",
                "loud"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "juda",
            "RightAnswer": "greatly",
            "options": [
                "precisely",
                "occasionally",
                "newly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'rinadigan",
            "RightAnswer": "visible",
            "options": [
                "comprehensive",
                "clinical",
                "ethnic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "elektr",
            "RightAnswer": "electric",
            "options": [
                "absolute",
                "rapid",
                "visual"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taassurot qoldiruvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "impressive",
            "options": [
                "visible",
                "comprehensive",
                "clinical"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rivojlanish, takomillashish",
            "RightAnswer": "evolution",
            "options": [
                "valley",
                "permission",
                "survival"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xabardorlik, ogohlik",
            "RightAnswer": "awareness",
            "options": [
                "evolution",
                "valley",
                "permission"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zo'ravon",
            "RightAnswer": "violent",
            "options": [
                "impressive",
                "visible",
                "comprehensive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qul",
            "RightAnswer": "slave",
            "options": [
                "awareness",
                "evolution",
                "valley"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boy",
            "RightAnswer": "wealthy",
            "options": [
                "violent",
                "impressive",
                "visible"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "arxitektura",
            "RightAnswer": "architecture",
            "options": [
                "slave",
                "awareness",
                "evolution"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "toâ€˜gâ€˜ri keladigan, ma'qul",
            "RightAnswer": "acceptable",
            "options": [
                "wealthy",
                "violent",
                "impressive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jurnal",
            "RightAnswer": "journal",
            "options": [
                "architecture",
                "slave",
                "awareness"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'mir",
            "RightAnswer": "coal",
            "options": [
                "journal",
                "architecture",
                "slave"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'lchov",
            "RightAnswer": "measurement",
            "options": [
                "coal",
                "journal",
                "architecture"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tasodifiy",
            "RightAnswer": "random",
            "options": [
                "electric",
                "absolute",
                "rapid"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muvaffaqiyatli",
            "RightAnswer": "successfully",
            "options": [
                "greatly",
                "precisely",
                "occasionally"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tushkunlikka solmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "depress",
            "options": [
                "possess",
                "bury",
                "rid"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tasvir",
            "RightAnswer": "illustration",
            "options": [
                "measurement",
                "coal",
                "journal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "portlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "burst",
            "options": [
                "float",
                "dare",
                "stroke"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "afzallik, ustunlik",
            "RightAnswer": "privilege",
            "options": [
                "counter",
                "counsel",
                "ruin"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xaridor",
            "RightAnswer": "buyer",
            "options": [
                "illustration",
                "measurement",
                "coal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'zaro",
            "RightAnswer": "mutual",
            "options": [
                "random",
                "electric",
                "absolute"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "temir yo'l",
            "RightAnswer": "rail",
            "options": [
                "privilege",
                "counter",
                "counsel"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rag'batlantirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "motivate",
            "options": [
                "depress",
                "possess",
                "bury"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "laboratoriya",
            "RightAnswer": "laboratory",
            "options": [
                "buyer",
                "illustration",
                "measurement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ipoteka",
            "RightAnswer": "mortgage",
            "options": [
                "rail",
                "privilege",
                "counter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'tarilish",
            "RightAnswer": "promotion",
            "options": [
                "laboratory",
                "buyer",
                "illustration"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishtiyoq",
            "RightAnswer": "passion",
            "options": [
                "promotion",
                "laboratory",
                "buyer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chempion",
            "RightAnswer": "champion",
            "options": [
                "mortgage",
                "rail",
                "privilege"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bajarmoq, amalga oshirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "fulfill",
            "options": [
                "motivate",
                "depress",
                "possess"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chang",
            "RightAnswer": "dust",
            "options": [
                "burst",
                "float",
                "dare"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bag'ishlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "dedicate",
            "options": [
                "fulfill",
                "motivate",
                "depress"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taxminan",
            "RightAnswer": "roughly",
            "options": [
                "successfully",
                "greatly",
                "precisely"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yubka",
            "RightAnswer": "skirt",
            "options": [
                "dust",
                "burst",
                "float"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "viloyat",
            "RightAnswer": "province",
            "options": [
                "passion",
                "promotion",
                "laboratory"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yurish",
            "RightAnswer": "march",
            "options": [
                "champion",
                "mortgage",
                "rail"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "baholash",
            "RightAnswer": "evaluation",
            "options": [
                "province",
                "passion",
                "promotion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kompromis",
            "RightAnswer": "compromise",
            "options": [
                "march",
                "champion",
                "mortgage"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uddalamoq, amalga oshirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "accomplish",
            "options": [
                "dedicate",
                "fulfill",
                "motivate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zaiflik",
            "RightAnswer": "weakness",
            "options": [
                "evaluation",
                "province",
                "passion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "e'lon",
            "RightAnswer": "announcement",
            "options": [
                "weakness",
                "evaluation",
                "province"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tuz",
            "RightAnswer": "salt",
            "options": [
                "compromise",
                "march",
                "champion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qarash",
            "RightAnswer": "glance",
            "options": [
                "skirt",
                "dust",
                "burst"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 50": [
        {
            "Question": "opera",
            "RightAnswer": "opera",
            "options": [
                "announcement",
                "weakness",
                "evaluation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "musobaqa",
            "RightAnswer": "contest",
            "options": [
                "salt",
                "compromise",
                "march"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "cho'tka",
            "RightAnswer": "brush",
            "options": [
                "glance",
                "skirt",
                "dust"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uyaltirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "embarrass",
            "options": [
                "accomplish",
                "dedicate",
                "fulfill"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "galereya",
            "RightAnswer": "gallery",
            "options": [
                "opera",
                "announcement",
                "weakness"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "genetik",
            "RightAnswer": "genetic",
            "options": [
                "acceptable",
                "wealthy",
                "violent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "agressiv",
            "RightAnswer": "aggressive",
            "options": [
                "genetic",
                "acceptable",
                "wealthy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'krak qafasi",
            "RightAnswer": "chest",
            "options": [
                "gallery",
                "opera",
                "announcement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "format, shakl",
            "RightAnswer": "format",
            "options": [
                "contest",
                "salt",
                "compromise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "adabiy",
            "RightAnswer": "literary",
            "options": [
                "aggressive",
                "genetic",
                "acceptable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hukmronlik qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "govern",
            "options": [
                "embarrass",
                "accomplish",
                "dedicate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qabul qilmoq, quchoqlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "embrace",
            "options": [
                "govern",
                "embarrass",
                "accomplish"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maqtamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "praise",
            "options": [
                "brush",
                "glance",
                "skirt"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jim, tinch",
            "RightAnswer": "silent",
            "options": [
                "literary",
                "aggressive",
                "genetic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nasos",
            "RightAnswer": "pump",
            "options": [
                "praise",
                "brush",
                "glance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nashriyotchi",
            "RightAnswer": "publisher",
            "options": [
                "chest",
                "gallery",
                "opera"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bayram",
            "RightAnswer": "celebration",
            "options": [
                "publisher",
                "chest",
                "gallery"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "golf",
            "RightAnswer": "golf",
            "options": [
                "celebration",
                "publisher",
                "chest"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kompensatsiya",
            "RightAnswer": "compensation",
            "options": [
                "golf",
                "celebration",
                "publisher"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "klassik",
            "RightAnswer": "classical",
            "options": [
                "silent",
                "literary",
                "aggressive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "og'irlikni o'lchamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "weigh",
            "options": [
                "embrace",
                "govern",
                "embarrass"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qarshi",
            "RightAnswer": "versus",
            "options": [
                "to",
                "till",
                "except"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kamchilik",
            "RightAnswer": "deficit",
            "options": [
                "compensation",
                "golf",
                "celebration"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'zgartirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "modify",
            "options": [
                "weigh",
                "embrace",
                "govern"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chaqmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "flash",
            "options": [
                "pump",
                "praise",
                "brush"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "do'stlik",
            "RightAnswer": "friendship",
            "options": [
                "deficit",
                "compensation",
                "golf"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kasb",
            "RightAnswer": "profession",
            "options": [
                "friendship",
                "deficit",
                "compensation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haqiqatdan",
            "RightAnswer": "literally",
            "options": [
                "roughly",
                "successfully",
                "greatly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tenglama",
            "RightAnswer": "equation",
            "options": [
                "profession",
                "friendship",
                "deficit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "imo-ishora",
            "RightAnswer": "gesture",
            "options": [
                "flash",
                "pump",
                "praise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kayfiyatini ko'tarmoq, zavqlantirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "entertain",
            "options": [
                "modify",
                "weigh",
                "embrace"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ajoyib",
            "RightAnswer": "fantastic",
            "options": [
                "classical",
                "silent",
                "literary"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tayinlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "assign",
            "options": [
                "entertain",
                "modify",
                "weigh"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "inflyatsiya",
            "RightAnswer": "inflation",
            "options": [
                "equation",
                "profession",
                "friendship"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tarixiy",
            "RightAnswer": "historic",
            "options": [
                "mutual",
                "random",
                "electric"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jarohat yetkazmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "injure",
            "options": [
                "assign",
                "entertain",
                "modify"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "masofaviy",
            "RightAnswer": "remote",
            "options": [
                "historic",
                "mutual",
                "random"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "terapiya",
            "RightAnswer": "therapy",
            "options": [
                "inflation",
                "equation",
                "profession"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "apelsin",
            "RightAnswer": "orange",
            "options": [
                "motor",
                "custom",
                "twin"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "burmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "twist",
            "options": [
                "gesture",
                "flash",
                "pump"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xodimlar",
            "RightAnswer": "personnel",
            "options": [
                "therapy",
                "inflation",
                "equation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tasavvur",
            "RightAnswer": "imagination",
            "options": [
                "personnel",
                "therapy",
                "inflation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rozilik bermaslik",
            "RightAnswer": "disagree",
            "options": [
                "injure",
                "assign",
                "entertain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tomoq",
            "RightAnswer": "throat",
            "options": [
                "imagination",
                "personnel",
                "therapy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tushuncha",
            "RightAnswer": "insight",
            "options": [
                "throat",
                "imagination",
                "personnel"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hal qilish",
            "RightAnswer": "tackle",
            "options": [
                "twist",
                "gesture",
                "flash"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "abadiy",
            "RightAnswer": "forever",
            "options": [
                "literally",
                "roughly",
                "successfully"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oshmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "exceed",
            "options": [
                "disagree",
                "injure",
                "assign"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xarajat",
            "RightAnswer": "expenditure",
            "options": [
                "insight",
                "throat",
                "imagination"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "quvonch",
            "RightAnswer": "joy",
            "options": [
                "expenditure",
                "insight",
                "throat"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 51": [
        {
            "Question": "homilador",
            "RightAnswer": "pregnant",
            "options": [
                "fantastic",
                "classical",
                "silent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishonchli",
            "RightAnswer": "reliable",
            "options": [
                "pregnant",
                "fantastic",
                "classical"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jihoz",
            "RightAnswer": "gear",
            "options": [
                "format",
                "contest",
                "salt"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bosmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "click",
            "options": [
                "tackle",
                "twist",
                "gesture"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shoir",
            "RightAnswer": "poet",
            "options": [
                "joy",
                "expenditure",
                "insight"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boylik",
            "RightAnswer": "fortune",
            "options": [
                "poet",
                "joy",
                "expenditure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "marosim",
            "RightAnswer": "ceremony",
            "options": [
                "fortune",
                "poet",
                "joy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ustma-ust turgan, to'plam  ",
            "RightAnswer": "pile",
            "options": [
                "gear",
                "format",
                "contest"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "cho'chqa",
            "RightAnswer": "pig",
            "options": [
                "pile",
                "gear",
                "format"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aralashma",
            "RightAnswer": "mixture",
            "options": [
                "ceremony",
                "fortune",
                "poet"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "avtomatik tarzda",
            "RightAnswer": "automatically",
            "options": [
                "forever",
                "literally",
                "roughly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "olim",
            "RightAnswer": "scholar",
            "options": [
                "mixture",
                "ceremony",
                "fortune"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "psixologik",
            "RightAnswer": "psychological",
            "options": [
                "reliable",
                "pregnant",
                "fantastic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dramatik tarzda",
            "RightAnswer": "dramatically",
            "options": [
                "automatically",
                "forever",
                "literally"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ulush, qoziq",
            "RightAnswer": "stake",
            "options": [
                "pig",
                "pile",
                "gear"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jonzot",
            "RightAnswer": "creature",
            "options": [
                "scholar",
                "mixture",
                "ceremony"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hamkorlik",
            "RightAnswer": "partnership",
            "options": [
                "creature",
                "scholar",
                "mixture"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishtirok",
            "RightAnswer": "participation",
            "options": [
                "partnership",
                "creature",
                "scholar"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "band, bob",
            "RightAnswer": "clause",
            "options": [
                "participation",
                "partnership",
                "creature"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jazo",
            "RightAnswer": "penalty",
            "options": [
                "clause",
                "participation",
                "partnership"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xonadon",
            "RightAnswer": "chamber",
            "options": [
                "penalty",
                "clause",
                "participation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hashamatli",
            "RightAnswer": "fancy",
            "options": [
                "remote",
                "historic",
                "mutual"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "she'riyat",
            "RightAnswer": "poetry",
            "options": [
                "chamber",
                "penalty",
                "clause"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "suhbat",
            "RightAnswer": "chat",
            "options": [
                "click",
                "tackle",
                "twist"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kiyim-kechak",
            "RightAnswer": "clothing",
            "options": [
                "poetry",
                "chamber",
                "penalty"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rivojlanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "evolve",
            "options": [
                "exceed",
                "disagree",
                "injure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maqsadida, uchun",
            "RightAnswer": "sake",
            "options": [
                "clothing",
                "poetry",
                "chamber"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tokcha",
            "RightAnswer": "shelf",
            "options": [
                "stake",
                "pig",
                "pile"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kuchaytirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "boost",
            "options": [
                "chat",
                "click",
                "tackle"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dum",
            "RightAnswer": "tail",
            "options": [
                "shelf",
                "stake",
                "pig"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "egalik",
            "RightAnswer": "possession",
            "options": [
                "sake",
                "clothing",
                "poetry"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bola oldirish",
            "RightAnswer": "abortion",
            "options": [
                "possession",
                "sake",
                "clothing"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiziqqon, qiziquvchan",
            "RightAnswer": "curious",
            "options": [
                "psychological",
                "reliable",
                "pregnant"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yog'ochdan yasalgan",
            "RightAnswer": "wooden",
            "options": [
                "curious",
                "psychological",
                "reliable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'sish",
            "RightAnswer": "boom",
            "options": [
                "boost",
                "chat",
                "click"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hikoya",
            "RightAnswer": "tale",
            "options": [
                "tail",
                "shelf",
                "stake"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "demokratik",
            "RightAnswer": "democratic",
            "options": [
                "wooden",
                "curious",
                "psychological"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "texnik xizmat",
            "RightAnswer": "maintenance",
            "options": [
                "abortion",
                "possession",
                "sake"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "natijada",
            "RightAnswer": "consequently",
            "options": [
                "dramatically",
                "automatically",
                "forever"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "idish",
            "RightAnswer": "pot",
            "options": [
                "tale",
                "tail",
                "shelf"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mol",
            "RightAnswer": "cow",
            "options": [
                "pot",
                "tale",
                "tail"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mustahkamlash",
            "RightAnswer": "strengthen",
            "options": [
                "evolve",
                "exceed",
                "disagree"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bir vaqtning o'zida",
            "RightAnswer": "whilst",
            "options": [
                "whenever",
                "nevertheless",
                "therefore"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "cheklov",
            "RightAnswer": "constraint",
            "options": [
                "maintenance",
                "abortion",
                "possession"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bukmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "fold",
            "options": [
                "boom",
                "boost",
                "chat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "quti",
            "RightAnswer": "bin",
            "options": [
                "cow",
                "pot",
                "tale"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshdan kechirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "undergo",
            "options": [
                "strengthen",
                "evolve",
                "exceed"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ehtimoliy",
            "RightAnswer": "potentially",
            "options": [
                "consequently",
                "dramatically",
                "automatically"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "doira, ko'lam",
            "RightAnswer": "scope",
            "options": [
                "bin",
                "cow",
                "pot"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "soxta qilish",
            "RightAnswer": "pretend",
            "options": [
                "undergo",
                "strengthen",
                "evolve"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 52": [
        {
            "Question": "xilma-xillik",
            "RightAnswer": "diversity",
            "options": [
                "constraint",
                "maintenance",
                "abortion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "da'vo qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "allege",
            "options": [
                "pretend",
                "undergo",
                "strengthen"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "faxr",
            "RightAnswer": "pride",
            "options": [
                "diversity",
                "constraint",
                "maintenance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kuchli",
            "RightAnswer": "intense",
            "options": [
                "democratic",
                "wooden",
                "curious"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "so'rov",
            "RightAnswer": "inquiry",
            "options": [
                "pride",
                "diversity",
                "constraint"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishdan ketmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "resign",
            "options": [
                "allege",
                "pretend",
                "undergo"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hunarmandchilik",
            "RightAnswer": "craft",
            "options": [
                "fold",
                "boom",
                "boost"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qat'iy",
            "RightAnswer": "strict",
            "options": [
                "intense",
                "democratic",
                "wooden"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "beton",
            "RightAnswer": "concrete",
            "options": [
                "parallel",
                "solid",
                "slight"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qobiq",
            "RightAnswer": "shell",
            "options": [
                "scope",
                "bin",
                "cow"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "la'nat",
            "RightAnswer": "damn",
            "options": [
                "prompt",
                "reverse",
                "upset"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ajralib turuvchi, alohida",
            "RightAnswer": "distinct",
            "options": [
                "strict",
                "intense",
                "democratic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hazil",
            "RightAnswer": "humor",
            "options": [
                "inquiry",
                "pride",
                "diversity"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "cheklov",
            "RightAnswer": "limitation",
            "options": [
                "humor",
                "inquiry",
                "pride"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'rsatkich",
            "RightAnswer": "indication",
            "options": [
                "limitation",
                "humor",
                "inquiry"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "barqarorlik",
            "RightAnswer": "stability",
            "options": [
                "indication",
                "limitation",
                "humor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dono",
            "RightAnswer": "wise",
            "options": [
                "eastern",
                "western",
                "sudden"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "e'tiborsizlik",
            "RightAnswer": "neglect",
            "options": [
                "craft",
                "fold",
                "boom"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaratmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "compose",
            "options": [
                "resign",
                "allege",
                "pretend"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qamoqxona",
            "RightAnswer": "jail",
            "options": [
                "shell",
                "scope",
                "bin"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshpana",
            "RightAnswer": "shelter",
            "options": [
                "neglect",
                "craft",
                "fold"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "faqatgina",
            "RightAnswer": "mere",
            "options": [
                "fancy",
                "remote",
                "historic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uglerod",
            "RightAnswer": "carbon",
            "options": [
                "stability",
                "indication",
                "limitation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tartibga solmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "regulate",
            "options": [
                "compose",
                "resign",
                "allege"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "pishloq",
            "RightAnswer": "cheese",
            "options": [
                "carbon",
                "stability",
                "indication"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tepki",
            "RightAnswer": "trigger",
            "options": [
                "shelter",
                "neglect",
                "craft"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nay, truba",
            "RightAnswer": "pipe",
            "options": [
                "jail",
                "shell",
                "scope"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vayronagarchilik",
            "RightAnswer": "destruction",
            "options": [
                "cheese",
                "carbon",
                "stability"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "gitara",
            "RightAnswer": "guitar",
            "options": [
                "destruction",
                "cheese",
                "carbon"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bayroq",
            "RightAnswer": "flag",
            "options": [
                "pipe",
                "jail",
                "shell"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "pianino",
            "RightAnswer": "piano",
            "options": [
                "guitar",
                "destruction",
                "cheese"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sehr",
            "RightAnswer": "magic",
            "options": [
                "orange",
                "motor",
                "custom"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sir, sinoat",
            "RightAnswer": "mystery",
            "options": [
                "piano",
                "guitar",
                "destruction"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chang'i",
            "RightAnswer": "ski",
            "options": [
                "trigger",
                "shelter",
                "neglect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "pichirlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "whisper",
            "options": [
                "ski",
                "trigger",
                "shelter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "orqa",
            "RightAnswer": "rear",
            "options": [
                "lean",
                "shut",
                "suspect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "menyu",
            "RightAnswer": "menu",
            "options": [
                "mystery",
                "piano",
                "guitar"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tur",
            "RightAnswer": "species",
            "options": [
                "menu",
                "mystery",
                "piano"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oy",
            "RightAnswer": "moon",
            "options": [
                "flag",
                "pipe",
                "jail"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taxminan",
            "RightAnswer": "presumably",
            "options": [
                "potentially",
                "consequently",
                "dramatically"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "duo qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "bless",
            "options": [
                "regulate",
                "compose",
                "resign"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aviakompaniya",
            "RightAnswer": "airline",
            "options": [
                "species",
                "menu",
                "mystery"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tuzatish",
            "RightAnswer": "amendment",
            "options": [
                "airline",
                "species",
                "menu"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "buvi",
            "RightAnswer": "grandmother",
            "options": [
                "amendment",
                "airline",
                "species"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hakamlar hay'ati",
            "RightAnswer": "jury",
            "options": [
                "grandmother",
                "amendment",
                "airline"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hamkorlik",
            "RightAnswer": "cooperation",
            "options": [
                "jury",
                "grandmother",
                "amendment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "fuqaro",
            "RightAnswer": "civilian",
            "options": [
                "mere",
                "fancy",
                "remote"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tarkib",
            "RightAnswer": "composition",
            "options": [
                "cooperation",
                "jury",
                "grandmother"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanga",
            "RightAnswer": "coin",
            "options": [
                "moon",
                "flag",
                "pipe"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "e'tiborsiz, ga qaramasdan",
            "RightAnswer": "regardless",
            "options": [
                "beneath",
                "beside",
                "besides"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 53": [
        {
            "Question": "tekshirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "scan",
            "options": [
                "whisper",
                "ski",
                "trigger"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "guruh",
            "RightAnswer": "bunch",
            "options": [
                "coin",
                "moon",
                "flag"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "irqiy",
            "RightAnswer": "racial",
            "options": [
                "civilian",
                "mere",
                "fancy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "salomlashmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "greet",
            "options": [
                "bless",
                "regulate",
                "compose"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "umid qilgan holda",
            "RightAnswer": "hopefully",
            "options": [
                "presumably",
                "potentially",
                "consequently"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jazo, sanktsiya",
            "RightAnswer": "sanction",
            "options": [
                "scan",
                "whisper",
                "ski"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hiyla",
            "RightAnswer": "trick",
            "options": [
                "sanction",
                "scan",
                "whisper"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "paragraf",
            "RightAnswer": "paragraph",
            "options": [
                "composition",
                "cooperation",
                "jury"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishlab chiqaruvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "maker",
            "options": [
                "paragraph",
                "composition",
                "cooperation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shokolad",
            "RightAnswer": "chocolate",
            "options": [
                "maker",
                "paragraph",
                "composition"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rag'batlantirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "stimulate",
            "options": [
                "greet",
                "bless",
                "regulate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kamar",
            "RightAnswer": "belt",
            "options": [
                "bunch",
                "coin",
                "moon"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kartoshka",
            "RightAnswer": "potato",
            "options": [
                "chocolate",
                "maker",
                "paragraph"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hikoya",
            "RightAnswer": "narrative",
            "options": [
                "potato",
                "chocolate",
                "maker"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'qima",
            "RightAnswer": "tissue",
            "options": [
                "narrative",
                "potato",
                "chocolate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bazo'r",
            "RightAnswer": "barely",
            "options": [
                "hopefully",
                "presumably",
                "potentially"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ixtiro qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "invent",
            "options": [
                "stimulate",
                "greet",
                "bless"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "turizm",
            "RightAnswer": "tourism",
            "options": [
                "tissue",
                "narrative",
                "potato"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "professional",
            "RightAnswer": "pro",
            "options": [
                "magic",
                "orange",
                "motor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zinapoya",
            "RightAnswer": "stair",
            "options": [
                "tourism",
                "tissue",
                "narrative"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ikkilanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "hesitate",
            "options": [
                "invent",
                "stimulate",
                "greet"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "porlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "shine",
            "options": [
                "trick",
                "sanction",
                "scan"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rag'bat",
            "RightAnswer": "motivation",
            "options": [
                "stair",
                "tourism",
                "tissue"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qat'iy",
            "RightAnswer": "firmly",
            "options": [
                "barely",
                "hopefully",
                "presumably"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ichki",
            "RightAnswer": "interior",
            "options": [
                "racial",
                "civilian",
                "mere"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oshqozon",
            "RightAnswer": "stomach",
            "options": [
                "motivation",
                "stair",
                "tourism"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hech qayerda",
            "RightAnswer": "nowhere",
            "options": [
                "anymore",
                "anywhere",
                "there"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ibodat qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "pray",
            "options": [
                "hesitate",
                "invent",
                "stimulate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chempionlik",
            "RightAnswer": "championship",
            "options": [
                "stomach",
                "motivation",
                "stair"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xizmatkor",
            "RightAnswer": "servant",
            "options": [
                "championship",
                "stomach",
                "motivation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "immigrant",
            "RightAnswer": "immigrant",
            "options": [
                "servant",
                "championship",
                "stomach"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ortiqcha",
            "RightAnswer": "excess",
            "options": [
                "pro",
                "magic",
                "orange"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "murakkablik",
            "RightAnswer": "complexity",
            "options": [
                "immigrant",
                "servant",
                "championship"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "javobgarlik",
            "RightAnswer": "liability",
            "options": [
                "complexity",
                "immigrant",
                "servant"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hayratlanarli",
            "RightAnswer": "surprisingly",
            "options": [
                "firmly",
                "barely",
                "hopefully"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chiqarib olish",
            "RightAnswer": "extract",
            "options": [
                "shine",
                "trick",
                "sanction"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "amalga oshirish",
            "RightAnswer": "implementation",
            "options": [
                "liability",
                "complexity",
                "immigrant"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tarafkashlik",
            "RightAnswer": "bias",
            "options": [
                "belt",
                "bunch",
                "coin"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "farqli tarzda",
            "RightAnswer": "differently",
            "options": [
                "surprisingly",
                "firmly",
                "barely"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "katalog",
            "RightAnswer": "catalog",
            "options": [
                "bias",
                "belt",
                "bunch"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uzluksiz",
            "RightAnswer": "continuous",
            "options": [
                "distinct",
                "strict",
                "intense"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oltin",
            "RightAnswer": "golden",
            "options": [
                "continuous",
                "distinct",
                "strict"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "pochta markasi",
            "RightAnswer": "stamp",
            "options": [
                "extract",
                "shine",
                "trick"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'rsatma",
            "RightAnswer": "guideline",
            "options": [
                "implementation",
                "liability",
                "complexity"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "konvert",
            "RightAnswer": "envelope",
            "options": [
                "guideline",
                "implementation",
                "liability"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "pichoq",
            "RightAnswer": "knife",
            "options": [
                "catalog",
                "bias",
                "belt"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "biologik",
            "RightAnswer": "biological",
            "options": [
                "golden",
                "continuous",
                "distinct"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "iste'mol qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "consume",
            "options": [
                "pray",
                "hesitate",
                "invent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hashamat",
            "RightAnswer": "luxury",
            "options": [
                "envelope",
                "guideline",
                "implementation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haftalik",
            "RightAnswer": "weekly",
            "options": [
                "mad",
                "overseas",
                "bloody"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 54": [
        {
            "Question": "qayerda bo'lmasin",
            "RightAnswer": "wherever",
            "options": [
                "nowhere",
                "anymore",
                "anywhere"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tishlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "bite",
            "options": [
                "stamp",
                "extract",
                "shine"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "printer",
            "RightAnswer": "printer",
            "options": [
                "luxury",
                "envelope",
                "guideline"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "birinchi navbatda",
            "RightAnswer": "firstly",
            "options": [
                "differently",
                "surprisingly",
                "firmly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashvishli",
            "RightAnswer": "anxious",
            "options": [
                "biological",
                "golden",
                "continuous"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sarguzasht",
            "RightAnswer": "adventure",
            "options": [
                "printer",
                "luxury",
                "envelope"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'siq",
            "RightAnswer": "fence",
            "options": [
                "bite",
                "stamp",
                "extract"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chiqarib yubormoq",
            "RightAnswer": "exhaust",
            "options": [
                "fence",
                "bite",
                "stamp"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "joziba",
            "RightAnswer": "attraction",
            "options": [
                "adventure",
                "printer",
                "luxury"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "okean",
            "RightAnswer": "ocean",
            "options": [
                "attraction",
                "adventure",
                "printer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jimjit",
            "RightAnswer": "quietly",
            "options": [
                "firstly",
                "differently",
                "surprisingly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qal'a",
            "RightAnswer": "castle",
            "options": [
                "ocean",
                "attraction",
                "adventure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'p yillik tajribaga ega",
            "RightAnswer": "veteran",
            "options": [
                "castle",
                "ocean",
                "attraction"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aks ettirish",
            "RightAnswer": "reflection",
            "options": [
                "veteran",
                "castle",
                "ocean"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asab",
            "RightAnswer": "nerve",
            "options": [
                "reflection",
                "veteran",
                "castle"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qat'iyat",
            "RightAnswer": "determination",
            "options": [
                "nerve",
                "reflection",
                "veteran"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jami",
            "RightAnswer": "altogether",
            "options": [
                "quietly",
                "firstly",
                "differently"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "adabiy asar",
            "RightAnswer": "fiction",
            "options": [
                "determination",
                "nerve",
                "reflection"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "gilam",
            "RightAnswer": "carpet",
            "options": [
                "knife",
                "catalog",
                "bias"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'plam",
            "RightAnswer": "cluster",
            "options": [
                "carpet",
                "knife",
                "catalog"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chalkashlik",
            "RightAnswer": "confusion",
            "options": [
                "fiction",
                "determination",
                "nerve"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shoshilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "hurry",
            "options": [
                "exhaust",
                "fence",
                "bite"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mantiq",
            "RightAnswer": "logic",
            "options": [
                "confusion",
                "fiction",
                "determination"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bahsli",
            "RightAnswer": "controversial",
            "options": [
                "anxious",
                "biological",
                "golden"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xom",
            "RightAnswer": "raw",
            "options": [
                "controversial",
                "anxious",
                "biological"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "grammatik qoidalar",
            "RightAnswer": "grammar",
            "options": [
                "logic",
                "confusion",
                "fiction"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qayta ko'rib chiqmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "revise",
            "options": [
                "consume",
                "pray",
                "hesitate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishora",
            "RightAnswer": "hint",
            "options": [
                "hurry",
                "exhaust",
                "fence"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ilgak",
            "RightAnswer": "hook",
            "options": [
                "hint",
                "hurry",
                "exhaust"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'ng'iroq",
            "RightAnswer": "bell",
            "options": [
                "grammar",
                "logic",
                "confusion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "suyuqlik",
            "RightAnswer": "liquid",
            "options": [
                "excess",
                "pro",
                "magic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashvishlanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "panic",
            "options": [
                "hook",
                "hint",
                "hurry"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "amaki, tog'a",
            "RightAnswer": "uncle",
            "options": [
                "bell",
                "grammar",
                "logic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "guruch",
            "RightAnswer": "rice",
            "options": [
                "uncle",
                "bell",
                "grammar"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiyalik",
            "RightAnswer": "slope",
            "options": [
                "cluster",
                "carpet",
                "knife"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "baxt",
            "RightAnswer": "happiness",
            "options": [
                "rice",
                "uncle",
                "bell"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haqiqiy",
            "RightAnswer": "genuine",
            "options": [
                "raw",
                "controversial",
                "anxious"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kema, idish",
            "RightAnswer": "vessel",
            "options": [
                "happiness",
                "rice",
                "uncle"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "fe'l",
            "RightAnswer": "verb",
            "options": [
                "vessel",
                "happiness",
                "rice"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hisoblamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "reckon",
            "options": [
                "revise",
                "consume",
                "pray"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ahmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "silly",
            "options": [
                "genuine",
                "raw",
                "controversial"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashish",
            "RightAnswer": "transportation",
            "options": [
                "verb",
                "vessel",
                "happiness"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "port, bandargoh",
            "RightAnswer": "harbor",
            "options": [
                "slope",
                "cluster",
                "carpet"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "komediya",
            "RightAnswer": "comedy",
            "options": [
                "transportation",
                "verb",
                "vessel"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ortidan quvmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "chase",
            "options": [
                "panic",
                "hook",
                "hint"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "saqlash joyi",
            "RightAnswer": "storage",
            "options": [
                "comedy",
                "transportation",
                "verb"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "olam",
            "RightAnswer": "universe",
            "options": [
                "storage",
                "comedy",
                "transportation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yomon",
            "RightAnswer": "horrible",
            "options": [
                "silly",
                "genuine",
                "raw"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'y",
            "RightAnswer": "sheep",
            "options": [
                "universe",
                "storage",
                "comedy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oshiq",
            "RightAnswer": "lover",
            "options": [
                "sheep",
                "universe",
                "storage"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 55": [
        {
            "Question": "kalamush",
            "RightAnswer": "rat",
            "options": [
                "harbor",
                "slope",
                "cluster"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "portret",
            "RightAnswer": "portrait",
            "options": [
                "lover",
                "sheep",
                "universe"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "begunoh",
            "RightAnswer": "innocent",
            "options": [
                "horrible",
                "silly",
                "genuine"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o'rnini bosuvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "substitute",
            "options": [
                "chase",
                "panic",
                "hook"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo'shimcha",
            "RightAnswer": "supplement",
            "options": [
                "substitute",
                "chase",
                "panic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sozlash",
            "RightAnswer": "adjustment",
            "options": [
                "portrait",
                "lover",
                "sheep"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oqilona",
            "RightAnswer": "reasonably",
            "options": [
                "altogether",
                "quietly",
                "firstly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "filtrlash",
            "RightAnswer": "filter",
            "options": [
                "supplement",
                "substitute",
                "chase"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "moslashuvchan",
            "RightAnswer": "flexible",
            "options": [
                "innocent",
                "horrible",
                "silly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mavhum",
            "RightAnswer": "abstract",
            "options": [
                "concrete",
                "parallel",
                "solid"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yelkan",
            "RightAnswer": "tent",
            "options": [
                "rat",
                "harbor",
                "slope"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aniq",
            "RightAnswer": "precise",
            "options": [
                "flexible",
                "innocent",
                "horrible"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "masofaviy, uzoq",
            "RightAnswer": "distant",
            "options": [
                "wise",
                "eastern",
                "western"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "begona",
            "RightAnswer": "stranger",
            "options": [
                "liquid",
                "excess",
                "pro"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "soya",
            "RightAnswer": "shade",
            "options": [
                "tent",
                "rat",
                "harbor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "don",
            "RightAnswer": "grain",
            "options": [
                "shade",
                "tent",
                "rat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "joylashtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "situate",
            "options": [
                "reckon",
                "revise",
                "consume"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xulosa qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "summarize",
            "options": [
                "situate",
                "reckon",
                "revise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sakramoq",
            "RightAnswer": "leap",
            "options": [
                "filter",
                "supplement",
                "substitute"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sindirish",
            "RightAnswer": "snap",
            "options": [
                "leap",
                "filter",
                "supplement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ehtimol",
            "RightAnswer": "probability",
            "options": [
                "adjustment",
                "portrait",
                "lover"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "teri",
            "RightAnswer": "leather",
            "options": [
                "stranger",
                "liquid",
                "excess"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "noaniqlik",
            "RightAnswer": "uncertainty",
            "options": [
                "probability",
                "adjustment",
                "portrait"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "so'kinmoq, qasam ichmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "swear",
            "options": [
                "damn",
                "prompt",
                "reverse"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qochqin",
            "RightAnswer": "refugee",
            "options": [
                "uncertainty",
                "probability",
                "adjustment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qirg'oq",
            "RightAnswer": "shore",
            "options": [
                "grain",
                "shade",
                "tent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oylik",
            "RightAnswer": "monthly",
            "options": [
                "weekly",
                "mad",
                "overseas"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashkil etmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "comprise",
            "options": [
                "summarize",
                "situate",
                "reckon"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aralashtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "stir",
            "options": [
                "snap",
                "leap",
                "filter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hayajon",
            "RightAnswer": "excitement",
            "options": [
                "refugee",
                "uncertainty",
                "probability"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xo'rsinmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "sigh",
            "options": [
                "stir",
                "snap",
                "leap"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "homiladorlik",
            "RightAnswer": "pregnancy",
            "options": [
                "excitement",
                "refugee",
                "uncertainty"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tajribaga oid",
            "RightAnswer": "experimental",
            "options": [
                "interior",
                "racial",
                "civilian"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "institutga oid",
            "RightAnswer": "institutional",
            "options": [
                "precise",
                "flexible",
                "innocent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bo'lak",
            "RightAnswer": "slice",
            "options": [
                "shore",
                "grain",
                "shade"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sang'imoq",
            "RightAnswer": "wander",
            "options": [
                "comprise",
                "summarize",
                "situate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "imperiya",
            "RightAnswer": "empire",
            "options": [
                "pregnancy",
                "excitement",
                "refugee"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "keyinroq",
            "RightAnswer": "subsequently",
            "options": [
                "reasonably",
                "altogether",
                "quietly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muloyim",
            "RightAnswer": "gentle",
            "options": [
                "institutional",
                "precise",
                "flexible"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qatnashish",
            "RightAnswer": "attendance",
            "options": [
                "empire",
                "pregnancy",
                "excitement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "egalik",
            "RightAnswer": "ownership",
            "options": [
                "attendance",
                "empire",
                "pregnancy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "malaka",
            "RightAnswer": "qualification",
            "options": [
                "ownership",
                "attendance",
                "empire"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to'xtatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "suspend",
            "options": [
                "wander",
                "comprise",
                "summarize"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "amaliy",
            "RightAnswer": "functional",
            "options": [
                "gentle",
                "institutional",
                "precise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko'ngilli",
            "RightAnswer": "voluntary",
            "options": [
                "experimental",
                "interior",
                "racial"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xira, rangsiz",
            "RightAnswer": "pale",
            "options": [
                "blind",
                "spare",
                "wet"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dog'",
            "RightAnswer": "stain",
            "options": [
                "sigh",
                "stir",
                "snap"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sportchi",
            "RightAnswer": "athlete",
            "options": [
                "qualification",
                "ownership",
                "attendance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "organik",
            "RightAnswer": "organic",
            "options": [
                "functional",
                "gentle",
                "institutional"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "til",
            "RightAnswer": "tongue",
            "options": [
                "athlete",
                "qualification",
                "ownership"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 56": [
        {
            "Question": "xizmatchi",
            "RightAnswer": "server",
            "options": [
                "tongue",
                "athlete",
                "qualification"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tizimga oid",
            "RightAnswer": "structural",
            "options": [
                "organic",
                "functional",
                "gentle"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "veb-sayt",
            "RightAnswer": "website",
            "options": [
                "server",
                "tongue",
                "athlete"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ahmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "fool",
            "options": [
                "stain",
                "sigh",
                "stir"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yonida",
            "RightAnswer": "alongside",
            "options": [
                "regardless",
                "beneath",
                "beside"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "birlashtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "unite",
            "options": [
                "suspend",
                "wander",
                "comprise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muloyimlik bilan",
            "RightAnswer": "gently",
            "options": [
                "subsequently",
                "reasonably",
                "altogether"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hisoblamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "compute",
            "options": [
                "unite",
                "suspend",
                "wander"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "artmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "wipe",
            "options": [
                "fool",
                "stain",
                "sigh"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "g'alati",
            "RightAnswer": "weird",
            "options": [
                "structural",
                "organic",
                "functional"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qarash",
            "RightAnswer": "gaze",
            "options": [
                "wipe",
                "fool",
                "stain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "so'nmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "fade",
            "options": [
                "gaze",
                "wipe",
                "fool"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yo'tlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "cough",
            "options": [
                "fade",
                "gaze",
                "wipe"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "gipoteza",
            "RightAnswer": "hypothesis",
            "options": [
                "website",
                "server",
                "tongue"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qirolga oid",
            "RightAnswer": "royal",
            "options": [
                "voluntary",
                "experimental",
                "interior"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nazariy",
            "RightAnswer": "theoretical",
            "options": [
                "weird",
                "structural",
                "organic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "parda",
            "RightAnswer": "curtain",
            "options": [
                "hypothesis",
                "website",
                "server"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shahar hokimi",
            "RightAnswer": "mayor",
            "options": [
                "curtain",
                "hypothesis",
                "website"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zulmat",
            "RightAnswer": "darkness",
            "options": [
                "mayor",
                "curtain",
                "hypothesis"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xola, amma",
            "RightAnswer": "aunt",
            "options": [
                "darkness",
                "mayor",
                "curtain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "turnir",
            "RightAnswer": "tournament",
            "options": [
                "aunt",
                "darkness",
                "mayor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ro'yxatdan o'tish",
            "RightAnswer": "registration",
            "options": [
                "tournament",
                "aunt",
                "darkness"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "parcha",
            "RightAnswer": "fragment",
            "options": [
                "registration",
                "tournament",
                "aunt"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tinglovchi",
            "RightAnswer": "listener",
            "options": [
                "fragment",
                "registration",
                "tournament"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "immigratsiya",
            "RightAnswer": "immigration",
            "options": [
                "listener",
                "fragment",
                "registration"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muloyim",
            "RightAnswer": "tender",
            "options": [
                "pale",
                "blind",
                "spare"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zichlik",
            "RightAnswer": "density",
            "options": [
                "immigration",
                "listener",
                "fragment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xunuk",
            "RightAnswer": "ugly",
            "options": [
                "theoretical",
                "weird",
                "structural"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "modul",
            "RightAnswer": "module",
            "options": [
                "density",
                "immigration",
                "listener"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "samimiy ravishda",
            "RightAnswer": "faithfully",
            "options": [
                "gently",
                "subsequently",
                "reasonably"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kuz",
            "RightAnswer": "autumn",
            "options": [
                "module",
                "density",
                "immigration"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yonoq",
            "RightAnswer": "cheek",
            "options": [
                "autumn",
                "module",
                "density"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bog'lanish",
            "RightAnswer": "attachment",
            "options": [
                "cheek",
                "autumn",
                "module"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tutgich",
            "RightAnswer": "holder",
            "options": [
                "attachment",
                "cheek",
                "autumn"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "quyoshga oid",
            "RightAnswer": "solar",
            "options": [
                "ugly",
                "theoretical",
                "weird"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kulish",
            "RightAnswer": "grin",
            "options": [
                "cough",
                "fade",
                "gaze"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "atirgul, o'sdi",
            "RightAnswer": "rose",
            "options": [
                "slice",
                "shore",
                "grain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ot",
            "RightAnswer": "noun",
            "options": [
                "holder",
                "attachment",
                "cheek"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "omadli",
            "RightAnswer": "fortunate",
            "options": [
                "solar",
                "ugly",
                "theoretical"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaxshi",
            "RightAnswer": "alright",
            "options": [
                "okay",
                "monthly",
                "weekly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dangasa",
            "RightAnswer": "lazy",
            "options": [
                "fortunate",
                "solar",
                "ugly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "salom",
            "RightAnswer": "hello",
            "options": [
                "hi",
                "each",
                "another"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ochlik",
            "RightAnswer": "hunger",
            "options": [
                "noun",
                "holder",
                "attachment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sug'urta qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "insure",
            "options": [
                "compute",
                "unite",
                "suspend"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uyalmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "ashamed",
            "options": [
                "lazy",
                "fortunate",
                "solar"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asos solmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "found",
            "options": [
                "rear",
                "lean",
                "shut"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "blog",
            "RightAnswer": "blog",
            "options": [
                "rose",
                "slice",
                "shore"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chanqoqlik",
            "RightAnswer": "thirst",
            "options": [
                "hunger",
                "noun",
                "holder"
            ]
        }
    ]
}